1	1700	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_1_07	크랩 사냥이 완료되었습니다. 해적 모건에게 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Crab hunt is completed.  Report to Pirate Morgun.	0	0	0	Crab avı tamamlandı. Korsan Morgun'a bildir.	Has terminado de cazar los Crabs. Infórmalo al Pirata Morgun.	تم اصطياد الCrab. أخبر Pirate Morgan.	Die Jagd auf die Crabs ist abgeschlossen. Erstatte dem Piraten Morgun Bericht.
1	1701	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_01	전에 자네가 크랩을 사냥해준 덕분에 마음 편히 지낼 수 있었어.
몹쓸 해적 녀석들! 나도 해적이지만 동료를 도와주지 않는 녀석들은 같은 해적이라고 생각하지 않아.
그래서 말인데 이런 나에게 누군가 재미있는 제안을 해왔는데 한 번 들어보겠나?
얼마 전 콘스탄티노플에 있는 장군 라첼이 요즘 해적들의 동태가 심상치 않다면서 나에게 정보를 빼달라고 부탁하는 게야. 예전 같으면 동료를 배신하는 일 따위는 꿈에서라도 생각해 보지 않았을 테지만 지금은 달라. 왜냐구? 자네도 알다시피 몸 성치 않은 나를 이런 외진 곳에 버려놓은 녀석들을 동료라고 생각할 수 없네.
그래서 내 앞에서 떠벌리기 좋아하는 몇몇의 녀석들에게서 라첼이 원하는 정보를 얻었는데 그녀에게 편지를 전해주지 않겠나?	0	0	0	0	0	Thank ya for hunting the Crabs last time, I could rest in peace.
Pirates! I myself was once a pirate, but not helping out a fellow comrade...They do not deserve to be called pirates!
And so...Someone made an interesting proposal to me, ya interested in hearing it?
General Ratchel in Constantinople told me the pirates' movement seem fishy, and asked me for information. Would've never dreamt about betraying my comrades, but not anymore. Why? As ya know, deserting me in an isolated place...Can't consider them as my comrades, yeah?
So I heard some stuff Ratchel would like to hear, so please deliver him this letter, will ya?	0	0	0	Geçen sefer Crableri avladığın için teşekkürler, sayende huzura erdim. Korsanlar…O alçaklar! Ben denizde bir zamanlar korsandım ama yoldaşıma yardım etmemezlik yapmadım. Korsan adını haketmiyorlar. Neyse...Birisi bana ilginç bir teklifte bulundu, ne olduğunu duymak ister misin? Constantinople'dan General Ratchel bana korsanların çalışmalarının şüpheli göründüğünü söyledi ve benden ne olduğu hakkında bilgi istedi. Yoldaşlarıma ihanet edeceğimi rüyamda görsem inanmazdım, ama artık değiller. Neden mi? Bildiğin gibi ıssız bir yerde beni terkettiler...Onları yoldaşlarım olarak düşünemem, değil mi? Ratchel'in hoşuna gidecek bir şeyler duydum, lütfen bu mektubu ona teslim eder misin?	Gracias por cazar a los Crabs la vez pasada. Ahora puedo descansar en paz. Piratas... ¡Esos bastardos! Yo fui un pirata una vez, y si no ayudas a tus compañeros... ¡ no mereces ser un pirata! Alguien me hizo una interesante propuesta, ¿estás interesado en escucharla? La General Ratchel en Constantinople me contó que los Pirates se comportan de forma sospechosa y me pidió información. Nunca había pensado en traicionar a mis compañeros, pero ya no me importa.ellos me  abandonaron en un lugar desolado... ¿Puedo considerarlos como mis compañeros?Averigüé  algo que le podría interesar a Ratchel. Por favor, entrégale esta Letter. ¿Lo harás?	شكراً لك لاصطيادك الCrab المرة السابقة لقد استطعت الراحة في سلام. 
القراصنة .. هؤلاء الأوغاد! لقد كنت واحداً منهم ذات يوم ولكن بعدم مساعدة مساعد مقرب .. فلا يستحقون تسمية القراصنة!
لذلك ... أحدهم أعطاني عرضاً مثيراً هل أنت مهتم بسماع هذا العرض؟
أخبرني الجنرال Ratchel في Constantinople بأن تحركات القراصنة تبدو غريبة وطلب مني بعض المعلومات. لم أكن أتخيل أن أخون مساعدين ولكن ليس بعد الآن... لماذا؟ كما تعلم من هجروني في مكان منعزل لا يمكنني اعتبارهم مساعدين ييييه ؟
لذلك لقد سمعت بعض الأشياء التي ربما يود Ratchel سماعها لذا أرجوك قم بتوصيل هذا الخطاب له .. هلا قمت بهذا؟	Danke, dass du letztes Mal die Crabs gejagt hast, das hat mir Ruhe verschafft.
Piraten! Ich war selbst einst ein Pirat. Wenn man einem Kameraden nicht mal helfen will... Sie verdienen es nicht, Piraten genannt zu werden!
Also... Jemand hat mir einen interessanten Vorschlag gemacht, willst du ihn hören?
General Ratchel in Constantinople vermutet, dass die Piraten etwas vorhaben, er hat mich um Informationen gebeten. Ich hätte nie gedacht, je meine Kameraden zu verraten, aber das hat sich geändert. Warum? Wie du weißt, haben sie mich hier alleine gelassen... Kameraden sind das keine, oder?
Ich habe Dinge gehört, die Ratchel gerne wissen würde, bitte bring ihm diesen Brief, ja?
1	1702	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_02	크큭… 고맙네. 라첼에게 이 편지를 전해주게.	0	0	0	0	0	Gigle… Thanks.  Take this letter to Ratchel.	0	0	0	Hahah… Teşekkürler. Bu mektubu Ratchel'a götür.	Ji ji ji...Gracias. Lleva esta Letter a Ratchel.	ها هاها ها ... شكراً لك. خذ هذا الخطاب إلى Ratchel.	Lacht… Danke. Bring Ratchel diesen Brief.
1	1703	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_03	크큭… 생각이 바뀌면 다시 찾아오게.	0	0	0	0	0	Gigle… Come back when change your mind.	0	0	0	Hahah… Fikrini değiştirdiğinde bana geri dön.	Ji ji ji... Regresa cuando cambies de opinión.	ها هاها ها ... عد إلي عندما تغير رأيك.	Lach… Komm wieder, wenn du deine Meinung geändert hast.
1	1704	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_04	아직 콘스탄티노플에 있는 장군 라첼에게 편지를 전해주지 않았는가?	0	0	0	0	0	Didn't you deliver this letter to General Ratchel yet?	0	0	0	Hala mektubu General Ratchel'a teslim etmedin mi?	¿Aun no has entregado la Letter a Ratchel?	ألم تقم بتوصيل الخطاب إلى الجنرال Ratchel بعد؟	Hast du General Ratchel diesen Brief noch nicht gebracht?
1	1705	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_05	흠… 해적 모건의 편지군.
그가 우리의 제안을 받아들인 모양이군.
편지는 잘 받았네. 이것은 사례일세.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm..  This is Pirate Morgun's letter.
He finally accepted our offer.
Thanks for the letter.  This is your reward.	0	0	0	Hmm.. Bu Korsan Morgun'un mektubu. Sonunda teklifimizi kabul etmiş. Mektup için teşekkürler. İşte ödülün.	Jmm... Esta es una Letter del Pirata Morgun. Finalmente aceptó la oferta que le hice. Gracias por la Letter. Aquí está tu recompensa.	همممم ... هذا هو خطاب Pirate Morgan.
لقد قبل عرضنا أخيراً.
شكراً من أجل الخطاب. هذه هي مكافأتك.	Hmm. Das ist der Brief von Pirat Morgun.
Er hat endlich unser Angebot angenommen.
Danke für den Brief. Das ist deine Belohnung.
1	1706	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_06	해적의 편지를 받았습니다. 장군 라첼에게 편지를 전해주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've got pirate's letter.  Deliver it to General Ratchel.	0	0	0	Korsanın mektubunu aldın. Onu General Ratchel'a teslim et.	Has obtenido la Pirate's Letter. Entrégala a la General Ratchel.	لقد حصلت على خطاب القرصان. قم بوصيله إلى الجنرال Ratchel.	Du hast den Pirate's Letter. Bring ihn zu General Ratchel.
1	1707	SN_TALK_QNO_AM_FERRY1_2_07	소지품 창이 꽉 차있어서 편지를 줄 수 없어. 빈 공간을 만들고 다시 찾아오면 편지를 주지.	0	0	0	0	0	I can't give you the letter because your inventory is currently full.  Please come back when you have empty space in your inventory.	0	0	0	Sana mektubu veremiyorum çünkü envanterin dolu. Lütfen envanterinde boş yer olduğunda geri gel.	Me gustaría recompensarte pero tu inventario se encuentra lleno. Vacía algunos espacios y regresa de nuevo.	لا يمكنني إعطاؤك الخطاب لأن خزينتك ممتلئة. قم بإفراغ موضع بها ثم عد لي.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir den Brief nicht geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	1708	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_01	마르마라해 건너 존재하는 해적들의 세력이 강해지는 가운데 군영에는 좋지 않은 소식들만 들어오고 있소.
그런데 해적들이 곧 콘스탄티노플을 침략할 것이라는 정보를 입수한 이래 별다른 해결 방법을 찾지 못하고 있던 중 최근 해적 스파이에게서 좋은 정보를 얻게 되었소.
그가 제공한 정보에 따르면 해적들의 공격을 주도하는 해적 돌격대장을 해치우면 해적들의 기세를 꺾을 수 있음은 물론 콘스탄티노플 침략 계획에 큰 차질을 불러 일으킬 것이라고 했소.
하지만 검증되지 않은 해적 스파이가 제공한 정보를 전부 믿기에는 군대의 위험이 크기 때문에 해적 한 명을 포로로 잡아 와서 확실한 정보인지 알아낼 필요가 있소.
지금 군영에서는 군인이 모자라 따로 해적을 포로로 잡아 올 만한 형편이 아닌데 당신이 그 일을 대신해 주지 않겠소?	0	0	0	0	0	Pirates over the Marmara Sea are gaining influence, while we at the Military Camp are receiving bad news. 
After having obtained information of pirates planning to invade Constantinople, we had no solution against it. However, we did manage to lay our hands on some good news through a pirate spy.
Based on the spy's information, it is believed that defeating the pirate's assault commander, the one in charge of making all necessary attacks, will greatly reduce the pirates' morale. Not only that, it can also cause major setback in their invasion plan.
But, moving the whole army by trusting information provided from an unverified pirate spy is a big risk, so we first need to capture a pirate to see if the information is true.
Soldiers are lacking in the Military Camp, and we are not in the situation to dispatch an army to hold a pirate captive. Thus I ask you to do the job for us.	0	0	0	Marmara Denizi üzerindeki korsanlar giderek nüfuz kazanıyor. Kötü haberi Askeri Kampta aldık. Korsanların Constantinople'yi istila planı yaptıkları bilgisini aldıktan sonra bu duruma karşı bir çözüm bulamadık. Ama bir korsan casus aracılığıyla bazı güzel haberler bulmayı başardık.   Casusun verdiği bilgiye göre, bütün saldırıları komuta eden tek bir kişi olan korsanların taarruz kumandanını öldürmenin, korsanların moralini oldukça bozacağı söyleniyor. Üstelik bu onların istila planında da büyük bir aksamaya neden olabilir. Fakat doğruluğu tasdik edilmemiş bir casus korsanın lafına güvenerek koca orduyu harekete geçirmek büyük bir risk olur, bu yüzden ilk olarak bir korsan esir alıp bilginin doğru olup olmadığını kontrol etmemiz gerek. Askeri Kampta asker kıtlığı çekiyoruz ve bir korsanı esir almak için orduyu gönderecek durumda değiliz. Bu yüzden işi bizim için yapmanı istiyorum.	Los Pirates de Marmara Sea están ganando influencia, mientras que nosotros recibimos malas noticias en el campamento militar. Supimos que los Pirates están planeando invadir Constantinople, pero no tenemos solución contra eso. Sin embargo, pudimos obtener información por medio de un pirata espía. Según lo que nos contó el espía, si derrotamos al Pirate's Assaul Commander quien está encargado de dirigir todos los ataques, los Pirates perderán los ánimos; además, esto causaría un mayor contratiempo en sus planes. Sin embargo, mover a toda la armada confiando en información no verificada es un gran riesgo. Por ende, debemos capturar primero un Pirate para confirmar que la información sea verdadera. No hay muchos soldados en el campamento; tampoco estamos en condiciones de enviar un ejército para capturar a un Pirate. Por eso te pido que hagas ese trabajo por nosotros.	القراصنة عبر بحر مارمارا يحصلون على سلطة وتأثير قوي بينما تأTina أخبار سيئة في المخيم العسكري. بعد الحصول على معلومات بأن القراصنة يخططون للهجوم على Constantinople فليس لدينا حل تجاه هذا. ومع ذلك فقد خططنا لوضع أيدينا على بعض الأخبار الجيدة عبر جاسوس القراصنة.
واعتماداً على معلومات الجاسوس فمن المعتقد أن هزيمة قائد هجوم القرصانة الرجل المسئول عن صنع جميع الهجمات اللازمة سيقلل من معنويات القراصن بشدة. وليس ذلك فقط ولكن أيضاً سيتسبب لهم في عقبات وعوائق في خطتهم الهجوموية.
ولكن تحريك جميع الجيش بالوثوق على المعلومات التي أخذناها من جاسوس غير موثوق فيه ربما يكون خطر كبير لذلك سنحتاج أولاً إلى القبض على القرصان لنرى ما إذا كانت هذه المعلومات صحيحة.
ولكن لدينا عجز في الجنود في المخيم العسكري ولسنا في موقف يسمح لنا بإرسال جيش لأسر قرصان. لذلك فسأطلب منك أن تقوم بهذه المهمة من أجلنا؟	Piraten am Marmarameer werden immer einflussreicher, während es für uns im Militärlager nur schlechte Nachrichten gibt. 
Wir erhielten Nachricht, dass die Piraten Constantinople angreifen wollten, konnten aber nichts unternehmen. Aber dann haben wir durch einen Spion bei den Piraten gute Neuigkeiten erhalten.
Laut den Informationen des Spions nehmen wir an, dass der Tod des Kommandanten der Piraten, der für alle Angriffe verantwortlich ist, die Moral der Piraten sehr beeinträchtigen würde. Und nicht nur das, es sollte ihrem Invasionsplan auch sehr schaden.
Aber es ist ein großes Risiko, die ganze Armee wegen der Information eines Piratenspions in Marsch zu setzen, also müssen wir erst einen Piraten gefangen nehmen, um die Information zu bestätigen.
Wir haben nicht genügend Soldaten im Militärlager und können keine Armee aussenden, um einen Piraten zu fangen. Also frage ich dich, ob du diese Aufgabe für uns übernimmst.
1	1709	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_02	고맙소. 마르마라해를 건너면 파이럿 브리간드라는 해적들이 있을 것이오.
이것은 군대에서 쓰는 그물로 만든 덫인데 그것을 이용하여 다른 해적들이 눈치채지 않게 그들 중 하나를 포획해 오시오.
시간이 흐를수록 덫이 약해져 해적이 도망갈 수 있으니 서둘러 돌아와야 할 것이오.	0	0	0	0	0	Thank you.  You will see Pirate Brigands across the Marmara Sea.
This is a trap made from a net used in the army, so use this to hold a pirate captive without any other pirates noticing it.
The trap will weaken as time passes, so you must hurry.
When proceeding this quest, you may not use return scrolls or portals.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. Marmara Denizinin karşısında Pirate Brigand'ları göreceksin. Bu ordunun kullandığı ağdan yapılan bir tuzak, bunu diğer korsanlar farketmeden bir korsan esir almak için kullan. Zaman geçtikçe tuzak zayıflayacak, bu yüzden acele etmelisin. Bu görevi yaparken Return scroll ya da portalları kullanamazsın.	Gracias. Verás a los Pirate Brigands al cruzar el Maramara Sea. Esta es una trampa hecha con una Net de la armada; úsala para capturar al Pirate sin que los otros se den de cuenta. La Net se debilitará con el paso del tiempo, así que debes darte prisa. Mientras realizas esta misión, no puedes usar Scrolls ni portales.	شكراً لك.
سترى القرصان Brigand عبر نهر Marmara
هذه مصيدة مصنوعة من شبكة يستخدمها الجيش لذا استخدمها للقبض على القرصان الأسير بدون أن يشعر بك أي قرصان آخر. 
ستضعف المصيدة بمرور الوقت لذا يجب أن تقوم بهذا سريعاً.
]عند القيام بهذه المهمة لن يمكنك استخدام رسائل العودة أو البوابات[
	Danke. Du wirst Pirate Brigands auf der anderen Seite des Marmarameers finden.
Diese Falle wurden aus Netzen der Armee hergestellt, fang mit ihr einen Piraten, ohne dass andere Piraten es merken.
Mit der Zeit wird die Falle schwächer werden, also musst du dich beeilen.
Auf dieser Quest darfst du weder Return Scrolls noch Portale benutzen.
1	1710	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_03	콘스탄티노플이 침략 당하면 당신도 무사하지 못할 텐데…	0	0	0	0	0	You won't be safe if Constantinople gets invaded…	0	0	0	Constantinople istilaya uğrarsa güvende olmayacaksın…	No estarás a salvo si Constantinople es invadida.	لن تكون بأمان إذا هاجموا Constantinople.	Du bist in Gefahr, wenn Constantinople überfallen wird…
1	1711	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_04	해적들이 침략 준비를 거의 끝내고 콘스탄티노플로 올 준비를 하고 있다는 소식을 접했소.
시간이 없소. 서둘러 파이럿 브리간드를 포획해 오시오.	0	0	0	0	0	I heard a news about pirates are almost ready for invasion of Constantinople.  There is not much time left.  Capture Pirate Brigand quickly.	0	0	0	Korsanların her an Constantinople'yi istila edecekleri hakkında yeni bir duyum aldım. Fazla zaman kalmadı. Bir an önce Pirate Brigand'ı ele geçir.	Escuché la noticia de que los Pirates casi están listos para invadir Constantinople. No queda mucho tiempo. Captura al Pirate Brigand rápido.	لقد سمعت شيئاً جديداً عن القراصنة أنهم يتجهزون لمهاجمة Constantinople. لم يتبق أمامنا الكثير من الوقت. قم بالقبض على بايرات بريجاند بسرعة.	Ich habe gehört, dass die Piraten fast bereit sind, in Constantinople einzufallen. Es bleibt nicht viel Zeit. Fang schnell einen Pirate Brigand.
1	1712	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_05	그물을 모두 사용해서 포획을 할 수 없게 되었나보군. 여기 그물을 받으시오.	0	0	0	0	0	You look like you can not capture anymore because you used all of the net.  Take this net.	0	0	0	Tüm netleri kullandığın için artık esir alamayacaksın gibi görünüyor. Bu neti al.	Parece que ya no lo puedes capturar porque usaste toda la Net. Toma esta Net.	يبدو أنك غير قادر على القبض على أحد بعد ذلك لأنك استخدمت جميع الشباك. خذ هذه الشبكة.	Du scheinst kein Netz mehr zu haben, um jemanden zu fangen. Nimm dieses Netz.
1	1713	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_06	그물 받기	0	0	0	0	0	Get Net	0	0	0	Net'i Al	Toma la Net	خذ الشبكة	Hol Netz.
1	1714	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_07	그물을 다시 주었으니 이번에는 꼭 성공하시길 바라오.	0	0	0	0	0	You got net again and I hope you succeed this time.	0	0	0	Net'i tekrar aldın ve umarım bu sefer başırırsın.	Obtuviste otra Net. Espero que lo logres esta vez.	لقد حصلت على الشبكة مرة أخرى آمل أن تنجح هذه المرة.	Du hast wieder ein Netz, ich hoffe, du hast diesmal Erfolg.
1	1715	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_08	여분의 그물을 모두 사용하여 당신에게 줄 그물이 없소.
그물을을 다시 구해볼테니 내일 다시 찾아와 주시오.	0	0	0	0	0	You used all of extra net so there isn't any left for you.
I'll try to get more net so come back tomorrow.	0	0	0	Fazladan netlerini da bitirdiğin için verecek başka kalmadı. Biraz daha almaya çalışacağım bu yüzden yarın tekrar gel.	Usaste toda la Net y no queda más. Trataré de conseguir más. Regresa mañana.	لقد استخدمت جميع الشباك الإضافية ولم يتبق لدي أي منها. سأحاول الحصول على المزيد إذا عدت إلي غداً.	Du hast alle Netze aufgebraucht, ich habe keine mehr für dich.
Ich werde versuchen, mehr zu bekommen, komm morgen wieder.
1	1716	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_09	물건을 주고 싶은데 소지품 창이 꽉 차있소. 한 칸 이상 비우고 다시 찾아오시오.	0	0	0	0	0	I would like to give you an item but your inventory is currently full.  Please come back when you have an empty space in your inventory.	0	0	0	Sana bir eşya vermek istiyordum fakat envanterin dolu. Lütfen envanterin boş olduğunda geri gel.	Me gustaría darte un ítem pero tu inventario está lleno. Por favor ,regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario	أرغب في إعطائك أداة ولكن خزينتك ممتلئة. عد إلي بعد إفراغ موضع في خزينتك.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir den Gegenstand nicht geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	1717	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_10	수고했소.
당신 덕분에 콘스탄티노플이 큰 위험으로부터 벗어났소.	0	0	0	0	0	Well done.
Constantinople got rid of a great danger because of you.	0	0	0	Aferin. Sayende Constantinople büyük bir tehlikeden kurtuldu.	Bien hecho. Has salvado a Constantinople de un gran peligro.	حسناً فعلت.
لقد نجت Constantinople من الخطر العظيم بفضلك.	Gut gemacht.
Dank dir ist Constantinople nicht mehr in Gefahr.
1	1718	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_11	파이럿 브리간드 포획을 성공하였습니다. 라첼에게 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Capturing Pirate Brigand has succeeded.  Report to Ratchel.	0	0	0	Pirate Brigand'ı ele geçirmeyi başardın. Ratchel'a bildir.	Lograste capturar al Pirate Brigand. Infórmalo a Ratchel.	لقد نجح القبض على بايارت برينجاد. أخبر Ratchel.	Du hast einen Pirate Brigand gefangen. Erstatte Ratchel Bericht.
1	1719	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_12	소지품 창에 포획된 몬스터를 저장할 공간이 없습니다. 빈 공간을 만들고 다시 시도하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You have no space for captured monster in your inventory.  Please come back when you have an empty space in your inventory.	0	0	0	Ele geçirdiğin canavarı için envanterinde yer yok. Lütfen envanterinde boş yer olduğunda geri gel.	No tienes espacio en tu inventario para el monstruo capturado. Por favor, regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario.	لا يوجد لديك مساحة كافية للوحش المقبوض عليه في خزينتك. عد إلي بعد إفراغ موضع في خزينتك.	Du hast keinen Platz in deinem Inventar für das eingefangene Monster. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	1720	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_13	플레이어가 죽었으므로 포획된 파이럿 브리간드가 도망갔습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Captured Pirate Brigand ran away due to player's death.	0	0	0	Oyuncu öldüğü için Yakalanan Pirate Brigand kaçtı.	La captura del Pirate Brigand ha fallado debido a que el personaje murió.	لقد هرب Pirate Brigand بسبب موت اللاعب.	Der Pirate Brigand ist weggerannt, weil der Spielercharakter gestorben ist.
1	1721	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_14	덫이 풀어져서 파이럿 브리간드가 도망갔습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Pirate Brigand ran away because the trap was open.	0	0	0	Tuzak açıldığı için Pirate Brigand kaçtı.	El Pirate Brigand ha escapado ya que la trampa fue abierta.	لقد هرب Pirate Brigand لأن المصيدة كانت مفتوحة.	Der Pirate Brigand ist geflüchtet, weil die Falle offen war.
1	1722	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_15	덫의 유효시간이 10 분 남았습니다. 서둘러 라첼에게 데리고 가세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Trap will lasts for 10 minutes.  Please hurry to Rachel.	0	0	0	Tuzağın 10 dakikası kaldı. Lütfen acele et ve onu Ratchel'a götür.	Le quedan 10 minutos a la trampa. Apresúrate y ve con Ratchel.	لم يتبق سوى 10 دقائق. أسرع إلى Ratchel.	Die Falle wird 10 Minuten funktionieren. Geh schnell zu Rachel.
1	1723	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_16	덫의 유효시간이 5 분 남았습니다. 서둘러 라첼에게 데리고 가세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Trap will lasts for 5 minutes.  Please hurry to Rachel.	0	0	0	Tuzağın 5 dakikası kaldı. Lütfen acele et ve onu Ratchel'a götür.	Le quedan 5 minutos a la trampa. Apresúrate y ve con Ratchel.	لم يتبق سوى 5 دقائق. أسرع إلى Ratchel.	Die Falle wird 5 Minuten funktionieren. Geh schnell zu Rachel.
1	1724	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_17	이미 파이럿 브리간드를 포획했으므로 덫을 설치할 수 없습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can not set up a trap because you've already captured Pirate Brigand.	0	0	0	Zaten Pirate Brigand'ı ele geçirdiğin için bir tuzak kuramazsın.	No puedes poner la trampa porque ya has capturado al Pirate Brigand.	لا يمكنك وضع المصيدة لأنك بالفعل قمت بالقبض على Pirate Brigand.	Du hast schon einen Pirate Brigand gefangen, also kannst du keine Falle aufstellen.
1	1725	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_18	주변에 몬스터가 존재하므로 덫을 설치할 수 없습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can not set up a trap because there are monsters around.	0	0	0	Etrafta canavarlar olduğu için bir tuzak kuramazsın.	No puedes poner la trampa porque hay monstruos alrededor.	لا يمكنك وضع المصيدة لأنه توجد وحوش حولك.	Du kannst hier keine Falle aufstellen, es sind Monster in der Nähe.
1	1726	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_1_19	몬스터 포획에 실패하였습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You've fail to capture the monster.	0	0	0	Canavarı yakalamayı başaramadın.	Has fallado en capturar al monstruo	لقد فشلت في القبض على الوحش.	Du hast das Monster nicht eingefangen.
1	1727	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_01	포획한 해적 스파이에게서 얻은 정보가 사실임을 밝혀냈소.
시시각각 해적들의 공격 소식이 들려오고 있는데 그들이 마르마라해를 건너기 전에 해적 돌격대장을 해치워 해적의 침략 계획을 저지해야 하오.
해적을 성공적으로 포획해 온 것으로 당신이 훌륭한 용병임이 증명되었는데 다시 한 번 그 뛰어난 실력을 보여주지 않겠소?
해적 돌격대장을 사냥하여 그의 전리품을 얻어 온다면 그에 맞는 보상을 해주겠소.	0	0	0	0	0	We have revealed from the captive that the spy's information was true after all.
Every moment we hear the news of pirates' attack. We must defeat the Pirate's Assault Commander before they cross the Marmara Sea, to prevent their invasion plan.
You have proven yourself to be a great mercenary by successfully holding a pirate captive, won't you show us your skills again?
Hunt the Pirate Assault Commander, and bring us his spoil to be rewarded.
	0	0	0	Ele geçirdiğimiz esirden, casusun verdiği bilginin doğru olduğunu ortaya çıkardık.  Her dakika korsanların saldırı haberlerini duyuyoruz. İstila planlarını önlemek için Marmara Denizi'ni aşmadan önce Pirates Assault Commander'ı öldürmeliyiz. Bir korsan rehin alarak büyük bir asker olduğunu kanıtladın, bize yeteneklerini tekrar göstermek ister misin? Pirate Assault Commander'ı avla ve ödüllendirilmek için bize onun spoilini getir.	Hemos descubierto por el Pirate cautivo que la información del espía es cierta después de todo. Siempre tenemos noticias sobre ataques de Pirates. Debemos derrotar su Pirate's Assault Commander antes de que crucen el mar Marmara Sea para prevenir su plan de invasión. Has probado ser un gran mercenario al lograr la captura del Pirate, ¿nos mostrarás tus habilidades de nuevo? Derrota al Pirate's Assault Commander y tráenos su botín para recompensarte.	لقد استوضحنا من القرصان الأسير بأن معلومات الجاسوس كانت صحيحة بعد كل هذا.
وفي كل دقيقة نسمع أخبار عن هجوم القراصنة. يجب علينا هزيمة Pirate Assault Commander قبل عبور نهر مارمارا لمنع خطة الهجوم.
يجب عليك إثبات نفسك لتصبح مرتزقة عظيم بالنجاح في قتل Pirate Assault Commander هلا أظرت لنا مهاراتك مرة أخرى؟
قم باصطياد Pirate Assault Commander وأحضره لنا غنائمه لنكافئك عليها.	Wir haben von dem Gefangenen erfahren, dass die Informationen des Spions doch stimmten.
Die Piraten können jeden Augenblick angreifen. Wir müssen den Pirate's Assault Commander besiegen, bevor sie das Marmarameer überqueren, um ihre Invasion zu verhindern.
Du hast dich als großartiger Söldner bewiesen, als du einen Piraten gefangen hast. Demonstrierst du uns nochmals deine Fähigkeiten?
Jag den Pirate Assault Commander und bring uns seine Beute, dann wirst du belohnt.

1	1728	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_02	고맙소. 그럼 해적 포로에게서 얻은 정보와 당신이 해야 할 일을 알려주겠소.
해적 돌격대장은 콘스탄티노플 침략을 위해 파이럿 브리간드 챔피언들에게 그들만이 알 수 있는 의미가 담긴 깃발을 나누어 주었다고 하오. 그 깃발을 흔들면 자세한 내용을 알아보기 위해 해적 돌격대장이 나타난다고 들었소.
현재 해적 돌격대장은 시기아 선착장 남동쪽에 있는 할리카르나소스성 폐허에서 머무르고 있는데 파이럿 브리간드 챔피언에게서 얻은 해적의 깃발을 성 근처에서 흔들면 그를 만날 수 있을 것이오.
해적 돌격대장은 무리를 지어 다니기 때문에 혼자의 힘으로는 상대하기 버거울 테니 꼭 파티를 이루어 가도록 하시오. 그리고 빨리 해치우지 못하면 자신의 불리함을 깨닫고 도망가기 때문에 서둘러 무찔러야 할 것이오.	0	0	0	0	0	Thank you.  Then I must tell you what to do with the information I got from the prisoner.
It is said that Pirate Assault Commander gave out flags to Pirate Brigand Champions for the invasion of Constantinople. Waving the flag will bring the Pirate Assault Commander to presence.
Currently the Pirate Assault Commander is staying at the ruins of Harlikarnasos Castle, located at southeast of Sigia Dock. You can meet the commander by using the Pirate's Flag received from Pirate Brigand Champions nearby the castle.
Pirate Assault Commander is always with a group of comrades, so make sure you form a party to hunt him down. And if you don't defeat him quickly, he will start to run away.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. O halde sana mahkumdan aldığım bilgiyle ne yapacağını söylemeliyim. Söylendiğine göre Pirates Assault Commander flaglerini Constantinople'nin istilası için Pirate Brigand Champion'a vermiş. Flag'i sallamak Pirate Assault Commander'ın ortaya çıkmasını sağlayacak. Bu aralar Pirate Assault Commander Sigia Limanı'nın güneydoğusunda bulunan Harlikarnasos Kalesi'nin yıkıntıları arasında kalıyor. Kalenin yanındaki Pirate Brigand Champion'dan Pirate's Flag'i alıp kullanarak commander'la karşılaşabilirsin. Pirate Assault Commander devamlı bir grup yoldaşıyladır, bu yüzden onu öldürmek için bir parti kurduğuna emin ol. Ve eğer onu bir an önce öldürmezsen kaçmaya başlayacak.	Gracias. Entonces te diré qué hacer basándome en la información del Pirate prisionero. Se dice que el Pirate Assault Commander repartió banderas a los Pirate Brigand Champions para la invasión de Constantinople. Ondear la bandera atraerá la presencia del Pirate Assault Commander. En estos momentos, el Pirate Assault Commander se está alojando en las ruinas del castillo de Harlikarnasos localizado al sureste de Sigia Dock. Podrás ver al Commander si usas la Pirate's Flag que recibieron los Pirate Brigand Champions cerca del castillo. El Pirate Assault Commander está siempre con un grupo de compañeros, así que asegúrate ir en grupo para derrotarlos. Si no lo derrotas rápido, escapará.	شكراً لك. سأخبرك المعلومات التي حصلت عليها من السجين.
يقال أن Pirate Assault Commander أعطى علم Pirate Brigand البطل لهجماته على Constantinople. بالتلويح  بهذا العلم سيجعل Assault Commander يظهر.
وحالياً يقيم كوماندر في أطلال قلعة هارليكارناسوس الموجدة في جنوب شرق رصيف سيجيا. يمكنك مقابلة القائد باستخدام علم القرصان الذي أخذته من بطل القراصنة برينجاد بجوار القلعة.
هجوم القراصنة يكون دائماً في مجموعات من الزملاء لذلك تأكد من تكوين فريق لاصطيادهم. وإذا لم تهزمه بسرعة سيبدأ في الهرب.	Danke. Dann sage ich dir, was mit den Informationen, die ich vom Gefangenen bekommen habe, zu tun ist.
Anscheinend hat der Pirate Assault Commander den Pirate Brigand Champions für die Invasion von Constantinople Fahnen gegeben. Wenn man diese Fahnen schwenkt, ruft das den Pirate Assault Commander herbei.
Der Pirate Assault Commander befindet sich momentan bei den Ruinen des Schlosses Harlikarnasos, südöstlich vom Droa-Dock. Du rufst den Commander mit Hilfe der Pirate's Flag, die du bei den Pirate Brigand Champions in der Nähe des Schlosses findest.
Der Pirate Assault Commander hat immer eine Gruppe Kameraden bei sich, also solltest du ihm in einer Gruppe gegenübertreten. Und wenn du ihn nicht schnell besiegst, wird er flüchten.
1	1729	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_03	당신의 강한 힘을 어디에 쓰려고 이 험한 시기에 도움 주는 것을 꺼려하는 것이오?	0	0	0	0	0	Why are you hiding your strength in  such a rough time from helping?	0	0	0	Bu kadar zor bir zamanda neden yardımını esirgiyorsun?	¿Por qué no usas tu fuerza para ayudarnos en esta situación tan difícil?	أنت تتهرب من المساعدة بقوتك في وقت عصيب مثل هذا؟	Warum leihst du uns in solch schweren Zeiten nicht deine Kraft?
1	1730	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_04	시간이 없소. 해적의 힘이 더 커지기 전에 그들을 제압해야 할 것이오.
해적 돌격대장을 해치우고 전리품을 나에게 가져오시오.	0	0	0	0	0	There is no time.  You need to defeat before pirates power increases. 
Defeat Pirate Assault Commander and bring me the prize.	0	0	0	Zaman yok. Korsanlar güçlenmeden önce mağlup etmen gerek.
Pirate Assault Commander'ı öldür ve bana spoilini getir.	No hay tiempo. Debes derrotarlos antes de que su poder aumente. Derrota al Pirate Assault Commander y tráeme el Prize.	لا يوجد وقت. ستحتاج لهزيمته قبل تزايد قوة القراصنة. 
قم بهزيمة Pirate Assault Commander وأحضر لي الجائزة.	Es bleibt keine Zeit. Du musst siegen, bevor die Macht der Piraten größer wird. 
Besiege den Pirate Assault Commander und bring mir die Beute.
1	1731	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_05	보상을 하고 싶은데 소지품 창이 꽉 찼소. 한 칸 이상 비우고 다시 찾아오시오.	0	0	0	0	0	I would like to reward you but your inventory is currently full.  Please come back when you have an empty space in your inventory.	0	0	0	Seni ödüllendirmek istiyordum fakat envanterin dolu. Lütfen envanterinde boş yer olduğunda geri gel.	Me gustaría recompensarte pero tu inventario está lleno. Por favor, regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario	أرغب في مكافأتك ولكن خزينتك ممتلئة. عد إلي بعد إفراغ موضع في خزينتك.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir die Belohnung nicht geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	1732	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_06	수고했소. 해적의 공격을 저지했으니 이제 한 숨 돌릴 수 있게 되었소.	0	0	0	0	0	Well done.  Now I can take a rest since you defeated the pirates.	0	0	0	Aferin. Korsanları öldürdüğüne göre artık rahat bir nefes alabilirim.	Bien hecho. Ahora puedo descansar ya que derrotaste a los Pirates.	حسناً فعلت. الآن يمكنني الراحة بما أنك هزمت القراصنة.	Gut gemacht. Jetzt kann ich mich ausruhen, da du die Piraten besiegt hast.
1	1733	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_07	해적의 깃발을 획득했습니다. 할리카르나소스성에 가서 해적 돌격대장을 불러내세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've got pirate's flag.  Go to Harlikarnasos Castle and call out Pirate Assault Commander.	0	0	0	Pirate's flag'i aldın. Harlikarnasos Kalesi'ne git ve Pirate Assault Commander'ı oraya çek.	Has obtenido la Pirate's Flag. Ve al castillo de Harlikarnasos y atrae al Pirate Assault Commander.	لقد حصلت على علم القراصنة. اذهب إلى قلعة هاريليكارناسوس واستدعي Pirate Assault Commander.	Du hast die Pirate's Flag. Geh zum Schloss Harlikarnasos und ruf den Pirate Assault Commander.
1	1734	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_08	경험치 분배/ 아이템 균등분배 파티가 아니므로 해적의 깃발을 사용할 수 없습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can not use pirate's flag because you are not in exp / item auto share party.	0	0	0	Pirate's flag'i kullanamazsın çünkü oto. deneyim / item paylaşımı olan bir partide değilsin.	No puedes usar la Pirate's Flag porque no perteneces a un grupo que comparta ítems y experiencia automáticamente.	لا يمكنك استخدام علمت القراصنة لأنك لست عضو في فريق بحالة التوزيع التلقائي للخبرة/الأدوات.	Du kannst die Pirate's Flag nicht benutzen, weil du nicht in einer Gruppe mit Auto-EXP und Gegenstand-Auto-Teilen bist.
1	1735	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_09	깃발을 사용할 수 있는 지역이 아닙니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can not use flag in this area.	0	0	0	Bu bölgede flagi kullanamazsın.	No puedes usar la Flag en esta zona.	لا يمكنك استخدام العلم في هذه المنطقة.	Du kannst die Fahne hier nicht benutzen.
1	1736	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_10	부탁할 일이 있는데 경험치 분배, 아이템 공동분배 파티를 하고 찾아오시면 알려주겠소.	0	0	0	0	0	I would like to ask you a favor, come back when you form a party with exp / item auto share.	0	0	0	Senden bir iyilik isteyeceğim, oto. deneyim / item paylaşımı olan bir parti oluşturduğunda geri gel.	Me gustaría pedirte un favor. Regresa cuando estés en un grupo que comparta ítems y experiencia automáticamente.	أرغب في طلب المساعدة منك عد إلي عندما تكون في فريق بحالة التوزيع التلقائي للخبرة/الأدوات.	Ich brauche deine Hilfe. Kehre zurück, nachdem du dich einer Gruppe mit Auto-EXP und Gegenstand-Auto-Teilen angeschlossen hast.
1	1737	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_2_11	돌격대장의 전리품을 획득했습니다. 장군 라첼에게 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've got Assault Commander's prize.  Report to General Ratchel.	0	0	0	Assault Commander'ın ganimetini aldın. General Ratchel'a bildir.	Has obtenido el Assault Commander's Prize. Infórmalo a la General Ratchel.	لقد حصلت على جائزة Assault Commander. أخبر الجنرال Ratchel.	Du hast den Assault Commander's Prize. Erstatte General Ratchel Bericht.
1	1738	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_01	해적 소탕 작전을 통해 해적 돌격대장의 전리품을 얻었는데 그것은 붉은 역십자가였소.
그런데 붉은 역십자가를 군영에 들여온 이후 밤에 군영에서 보초를 서는 병사들이 이상한 소리를 들었다는 보고를 하고 있소. 나 역시 직접 그 이상한 소리를 확인했는데 희미하게 누군가의 이름을 부르는 소리 같았는데 그 이름은 '세니엘' 이었소.
아무래도 전리품으로 얻은 붉은 역십자가에 무슨 사연이 있는 것 같은데 성직자 가브리엘이라면 붉은 역십자가의 유래를 알지도 모르오.
가브리엘에게 붉은 역십자가를 전해주고 십자가에 담긴 사연을 내게 알려주지 않겠소?	0	0	0	0	0	You obtained the commander's spoil from the pirate sweeping mission, which turns out to be a reversed cross in red.
But after we brought in the reversed cross into the military camp, I am receiving reports from soldiers on watch that they continue to hear weird noises. I myself heard the noise, and it sounded like a name...The name it was calling was 'Seniel'.
Seems like there is a story based on the Red Reversed Cross you brought in, why don't you check it with Clergy Gabriel?
Take the Red Reversed Cross to Gabriel, and tell me the story behind it.	0	0	0	Korsan süpürücü görevin ardından red reversed cross'a dönüşen commander'ın ganimetini aldın. Fakat reversed cross askeri kampa getirdikten sonra gözcü askerlerden tuhaf sesler duymaya devam ettikleri raporunu aldım. Ben kendim de sesi duydum, bir isim seslenir gibi bir sesti... Çağırdığı isim 'Seniel' idi. Getirdiğin Red Reversed Cross'un bir hikayesi var gibi gözüküyor, neden gidip Rahip Gabriel'den bir soruşturmuyorsun? Red Reversed Cross'u Gabriel'e götür ve ardında yatan hikayeyi bana anlat.	Obtuviste el Commander's Spoil de la misión, el cual resultó ser una Red Reversed Cross.Después de traerla al campamento militar, los soldados de vigilancia dicen escuchar unos ruidos extraños. Yo misma escuché el ruido y suena como un nombre. El nombre que llamaba era "Seniel". Parece que hay una historia basada en la Red Reversed Cross que trajiste. ¿Por qué no averiguas con el clérigo Gabriel? Lleva la Red Reversed Cross a Gabriel y luego cuéntame la historia detrás de ella.	لقد حصلت على منهوبات القراصنة من مهمة إبادة القراصنة والتي تتحول لتصحبح صليب معكوس أحمر.
ولكن بعدما جلبت االصليب المعكوس إلى المخيم العسكري تصلني تقارير من الجنود بأنهم يستمرون في استماع ضحة غريبة. وأنا نفسي قد سمعت هذه الضحة وكانت مثل اسم ... هذا الاسم كان يسمى "Seniel"
يبدو أن هناك قصة وراء هذا الصليب الأحمر المعكوس الذي جلبته لماذا لا تتفقد ذلك مع القس Gabriel؟
خذ الصليب الأحمر المعكوس إلى Gabriel وأخبرني ما القصة وراءه.	Du hast die Beute des Kommandanten von den Piraten bekommen, die sich als umgekehrtes rotes Kreuz herausstellt.
Aber nachdem wir das umgekehrte Kreuz ins Militärlager gebracht hatten, habe ich von den Wachsoldaten gehört, dass sie seltsame Geräusche vernommen haben. Ich selbst habe die Geräusche auch gehört, es hörte sich wie ein Name an... Der Name, der gerufen wurde, war 'Seniel'.
Das Red Reversed Cross, das du gebracht hast, scheint eine Geschichte zu haben. Warum fragst du nicht den Geistlichen Gabriel?
Bring das Red Reversed Cross zu Gabriel, und erzähl mir seine Geschichte.
1	1739	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_02	고맙소. 가브리엘은 대성당에 가면 찾을 수 있을 것이오.	0	0	0	0	0	Thank you.  Gabriel can be found at the Cathedral.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. Gabriel'i Katedral'de bulabilirsin.	Gracias. Encontrarás a Gabriel en la Catedral.	شكراً لك. يمكنك أن تجد Gabriel في الكاتدرائية.	Danke. Gabriel kannst du bei der Kathedrale finden.
1	1740	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_03	다른 바쁜 일이 있는 것 같으니 다른 사람을 찾아보겠소.	0	0	0	0	0	Looks like you have something else to do.  I'll find someone else.	0	0	0	Yapacak başka bir işin var gibi görünüyor. Başka birini bulacağım.	Parece que tienes otra cosa que hacer. Buscaré a alguien más.	يبدو أن لديك شيئاً آخر لتقوم به. سأبحث عن شخص آخر.	Du scheinst etwas anderes vorzuhaben. Ich werde jemand anderes finden.
1	1741	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_04	아직도 가브리엘에게 붉은 역십자가를 전해주지 않았소?
성직자 가브리엘은 대성당에 가면 찾을 수 있소.	0	0	0	0	0	Didn't you deliever the Red Reversed Cross to Gabriel yet?
Clergy Gabriel can be found at the Cathedral.	0	0	0	Hala Red Reversed Cross'u Gabriel'e götürmedin mi? Rahip Gabriel'i Cathedral'de bulabilirsin.	¿Aun no has entregado la Red Reversed Cross a Gabriel? El clérigo Gabriel debe estar en la Catedral.	ألم تقم بتوصيل الصليب الأحمر المعكوس إلى Gabriel بعد؟
ستجد القس Gabriel في الكاتدرائية.	Hast du Gabriel das Red Reversed Cross noch nicht gegeben?
Den Geistlichen Gabriel kannst du bei der Kathedrale finden.
1	1742	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_05	장군 라첼이 붉은 역십자가를 저에게 보여주라고 했다고 했습니까?
흠… 자세히 봐야겠군요.	0	0	0	0	0	Did General Ratchel say to show me the Red Reversed Cross?
Hmm…  I need to look at carefully.	0	0	0	General Ratchel Red Reversed Cross'u bana göstermeni mi söyledi? Hmm… Dikkatlice bir bakmam gerek.	¿La General Ratchel te dijo que me mostraras la Red Reversed Cross? Jmm... Necesito echar un vistazo cuidadosamente.	هل قال لك الجنرال أن تريني الصليب الأحمر المعكوس؟
همممم .... أرغب في النظر له بعناية.	Hat General Ratchel dich gebeten, mir das Red Reversed Cross zu zeigen?
Hmm… Ich muss es mir genau ansehen.
1	1743	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_06	붉은 역십자가를 받았습니다. 성직자 가브리엘에게 가져다 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've got the Red Reversed Cross.  Deliver it to Clergy Gabriel.	0	0	0	Red Reversed Cross'u aldın. Onu Rahip Gabriel'e götür.	Has obtenido la Red Reversed Cross. Por favor, entrégala al Clérigo Gabriel.	لقد حصلت على الصليب الأحمر المعكوس. قم بتوصيله إلى القص Gabriel.	Du hast das Red Reversed Cross. Bring es zum Geistlichen Gabriel.
1	1744	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_GENERAL_3_07	소지품 창이 가득 차서 붉은 역십자가를 줄 수 없소. 빈 공간을 만들고 다시 내게 찾아오시오.	0	0	0	0	0	I can't give you the Red Reversed Cross because your inventory is currently full.  Please come back when you have empty space in your inventory.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu olduğu için sana Red Reversed Cross'u veremiyorum. Lütfen envanterinde boş yer olduğunda geri gel.	No tienes espacio en tu inventario para la Red Reversed Cross. Por favor, regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario	لا يمكنني إعطائك الصليب الأحمر المعكوس لأن خزينتك ممتلئة. عد إلي بعد إفراغ موضع في خزينتك.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir das Red Reversed Cross nicht geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	1745	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_PRIEST_1_01	장군 라첼이 저에게 보내준 붉은 역십자가의 정체는 타락천사 세니엘을 상징하는 물건입니다.
저 역시 붉은 역십자가에서 흘러나오는 이름을 들었고 그제서야 세니엘의 물건임을 알게 되었지요.
타락천사 세니엘은 천계에서 있었던 대천사 루시퍼의 반란에 참여한 천사 중 하나였습니다. 변신과 현혹의 능력을 가지고 있어서 많은 천사들을 타락시키고 자신들의 동료로 만들었지요.
하지만 루시퍼가 전쟁에서 패하고 천계에서 추방당할 때 세니엘은 지은 죄의 대가로 몸은 지옥에 봉인되고 영혼은 지상에 있는 오래된 목걸이에 봉인되는 벌을 받게 되었습니다.
바다 건너편에 있는 해적에게서 이 목걸이를 얻었다면 누군가가 세니엘이 봉인되어 있는 목걸이를 가지고 있고 그가 세니엘의 조종을 받아 해적들에게 영향력을 행사하는 것이라고 보여지는군요.
해적들의 횡포와 세니엘이 연관된 것 같으니 이 사실을 장군 라첼에게 전해주시겠습니까?	0	0	0	0	0	The Red Reversed Cross that Ratchel sent in is an item that symbolizes the fallen angel Seniel.
I have also heard the name that has been called out from the Red Reversed Cross, and managed to figure out that the item belongs to Seniel.
Fallen angel Seniel was one of the angels that had participated in the rebellion of archangel Lucifer. Skilled in dazzlement and metamorphosis, Seniel has corrupted many angels and made them his allies.
But when Lucifer was defeated in battle, when Seniel was banished from the heaven, he was punished for the sins he had committed. His body was sealed in hell, and his spirit in a necklace belonging to this world.
If you obtained this necklace from a pirate overseas, it seems like someone has the necklace with Seniel sealed in. The owner of the necklace is most likely to be possessed by Seniel, and is trying to dominate the pirates.
It is very likely that the pirates' oppression has connections to Seniel, so give this news to General Ratchel.	0	0	0	Ratchel'ın gönderdiği Red Reversed Cross sürgün melek Seniel'i sembolize eden bir item. Red Reversed Cross'un seslendiği ismi ben de duydum ve itemin sürgün melek Seniel'e ait olduğunu çözmeyi başardım. Sürgün melek Seniel, başmelek Lucifer'in isyanına katılmış meleklerden biri. Kamaştırma ve başkalaşımda usta olan Seniel birçok meleği baştan çıkarıp onları müttefiği haline getirmiş.   Fakat Lucifer savaşta yenilip Seniel cennetten kovulunca işlediği günahlar için cezalandırılmış. Bedeni cehenneme, ruhu da bu dünyaya ait bir kolyeye hapsedilmiş. Eğer denizaşırı bir korsandan bu kolyeyi ele geçirirsen Seniel'in hapsolduğu kolyenin içinde biri varmış gibi gözüktüğünü göreceksin. Kolyenin sahibi büyük ihtimalle Seniel tarafından ele geçirilmiş biri ve korsanlara hükmetmeye çalışıyor. Korsanların zalimliği muhtemelen Seniel ile bağlantılı. Bu haberleri gidip General Ratchel'a ilet.	La Red Reversed Cross que Ratchel envió es un ítem que simboliza la caída del ángel Seniel. También he escuchado el nombre que emite la Red Reversed Cross y supongo que el ítem pertenece a Seniel. Seniel fue uno de los ángeles que participó en la rebelión del arcángel Lucifer. Es habilidoso en la hechicería y la metamorfosis. Seniel ha capturado a muchos ángeles y los ha convertido en sus aliados. Pero cuando Lucifer fue derrotado en la batalla y fue expulsado del cielo, Seniel fue castigado por todos los pecados que cometió. Su cuerpo fue encerrado en el infierno y su espíritu en un Necklace perteneciente a este mundo. Si obtuviste ese collar de un Pirate de altamar, parece como si alguien tuviese el collar con Seniel encerrado allí. Lo más probable es que el dueño del collar esté poseído por Seniel y trate de dominar a los demás Pirates. Es muy posible que la opresión de los Pirates tenga una conexión con Seniel. Dale esta noticia a la General Ratchel.	الصليب الأحمر المعكوس الذي أرسله لي Ratchel هو أداة ترمز إلى الملاك Seniel.
لقد سمعت أيضاً الاسم الذي كان يطلق عليه الصليب الأحمر المعكوس واكتشفت أن أن هذه الأداة تعود إلى Seniel.
الملاك Seniel كان واحد من الملائكة الذين شاركوا في ثورة رئيس الملائكة لوشيفير. وSeniel لديه مهارة في إلإغواء والتحويل لقد أغوى Seniel العديد من الملائكة وجعلهم حلفاء له.
ولكن عندما تمت هزيمية لوسيفير في المعركة تم نفي Seniel من السماء وتمت معاقبة بسبب الآثام التي اقترفها. لقد ذهب هذا الجسد إلى الجحيم وذهبت روحه إلى عقد يعود إلى هذا العالم. 
إذا حصلت على هذا العقد من القراصنة عبر البحار فبما يبدو أن أحد ما لديه هذا العقد. مالك العقد على الأغلب أنه ممسوس من الملاك Seniel وهو يحاول السيطرة على القراصنة.
إنه من الواضح أن هذا القرصان الظالم لديه اتصال مع الملاك Seniel لذا أعط هذه الأخبار إلى الجنرال Ratchel.	Das Red Reversed Cross, das Ratchel schickt, symbolisiert den gefallenen Engel Seniel.
Ich habe auch den Namen gehört, den das Red Reversed Cross gerufen hat. Ich habe herausgefunden, dass es Seniel gehört hat.
Der gefallene Engel Seniel war einer der Engel, der bei der Rebellion des Erzengels Lucifer mitgemacht hat. Seniel kann gut täuschen und sich für andere ausgeben, damit hat er viele Engel verdorben und zu seinen Verbündeten gemacht.
Aber als Lucifer im Kampf besiegt wurde, wurde Seniel für seine Sünden bestraft und aus dem Himmel verbannt. Sein Körper wurde in der Hölle eingeschlossen, sein Geist in einer Halskette dieser Welt.
Anscheinend gibt es jemanden, der die Halskette hat, in der Seniel eingeschlossen ist. Der Besitzer dieser Halskette ist höchstwahrscheinlich von Seniel besessen und wird versuchen, die Piraten zu beherrschen.
Es ist sehr wahrscheinlich, dass die Unterdrückung der Piraten mit Seniel zu tun hat. Bring General Ratchel diese Nachricht.
1	1746	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_PRIEST_1_02	고맙습니다.
신의 가호가 당신과 함께하길 기원합니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Thank you.
May God bless you.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. Tanrı seni korusun.	Gracias. Que Dios te bendiga.	شكراً لك.
ليباركك الرب.	Danke.
Gott segne dich.
1	1747	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_PRIEST_1_03	다른 바쁜 일이 있으신가 보군요.	0	0	0	0	0	Looks like you have something else to do.	0	0	0	Yapacak başka bir işin var gibi görünüyor.	Parece que tienes algo más que hacer.	يبدو أن لديك شيئاً آخر لتقوم به. سأبحث عن شخص آخر.	Du scheinst etwas anderes vorzuhaben.
1	1748	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_PRIEST_1_04	장군 라첼에게 타락천사 세니엘의 정체와 붉은 역십자가의 정체를 알려주십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	Go tell Ratchel about what symbolizes The Red Reversed Cross and  fallen angel Seniel.	0	0	0	Gidip Ratchel'a Red Reversed Cross'un neyi sembolize ettiğini ve sürgün melek Seniel'i anlat.	Ve a contarle a Ratchel lo que simboliza la Red Reversed Cross y el ángel caído Seniel.	اذهب وأخبر Ratchel عما يرمز إليه الصليب الأحمر المعكوس والملاك Seniel.	Erzähl Ratchel, was das Red Reversed Cross symbolisiert und vom gefallenen Engel Seniel.
1	1749	SN_TALK_QNO_EU_PRIEST_1_05	흠… 가브리엘의 말이 사실이라면 세니엘이 봉인된 목걸이를 가졌다고 의심할 만한 사람이 한 명 있소.
몇 년전 우리 군대에는 용맹한 여자 용병이 한 명 있었소. 그 여자는 반란군을 제압하기 위해 소아시아로 출병하였고 무사히 임무를 마치고 돌아오던 중 갑자기 변심하여 용병 동료를 비롯한 모든 병사들 죽이고 자취를 감추었소. 직접 그녀를 고용했고 딸처럼 여기고 있었던 나는 그녀가 그런 잔인한 행동을 했다고는 믿을 수 없었으나 그녀의 흔적이 남은 사상자들을 보고 그녀의 변심에 가슴 아파할 수 밖에 없었소.
그 뒤 새로운 해적 두목이 등장했다고 하는데 그것은 바로 자취를 감추었던 용맹한 여자 용병이었소.
캡틴 아이비... 이제는 그렇게 불리고 있는 여자 용병이 변심한 이유가 바로 세니엘 때문이었으니 그녀를 잘 설득하면 다시 본래의 모습을 되찾을 수 있을 것이오. 또한 해적들과의 전쟁도 끝낼 수 있을 것이고 말이오.
이제 새로운 작전을 세워야겠소. 첩자를 해적소굴에 파견해 아이비를 만날 수 있는 방법을 알아내야겠소.
당신이 전해준 정보가 큰 도움이 되었소. 고맙소.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm..  If Gabriel is true, then there is one person for Seniel to suspect to have the sealed necklace.
There was a brave female tactic few years ago. She left to Asia Minor to beat the rebellions but she killed all her comrades and disappeared on way of coming back.  I couldn't believe her cruel act becasue she was like a daughter to me and I hired her.  But I was t broken hearted as I looked the wounded and dead people by her.
There was a new pirate leader appeared after the happen and she was the missing brave tactic.  Captain Ivy... The chaged mind female tactic is now called by this name and Seniel was the reason for changing of her mind.  If we convince her then she might turn back to how she looked like.  And we might be able to end the fight against with pirates.
Now we need to make a new plan.  Dispatch spy into pirates den to find out the method to meed Ivy.
Your information had been really helpful.  Thank you.	0	0	0	Hmm.. Eğer Gabriel haklıysa Seniel'in sealed necklace'sine sahip olduğundan şüphelenilecek bir kişi var. Birkaç yıl önce cesur bir tebiye vardı. Küçük Asya'dan isyanları bastırmak için ayrıldı ama tüm yoldaşlarını öldürüp geri dönüş yolunda ortadan kayboldu. Onun bu gaddarca davranışına inanamıyorum çünkü o benim kızım gibiydi ve onu işe ben almıştım. Fakat onun tarafından doğranmış ve öldürülmüş insanlara bakınca kalbim buz kesildi. Olaydan sonra yeni bir korsan lideri ortaya çıktı ve o da kayıp cesur bir tebiyeydi. Captain Ivy... Zihni yıkanmış tebiye artık bu adla çağırılıyor ve onun zihnini yıkadğı için bunun sorumlusu Seniel. Eğer onu ikna edebilirsek göründüğü haline geri dönebilir. Ve biz de korsanlara karşı olan savaşı sona erdirebiliriz. Şimdi yeni bir plan yapmamız gerek. Ivy ile karşılaşma yolunu öğrenmek için korsanların mağarasına casus gönder. Verdiğin bilgiler çok faydalı oldu. Teşekkürler.	Jmm... Si lo que dice Gabriel es cierto, entonces hay una persona sospechosa de tener el collar sellado de Seniel. Hubo una valiente estratega femenina hace algunos años. Se fue a Asia Minor a combatir las rebeliones, pero mató a todos sus compañeros y desapareció en el camino de regreso. Yo no podía creer su cruel acto porque era como una hija para mí puesto que yo la crié, pero se me destrozó el corazón cuando vi a las personas asesinadas y heridas por ella.Apareció una nueva líder para los Pirates después de lo ocurrido. Capitan Ivy... ahora la llaman por este nombre. Seniel fue la razón del cambio de su mentalidad. Si la convencemos, ella volvería a ser lo que era y podremos terminar la batalla con los Pirates. Ahora necesitamos hacer un nuevo plan. Debo enviar espías entre los Pirates para averiguar cómo ver a Ivy. Tu información ha sido muy útil. Gracias.	همممم... إذا كان جبريل محقاً فهناك سبب للشك في Seniel أنه سرق العقد.
لقد كانت هناك خطة أنثوية شجاعة منذ عدة سنوات. لقد تركت آسيا الصغرى لهزيمة الثورات ولكنها قتلت جميع زملائها واختفت بطريقة تأتي بها بعد ذلك. لم أصدق تصرفها القاسي هذا لأنها كانت مثل ابنة لي وقد عينتها. ولكن لم ينفطر قلبي عندما نظرت للجرحى والموتى الذين تسببت في جرحهم وقتلهم.
لقد كان هناك قائد جديد للقراصنة ظهر بعد حدوث هذا وقد كانت الوسيلة الشجاعة المفقودة. كابت lvy ... الأنثى التي خططت لذلك والتي تغير عقلها تسمى الآن Seniel فقد كانت هي سبب تغيير عقلها. إذا أقنعناها ربما تعود كما كانت. وربما نكون قادرين على أنهاء القتال ضد القراصنة.
الآن سنحتاج لوضع خطة جديدة. نرسل جاسوس إلى وكر القراصنة لنجد طريقة لمقابلة lvy.
لقد كانت معلوماتك مفيدة حقاً. شكراً لك.	Hmm. Wenn Gabriel Recht hat, dann könnte es eine Person geben, die die Halskette hat.
Vor ein paar Jahren war hier eine mutige Taktikerin. Sie ging nach Asia Minor, um dort die Rebellion niederzuschlagen, aber auf ihrem Rückweg brachte sie alle ihre Kameraden um und verschwand. Ich konnte ihre grausame Tat nicht glauben. Sie war für mich wie eine Tochter, ich hatte sie angeheuert. Es brach mir das Herz, als ich die Verwundeten und Toten um sie herum sah.
Danach erschien ein neuer Piratenführer, es war die vermisste mutige Taktikerin. Kapitänin Ivy... So wird die Taktikerin jetzt genannt, und Seniel war der Grund für diese Veränderung in ihrem Wesen. Wenn wir sie überzeugen können, könnte sie vielleicht wieder so wie früher werden. Dann könnten wir vielleicht den Kampf gegen die Piraten beenden.
Wir brauchen einen neuen Plan. Schick einen Spion ins Piratenlager, um herauszufinden, wie wir Ivy finden können.
Deine Informationen haben wirklich geholfen. Danke.
