1	2000	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_02	기본 행동법	0	0	0	0	0	Basic Movement.	0	0	0	Temel İşlemler	Acciones Básicas.	الحركات الأساسية	Grundlegende Bewegungen.
1	2001	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_03	그럼 어떻게 행동을 할 수 있는지 기본 행동법을 알려드릴께요.
오른쪽 하단의 메뉴버튼을 누르면 등장하는 창에서 왼쪽에 있는 네 번째 버튼을 누르면 행동에 관련된 창이 떠요.
그곳에 있는 아이콘에 화살표를 가져가면 그 아이콘의 설명이 뜨는데 그 아이콘을 오른쪽 클릭하면 아이콘의 설명에 해당하는 행동을 하게 된답니다.
앉기/서기, 자동줍기, 노점등의 아이콘들은 자주 쓰이게 되니까 잘 기억해 놓으면 많은 도움이 될 거에요.	0	0	0	0	0	Alright then.  I will tell you about the basic movement.
When you press menu button on your right bottom corner, window will appear.  Then press the fourth button to the left of a window.  Then Action related window will appear. 
Move the arrow to the icon there, then there will be decription pops up.  At this point, if you click mouse right button, character will move as it is described on the description. 
Sit / Stand, Auto Grab, Stall, etc. are oftenly used icons so it will be very helpful if you keep in mind.	0	0	0	Tamam o halde. Sana temel oyun işlemlerini anlatacağım.
Sağ alt köşedeki menü butonuna bas, yeni bir pencere açılacak.
Pencerenin soldan dördüncü butonuna bas.
Eylem simgelerinin olduğu yeni bir pencere açılacak.
Farenin imlecini simgelerin üzerine götürdüğünde açıklama belirecek.
Simgeye sağ tıklarsan eylem başlar.
Otur/Kalk, otomatik kapma, tezgah ve bunun gibi simgeleri sıkça kullanacaksın. Sıkça kullanılan simgeleri aklında tutman senin yararına olur.	Te enseñaré las acciones básicas del juego. Haz clic en el botón del menú ubicado en el lado inferior derecho, luego, una nueva ventana aparecerá. Haz clic en el 4º botón  del lado izquierdo de la ventana aparecerá una ventana con íconos de Acción. Coloca el cursor sobre el ícono para obtener la explicación. Si haces clic con el botón derecho, la acción se iniciará. Frecuentemente usarás íconos como Levantarse/Sentarse, Tomar automáticamente, etc. Será útil recordar los íconos usados frecuentemente.	سأوضح لك العمليات الأساسية في اللعبة.
أنقر على مفتاح القائمة الموجود في الركن الأيمن السفلي ستظهر لك نافذة جديدة. أنقر على المفتاح الرابع في الركن الأيسر من الشاشة. ستظهر لك نافذة جديدة بأيقونات العمليات.
قم بتحريك مؤشر الفأرة عل الأيقونة سيظهر لك الوصف. إذا قمت بالنقر بالمفتاح الأيمن للفأرة على الأيقونه ستبدأ هذه العملية.
ستستخدم دائماً أيقونات مثل وقوف/جلوس التقاط تلقائي ركن البيع وهكذا.
سيكون من الأفضل لك أن تأخذ في اعتبارك الأيقونات التي تستخدمها دائماً.	Gut. Ich werde dir die grundlegenden Bewegungen erklären.
Wenn du die Menütaste in der Ecke unten rechts drückst, öffnet sich ein Fenster. Klicke dann auf die vierte Taste von links in diesem Fenster. Das Handlungen-Fenster wird sich öffnen. 
Wenn du den Pfeil über ein Symbol führst, erscheint eine Beschreibung. Wenn du jetzt mit der rechten Maustaste darauf klickst, wird der Charakter sich entsprechend bewegen. 
Sitzen / Stehen, Auto-Nehmen, Stand usw. werden oft benutzt, also solltest du sie dir merken.
1	2002	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_04	기본 행동법은 알려드렸으니 콘스탄티노플 성 안의 여러 곳을 돌아다니면서 NPC들과 대화를 하시면서 많은 정보를 얻을 수 있을 거에요. 방어구점 점원 자토모에게 가면 도움이 되는 정보를 얻을 수 있을 것이니 자토모에게 가보세요.
그리고 튜토리얼 퀘스트에 대한 정보를 확인하고 싶다면 단축키 'Q'키를 눌러주세요. 현재 진행하고 있는 퀘스트의 이름과 무엇을 수행해야 하는지 확인할 수 있어요.	0	0	0	0	0	I've taught you the basic action method.  Try talking to the NPCs located around Constantinople castle, you will be able to receive various information. Go to armor trader Jatomo, you'll be able to hear some helpful information.  And if you want to check information on tutorial quest, press the short-cut key 'Q'.   You will be able to see the title of the quest, and what you need to do.	0	0	0	Sana temel işlem yöntemlerini öğrettim. Biraz da Constantinople kalesi etrafındaki NPC'ler hakkında konuşalım, buradan çeşitli bilgiler alabileceksin. Zırh tüccarı Jatomo'ya git, bazı yardımcı bilgiler alacaksın.
Ve aldığın bilgileri eğitim görevinde denemek istediğinde kısa yol tuşundan 'Q' ya bas. Görevin başlığını ve ne yapman gerektiğini göreceksin.	Te he enseñado el método de acciones básicas. Intenta hablar con los NPCs localizados alrededor del castillo de Constantinople para informarte. Dirígete a Jatomo, el comerciante de Armors y podrás recibir algo de información útil. Si quieres revisar información sobre la misión de Tutorial, presiona la tecla 'Q'. Podrás ver el título de la misión y lo que necesitas hacer.	سأعلمك طريقة الحركات الأساسية حاول التحدث إلى NPC الموجودون حول قلعة Constantinople وستحصل منهم على العديد من المعلومات. اذهب إلى تاجر armor Jatomo وستسمع منه بعض المعلومات المفيدة وإذا أردت تفقد المعلومات في مهمة تعليمية انقر على مفتاح الاختصار "q". وستكون قادراً على رؤية عنوان المهمة وما يجب عليك فعله.	Ich habe dir die grundlegenden Aktionen des Spiels erklärt. Rede mit den verschiedenen NPCs im Schloss von Constantinople, von ihnen wirst du Informationen bekommen. Geh zum Rüstungshändler Jatomo, er wird dir hilfreiche Informationen geben. Wenn du Informationen über die Tutorialquest brauchst, drück die Schnelltaste 'Q'. Du siehst den Titel der Quest und deine Aufgaben.
1	2003	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_05	방어구점 자토모에게 가서 새로운 정보를 얻으세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Protector Trader Jatomo and get new information.	0	0	0	Zırh Tüccarı Jatomo'ya git ve yeni bilgiler al.	Ve con Jatomo , el comerciante de Protectors para obtener nueva información.	اذهب إلى تاجر الملابس الدفاعية Jatomo واحصل على معلومات جديدة.	Geh zu Rüstungshändler Jatomo und erhalte neue Informationen.
1	2004	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_06	방어구점 자토모에게 가면 새로운 정보를 얻을 수 있을 것이니 그에게 찾아가세요.
만약 게임에 도움이 되는 정보를 확인하고 싶으시면 원하는 목록을 클릭해 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Protector Trader Jatomo after checking the information then you will be able to get new information.  
If you want helpful information to check the select the wanted list.	0	0	0	Bilgileri kontrol ettikten sonra Zırh Tüccarı Jatomo'ya git, ardından yeni bilgiler alabileceksin. Faydalı olacak bilgileri kontrol etmek istersen talep listesini seç.	Ve a ver a Jatomo. Después de recibir la información que él te dará, podrás obtener más información. Si quieres información útil, selecciona en la lista.	إذهب إلى تاجر الأدوات الدفاعية Jatomo بعد تفقد المعلومات وستكون قادراً على أن تحصل على معلومات جديدة.
إذا رغبت في معلومات مفيدة حددها في القائمة المرغوبة.	Geh zu Rüstungshändler Jatomo, nachdem du die Information gelesen hast, dann wirst du neue Informationen erhalten. 
Schaue auf die Liste für hilfreiche Informationen und wähle ein Thema.
1	2005	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_07	어서오게. 콘스탄티노플에 새로 입성한 사람이로구먼. 자네도 라피가 나에게 가보라고 해서 온 것일테지? 
역시 내가 콘스탄티노플에서 가장 믿음직스럽고 능력있는 사람이기 때문에 나에게 도움을 청하라고 했을꺼야. 크크크크…
자네도 나에게 잘 보여야 할꺼야. 크크크크… 내가 이래뵈도 콘스탄티노플에서 숨은 실력자거든… 이것은 비밀이니 다른 사람에게 말하면 안된다네.
그건 그렇고 자네에게 도움이 되는 말을 해 주겠네.
보다시피 이 곳에 있는 방어구들은 자네가 새로운 세계에서 몸을 보호하기 위해 필요한 아이템 이라네. 그것을 사용하는 방법을 알려주겠네.	0	0	0	0	0	Welcome.  You are new here.  Did Lipria send you here?
I knew I'm the most truthful and have the most abilities and therefore, Lipria told to ask me for a help.   Hahaha…
You better be nice to me.  Hahaha…  I'm the hidden man of influence even I look like this...  This is scret so don't tell anyone.  
Alright then.  I'l tell you something helpful.  
As you can see, Armors here are items you need toprotect yourself  as you travel the around the world
Now, I'll teach you how to use.	0	0	0	Hoş geldin. Burada yenisin. Seni Lipria mı gönderdi?
En güvenilir ve en yeteneklinin ben olduğumu biliyorum ve dolayısıyla, Lipria sana benden yardım istemeni söyledi. Hahaha…
Bana karşı nazik olsan iyi edersin. Hahaha... Böyle gözüksem bile gizli bir nüfuzlu adamım ben... Bu bir sır, sakın kimseye söyleme.
Gördüğün gibi, buradaki zırhlar dünyada yolculuk ederken kendini korumak için gerekli olan itemler.
Şimdi onları nasıl kullanacağını öğreteceğim.	Bienvenido. Tú eres nuevo aquí. ¿Lipria te envió? Supe que soy el más confiable y tengo las mejores habilidades; por eso, Lipria te dijo que me pidieras ayuda. Jajaja... Te conviene ser bueno conmigo. Ja ja ja... Aunque luzca así, soy un hombre influyente de incógnito... Es un secreto, así que no le digas a nadie.De acuerdo, te diré algo útil.Como verás las Armors son necesarias para protegerte durante el viaje que harás en este mundo.Te enseñaré cómo usarlas.	مرحباً. أنت جديد هنا. هل أرسلتك Lipria هنا؟
أعلم أنني أكثرهم صدقاً ولدي العديد من المهارات. أخبرتني Lipria أنك تحتاج إلى المساعدة.
هاها هاها ها 
من الأفضل أن تكون لطيفاً معي . ها ها ها ها أنا رجل التأثير الخفي حتى ولو كنت أبدو هكذا ...... هذا سر فلا تخبر أحد.
حسناً. سأخبرك شيئاً يساعدك.
كما ترى الأدوات الدفاعية هنا هي أدوات تحتاج لحماية نفسك بها عند سفرك حول العالم.
الآن سأعلمك كيفية استخدامها.	Willkommen. Du bist neu hier. Hat Lipria dich geschickt?
Ich weiß, ich bin am ehrlichsten und fähigsten, deshalb hat Lipria dir gesagt, du kannst mich um Hilfe bitten. Hahaha…
Du solltest lieber nett zu mir sein. Hahaha… Ich bin ein Mann mit viel Einfluss, auch wenn ich so aussehe... Das ist ein Geheimnis, also verrat es niemandem. 
Gut. Ich werde dir etwas Hilfreiches sagen. 
Wie du siehst, sind Rüstungen Gegenstände, die dich auf deinen Reisen durch die Welt beschützen.
Ich werde dir beibringen, wie man sie benutzt.
1	2006	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_08	네. 다른 사람에게 말하지 않을테니 도움이 되는 이야기를 해주십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	Yes.  I won't tell anyone so please tell me something helpful.	0	0	0	Evet. Kimseye söylemeyeceğim, lütfen bana faydalı bir şey anlat.	Tranquilo, no le contaré a nadie. Por favor, dime algo útil.	نعم لن أخبر أحد لذا أخبرني شيئاً جيداً.	Ja. Ich sage es niemandem, also sag mir bitte etwas Hilfreiches.
1	2007	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_09	너무 재촉하지 말게. 지금부터 알려줄 거니까 잘 들으라고.
먼저 자네가 콘스탄티노플에 처음 온 기념으로 내가 선물 하나를 줄 것인데 먼저 그것을 사용하는 법을 알려주겠네.	0	0	0	0	0	Don't you push me on it.  I'll tell you from now so listen very carefully.
First, I'll give you a gift for coming to Constantinople for the first time and I'll tell you how to use it first.	0	0	0	Beni sıkıştırma. Şimdi sana anlatacaklarımı dikkatlice dinle.
İlk olarak Constantinople'a ilk kez gelişin için sana bir hediye verceğim ve onu nasıl kullanacağını anlatacağım.	No me presiones. Te contaré desde ya, así que escucha con mucho cuidado. Primero, te daré un obsequio por venir a Constantinople por primera vez y te diré cómo usarlo.	لا تدفعني عليها. سأخبرك من الآن لذا فاستمع لي بحرص.
أولاً سأعطيك هدية لأنك أتيت إلى Constantinople للمرة الأولى وسأخبرك كيف تستخدمها في البداية.	Dräng mich nicht. Ich werde es dir jetzt sagen, also höre genau zu.
Erst gebe ich dir ein Geschenk dafür, zum ersten Mal in Constantinople zu sein, und ich sage dir, wie du es benutzt.
1	2008	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_10	아이템 착용법	0	0	0	0	0	Item Usage	0	0	0	İtem Kullanımı	Uso del ítem.	استخدام الأدوات.	Benutzen von Gegenständen
1	2009	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_11	메뉴 버튼을 눌러 왼쪽 두 번째 버튼을 누르거나 단축키 'I'를 누르면 인벤토리 창이 나오는데 현재 자신이 소유하고 있는 물건들이 거기에 나와있지. 그 물건들을 왼쪽 클릭하면 아이템을 옮길 수 있게 되고 소모성 아이템들 즉 물약이나 치료약 같은 물건들은 오른쪽 클릭을 하면 그 물건을 사용하게 되네. 인벤토리 창의 오른쪽은 장비 창인데 현재 자신이 착용하고 있는 장비를 보여준다네. 장비를 착용하려면 자신이 착용할 수 있는 장비를 인벤토리 창에서 왼쪽 클릭하여 장비창에 가져가 다시 왼쪽 클릭을 하면 장비를 착용할 수 있다네.	0	0	0	0	0	Inventory window will appear when you press 'I' key on the second left button after pressing the menu button.  There are the stuff you have so far.  If you left click, then you will be able to move it.  And you can use  the usable items like potion of cure pills by right click of the mouse.  Right hand side of inventory window shows your equipments that you have on.  To wear the equipments, click left button on the equipment you want to wear from the inventory window then click left button again on the equipment window.	0	0	0	Menü butonuna bastıktan sonra soldan ikinci 'I' tuşuna basınca envanter penceresi açılacak. Burada sahip olduğun itemler bulunuyor. Sol tıklarsan onları hareket ettirebilirsin. İyieştirme ilacı iksiri gibi tüketilebilir itemleri farenin sağ tuşunu tıklayarak kullanabilirsin. Envanter penceresinin sağ tarafında üzerinde bulunan ekipmanlar gösterilir. Ekipmanı giymek için, envanter penceresinden giymek istediğin ekipmana sol tıkla ardından ekipman penceresine tekrar sol tıkla.	La ventana de inventario aparecerá cuando presiones la tecla "I"; también, en el segundo botón izquierdo después de presionar el botón de menú. Ahí encontrarás las cosas que ya tienes. Si haces clic izquierdo, podrás moverlo. Puedes usar los ítems consumibles como Potions o Pills de cura haciendo clic derecho en el mouse. A la derecha del inventario, se muestran los equipamientos de los que dispones. Para vestir los equipamientos, haz clic izquierdo en el que quieras vestir desde la ventana de inventario. Luego, haz clic izquierdo de nuevo en la ventana de equipamiento.	أنقر على مفتاح القائمة ثم أنقر على المفتاح الثاني أو مفتاح [I] ستفتح لك نافذة الخزينة ستجد الأدوات التي تملكها هناك.
يمكنك تحريك الأدوات بالنقر بالمفتاح الأيسر أو استخدام الأدوات المستهلكة مثل الجرعات بالنقر بالمفتاح الأيمن. التحديد على الجانب الأيمن من الخزينة للتجهيزات. إنه يظهر لك الأدوات والتجهيزات التي ترتديها حالياً. لوضع أي تجهيزات أنقر بالمفتاح الأيسر على التجهيزات المتاحة ثم بالمفتاح الأيسر على جزء التجهيزات التي ترتديها حالياً. عندها سترتدي هذه التجهيزات.	Das Inventarfenster öffnet sich, wenn du nach dem Drücken der Menütaste die Taste 'I' auf der zweiten Taste von links drückst. Das sind alle Sachen, die du schon hast. Mit einem Linksklick kannst du sie verschieben. Du kannst auch konsumierbare Gegenstände wie Tränke oder Cure Pills mit einem Klick der rechten Maustaste benutzen. Auf der rechten Seite des Inventarfensters siehst du die Ausrüstung, die du gerade trägst. Um Ausrüstung anzulegen, klicke mit der linken Maustaste auf die gewünschte Ausrüstung aus dem Inventarfenster, dann klicke nochmals mit der linken Taste im Ausrüstungsfenster.
1	2010	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_12	아이템을 빠르게 사용하기 위해서는 화면 하단 중앙에 있는 퀵슬롯창을 이용하면 되는데 인벤토리 창에 있는 아이템을 퀵슬롯창에 가져다 번호에 등록을 하면 다음부터는 키보드의 번호만 누르면 그 아이템을 사용할 수 있다네. 퀵슬롯창을 이용하면 장비나 스킬, 행동도 빠르게 사용할 수 있지.
자 그럼 이것을 받게. 자네가 콘스탄티노플에 처음 온 기념으로 주는 선물일세.
아, 그리고 장비를 착용시 마스터리 조건을 만족하지 못하면 착용할 수 없으니 그 점 유의하게나.	0	0	0	0	0	You can use items quickly with the quick slot interface in the center bottom of the screen. You can use it by pressing the corresponding number on the keyboard after registering an item on the quick slot window. By using the quick slot window, you can also use skills, actions, and equipments easily..
Then, you may take this.  This is the gift to you for the first time of Constantinople.  
Oh, you won't be able to wear the equipments if it doesn't satisfy its mastery condition.	0	0	0	Ekranın ortasındaki hızlı arabirim sayesinde itemlerini hızlı bir şekilde kullanabilirsin. Hızlı arabirim penceresinde itemlere numara atadıktan sonra, klavyende ilişkilendirdiğin numaraya basarak o itemi kullanabilirsin. Hızlı arabirim penceresinde ayrıca becerilerini, işlemleri ve ekipmanları kolayca yönetebilirsin..
O halde bunu alabilirsin. Bu hediye Constantinople'a ilk kez geldiğin için.
Unutma ki itemler eğer maharet durumunu karşılamazsa ekipmanı giyemezsin.	Puedes usar los ítems rápidamente con la interfaz de espacios rápidos que aparece en el centro inferior de la pantalla. Los ítems en estos espacios se usan presionando el número correspondiente al espacio rápido en el teclado. Esta ventana también te permite usar habilidades, acciones, y equipamiento fácilmente. Entonces, puedes tomar esto. Es un regalo por tu primera vez en Constantinopla. Oh, no podrás usar los equipamientos si no cumplen con los requisitos de la maestría.	يمكنك استخدام الأدوات بسرعة عن طريق شريط المواضع السريعة في منتصف أسفل الشاشة. يمكنك استخدامها بالنقر على الرقم المخصص في لوحة المفاتيح بعد وضع الأدوات في شريط المواضع السريعة. وباستخدام شريط المواضع السريعة ستستطيع أيضاً استخدام المهارات العمليات و التجهيزات بسهولة..
ثم سيمكنك أخذ هذا. هذه الهدية لأنك تأتي إلى Constantinople للمرة الأولى.
أوه لن تكون قادراً على ارتداء التجهيزات إذا لم تفي بشروط مهارتها.	Mit der Schnellauswahl unten in der Mitte des Bildschirms kannst du Gegenstände schnell einsetzen. Du kannst sie dann schnell einsetzen, indem du die entsprechende Nummer auf der Tastatur drückst. Mit der Schnellauswahl kannst du auch Fähigkeiten, Aktionen und Ausrüstungen einfach einsetzen.
Dann kannst du dies nehmen. Das ist dein Geschenk für deinen ersten Besuch in Constantinople. 
Oh, du kannst die Ausrüstung nicht tragen, wenn sie die Mastery Kondition nicht erfüllt.
1	2011	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_13	소지품창이 꽉 차서 선물을 줄 수 없네. 빈 공간을 만들고 다시 찾아오게.	0	0	0	0	0	I can not give you a gift because your inventory is currently full.  Please come back when your have an empty space in your inventory,	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu olduğu için hediyeni sana veremiyorum. Biraz yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Me gustaría darte el regalo, pero tu inventario está lleno. Por favor, regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario.	لا يمكنك تسلم الهدية لأن خزينتك ممتلئة. عد مرة أخرى بعد إفراغ موضع في خزينتك.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir kein Geschenk geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	2012	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_14	바젤에게 찾아가서 그녀의 부탁을 들어주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Grocery Trader Bajel and do her favor.	0	0	0	Gıda Tüccarı Bajel'e git ve isteğini yerine getir.	Ve con Bajel, la comerciante de alimentos y cumple su petición.	اذهب إلى تاجرة الإكسسوارات Bajel وأسد لها خدمة.	Geh zur Gemischtwarenhändlerin Bajel und tu ihr einen Gefallen.
1	2013	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_15	바젤이 부탁할 일이 있다면서 사람을 구하고 있는데 그녀에게 한 번 가보게나.	0	0	0	0	0	Bajel is looking for people to do her favor so go visit her.	0	0	0	Bajel isteğini yapması için birini arıyor, git ve onu ziyaret et.	Bajel necesita ayuda, así que ve a visitarla.	Bajel تبحث عمن يسدي لها خدمه اذهب لزيارتها.	Bajel sucht nach Leuten, die ihr einen Gefallen tun, also besuch sie.
1	2014	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_16	안녕하세요. 자토모에게서 좋은 정보를 얻고 오셨나요?
게임에 도움이 되는 정보를 확인하고 싶으시면 제가 알려드릴께요.
이런...서둘러 바젤에게 가셔야 한다구요? 바젤은 광장 남서쪽의 잡화점에서 찾을 수 있어요.	0	0	0	0	0	Oh~ hi.  Did you get any helpful information from Jatomo?
If you want to check out the helpful information about the game, I will tell you.  
Oh my…  You need to hurry to Bajel?  Bajel can be found at the Grocery, southwest of piazza.	0	0	0	Oh~ merhaba. Jatomo'dan yardımcı bilgiler alabildin mi?
Oyun hakkındaki yardımcı bilgileri kontrol etmek istersen ben sana anlatırım.
Aman allahım… Acilen Bajel'e mi gitmen gerek? Bajel'i, meydanın güneybatısındaki Gıda Pazarında bulabilirsin.	Oh. Hola. ¿Obtuviste alguna información útil de Jatomo? Si quieres revisar la información sobre el juego, yo te diré. Oh... ¿Necesitas ir rápido con Bajel? Ella debe estar en el abasto al suroeste de la Piazza.	أوه ... هل حصلت على أي معلومات مفيدة من Jatomo؟
إذا رغبت في الحصول على معلومات مفيدة عن اللعبة. سأخبرك.
أوه ... يجب أن تسرع إلى Bajel؟ ستجد Bajel في متجر الاكسسوارات جنوب غرب الميدان.	Oh, hallo. Hast du hilfreiche Informationen von Jatomo erhalten?
Wenn du hilfreiche Informationen über das Spiel brauchst, kann ich sie dir geben. 
Oje… Du musst schnell zu Bajel? Bajel findest du bei der Gemischtwarenhandlung südwestlich vom Hauptplatz.
1	2015	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_17	안녕하세요. 콘스탄티노플에 처음 입성하신 분인가 보군요.
저는 콘스탄티노플에서 잡화점을 운영하고 있는 바젤이라고 해요. 앞으로 볼 일이 많아질테니 잘 부탁드려요.
그런데 초면에 실례가 될지도 모르겠지만 부탁이 하나 있는데 들어주실 수 있나요?
어렵지 않은 부탁인데…	0	0	0	0	0	Hello.  Looks like you came to Constantinople for the first time.
My name is Bajel and I run a Grocery Shop in Constantinople.  Nice to meet you.  
I know it's not polite to ask you a favor to a stranger but can you do me a favor?  
I have one easy favor to ask you...	0	0	0	Merhaba. Constantinople'a ilk defa gelmiş gibi görünüyorsun.
Benim adım Bajel ve Constantinople'deki Gıda Dükkanını işletiyorum. Tanıştığıma memnun oldum. Biliyorum bir yabancıdan yardım istemek pek kibarca olmaz ama bana bir iyilik yapar mısın? Çok kolay bir şey isteyeceğim...	Hola... Parece que vienes a Constantinople por primera vez. Mi nombre es Bajel; dirijo un abasto en Constantinople. Gusto en conocerte. Sé que no es educado que le pida un favor a un extraño, pero ¿me puedes ayudar?  Es algo fácil de hacer.	مرحباً. يبدو انك أتيت إلى Constantinople للمرة الأولى.
اسمي Bajel وأنا أدير متجر الاكسسوارات في Constantinople.
تشرفت بمقابلتك.
أعلم أنه ليس من الأدب طلب خدمة من غريب ولكن هلا أسديت لي هذه الخدمة؟
لدي خدمة سهلة لأطلب منك القيام بها.	Hallo. Du scheinst zum ersten Mal in Constantinople zu sein.
Ich heiße Bajel und habe einen Gemischtwarenladen in Constantinople. Sehr erfreut. 
Ich weiß, es ist nicht höflich, einen Fremden um einen Gefallen zu bitten, aber könntest du mir einen tun? 
Ich möchte dich um einen einfachen Gefallen bitten...
1	2016	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_18	제가 할 수 있는 일이라면 도와드리지요.	0	0	0	0	0	I'll help you if I can handle it.	0	0	0	Üstesinden gelebilirsem sana yardım ederim.	Te ayudaré si lo puedes hacer.	سأساعدك إذا قمت بها.	Ich helfe dir, wenn ich es kann.
1	2017	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_19	아아… 감사합니다.
얼마전에 무기점 상인 발바르도가 몸이 아프다는 이야기를 들었어요.
평소 건강에 대해서 강한 자신감을 가지고 있던 분이라서 약을 챙겨서 먹었는지 걱정이 되는데… 수녀 레탈디에게 가서 약을 사갔는지 알아봐주세요.
만약 약을 사가지 않았다면 제가 돈을 드릴테니 그 돈으로 약을 사서 발바르도에게 전해주세요.
그리고 약을 전해줄 때 제가 약을 사주라고 했다는 말은 하지 말아주세요.
제가 그를 걱정하고 있다는 것은 당분간 저와 당신만의 비밀로 간직하고 싶어요. 부탁드립니다.
그럼 만약 약을 구입할 경우를 대비해서 상점을 이용하는 방법에 대해서 알려드리겠어요.	0	0	0	0	0	Ah ah.. Thank you.  I heard Weapon Trader Balbardo is sick recently.
I wonder if he had taken the medicine.  He usually has great concern on health…  Please go and ask if he had bought the medicine from Nun Retaldi.  If he didn't, then buy the medicine and give it to Balbardo with the money I give you.  And do not tell him I asked you to buy him when you deliver the medicine.
I want to keep in secret between you and me that I worry about him for now.  Please.  
Then in case of buying the medicine, I'll teach you how to use the shop.	0	0	0	Ah ah.. Teşekkür ederim.
Silah Tüccarı Balbardo'nun geçenlerde hastalandığını duydum.
İlacını aldı mı merak ediyorum. Genelde sağlığına çok düşkündür... Lütfen  gidip onun Rahibe Retaldi'den ilacı alıp almadığını sor. Eğer almamışsa, ilacı sana verdiğim parayla al ve Balbardo'ya götür. İlacı ona verirken sakın benim almanı söylediğimi söyleme.
Şu aralar onun için endişelendiğim için bunun seninle benim aramda bir sır olarak kalmasını istiyorum.
İlacı alacak olursan sana dükkanı nasıl kullanacağını öğretirim.	Ah ah. ¡Gracias! Recientemente escuché que Balbardo, el comerciante de armas ha estado enfermo.Me pregunto si se ha tomado la medicina. Por lo general, se preocupa por su salud... Por favor, ve y pregunta a la Monja Retaldi si él ha comprado la medicina. Si no lo ha hecho, entonces compra la medicina con el dinero que te di y dásela a Balbardo. No le digas que yo te pedí que la compraras cuando se la entregues. Por ahora, quiero mantener en secreto el hecho de que me preocupo por él.En caso de que tengas que comprar la medicina, te enseñaré cómo usar las tiendas.	أوه. ... شكراً لك. .... لقد  سمعت أن تاجر الأسلحة Balbardo مريض في الفترة الأخير.
أتسائل ما إذا كان قد أخذ الدواء. هو يهتم دائماً بصحته ... اهذب واسئله إذا قام بشراء الدواء من الراهبة Retaldi. وإذا لم يقم بهذا فقم بشراء الدواء وأعطه له بالنقود التي أعطيتها لك. ولا تخبره بأنني طلبت منك أن تشتري له الدواء عندما توصل له الدواء.
أرغب في أن أحتفظ بهذا سراً بيني وبينك فأنا قلة بشأنه الآن.
وفي حالة ما اشترى الدواء سأعلمك كيف تستخدم المتجر.	Ah... Danke. Ich habe gehört, dass der Waffenhändler Balbardo krank geworden ist.
Ich frage mich, ob er seine Medizin genommen hat. Er achtet sonst sehr auf seine Gesundheit… Bitte frag ihn, ob er seine Medizin von Nonne Retaldi gekauft hat. Wenn nicht, dann kauf sie mit dem Geld, das ich dir gebe, und gib sie Balbardo. Und sag ihm nicht, dass ich dich gebeten habe, sie zu kaufen.
Es soll erst mal unser Geheimnis bleiben, dass ich mir Sorgen um ihn mache. Bitte. 
Wenn du die Medizin kaufen musst, werde ich dir beibringen, wie man einen Laden benutzt.
1	2018	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_20	아이템 구입방법	0	0	0	0	0	Item Purchase Method	0	0	0	İtem Satın Alma Yöntemi	Método de Compra de Ítems	طريقة شراء الأدوات	Wie man Gegenstände kauft
1	2019	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_21	상점은 크게 무기점, 방어구점, 약방, 잡화점, 특산품점, 창고로 나누어져 있어요. 무기점은 무기를 파는 곳이고 방어구점은 방어구를 약방이나 물약상인은 회복이나 치료에 관련된 물건을 파는 곳이지요. 그리고 제가 운영하는 잡화점은 장신구나 귀환서등의 물건을 팔고 특산품점은 무역에 관련된 물건을 팔고 있어요.
상점이용은 상점NPC를 클릭하여 구입/판매 글을 클릭하면 관련 상점창이 뜨고 구입하려는 물건을 인벤토리에 넣으면 구입을 할 수 있고 인벤토리의 물건을 상점창에 가져다 놓으면 자신의 물건을 상점에 팔 수가 있지요.
그리고 이것은 콘스탄티노플에 처음 입성하신 기념으로 제가 드리는 선물이에요. 혹시 발바르도에게 약을 전해주게 되면 약을 구입할 돈이 필요할지도 모르니 돈도 함께 드릴께요.	0	0	0	0	0	The shops are classified into Weapons shops, Defensive tool shops, Pharmacies, Special product shops, and Storage.
At the weapons shop, you can buy weapons and shields. At the defensive tool shop, you can buy protection. The pharmacy sells items related to recovery and cure. At the accessory shop, you can buy some enhancing equipment

 At the special product shop, they sell goods used in trade runs. 
To use a shop, click on the shop NPC then click on Buy/Sell then the relevant shop window appears. 
Drag the items that you want to into your inventory. 
You can sell your items to the shop by dragging it to the shop window. If you want to sell or buy a large amount of goods, you can enter the number. But if you want to sell all of that item at once, control key use is very convenient. Only you need to be careful not to sell your important items because the confirmation window won't appear and the trade will be finish immediately when you use the control key.
You don't need to pay a fee when you take your items from storage but you have to pay a fee when you want to deposit your items in storage.
And this is a gift to you for the first time in Constantinople.  In case you might need to buy medicine for Balbardo, take this money also.	0	0	0	Dükkanlar, silah dükkanı, zırh gereçleri dükkanı, iksir dükkanı, aksesuar dükkanı, özel ürün dükkanı ve ambar olarak sınıflara ayrılır.
Silah dükkanında, silah ve kalkan satın alabilirsin. Zırh gereçleri dükkanında, zırh ekipmanları alabilirsin. İksir dükkanı sağlık ve deva ürünleri satar. Aksesuar dükkanında bazı gelişmiş ekipmanları ve return scrolları bulabilirsin. Özel ürün dükkanı ticarette kullanılan mallar satar.
Dükkanı kullanmak için, NPC'nin üzerine, ardından Al/Sat'a tıkla. İlgili dükkan penceresi açılacak. Almak istediğin itemi envanterine sürükle. İtemlerini dükkan penceresine sürükleyerek satabilirsin. Yüksek miktarda item alacağın zaman, almak istediğin miktarı yazmalısın. Toplu olarak item alıp satmak istediğinde de, kontrol tuşunu kullanmak sana kolaylık sağlar. Ancak kontrol tuşunu kullandığında, alışveriş anında yapıldığı için onay penceresi açılmadan sana gerekli itemleri satmadığından emin olmalısın.
Ambardan itemlerini alırken para ödemene gerek yok ancak onları ambara koyarken ücret ödemek zorundasın.
Ve bu ödül ilk kez Constantinople'a geldiğin için. Balbardo'ya ilaç alman gerekirse diye de bu parayı veriyorum.	Las tiendas están clasificadas en: tiendas de armas, tiendas de herramientas defensivas, farmacias, tiendas de accesorios, tiendas de productos especiales y depósitos. En la tienda de armas, puedes comprar armas y Shields. En la tienda de herramientas defensivas, puedes comprar protección. La farmacia vende ítems de recuperación y cura. En la tienda de accesorios, puedes comprar artículos para mejorar tu equipamiento y Return Scrolls. La tienda de productos especiales vende ítems de comercio.Para usar una tienda, haz clic en el NPC de la tienda, luego haz clic en Comprar/vender. La ventana de la tienda aparecerá.  Arrastra el ítem que quieres comprar hacia tu inventario. Para vender tus ítems a la tienda, colócalos en la ventana de la misma. Si quieres vender o comprar una gran cantidad de artículos, puedes ingresar el número, pero si quieres vender todos los ítems de una vez, el uso de la tecla CTRL es muy conveniente. Sólo debes tener cuidado de no vender todos los ítems importantes ya que la ventana de confirmación no aparecerá y el negocio será finalizado inmediatamente cuando oprimas la tecla CTRL. No debes pagar cuando tomes un ítem del depósito, pero sí tienes que hacerlo cuando deposites los ítems. Este es un regalo por tu primera vez en Constantinopla. En caso de que necesites comprar medicina para Balbardo, toma este dinero también.	تصنف المتاجر إلى متاجر الأسلحة متاجر Protector الصيدلية متجر الاكسسوارات متجر الأدوات المميزة والمخزن.
في متجر الأسلحة سيمكنك شراء الأسلحة والدروع وفي متجر Protector سيمكنك شراء Protector والصيدلية تبيع جميع الأدوات المرتبطة بالشفاء والعلاج. وفي متجر الاكسسوارات سيمكنك شراء أدات التحسين ورسائل العودة. ومتاجر الأدوات المميزة تبيع البضائع التي تستخدم في التجارة.
لاستخدام المتجر أنقر على NPC المتجر ثم أنقر على بيع/شراء.ستظهر لك عندها نافذة المتجر الخاصة. قم بسحب الأداة التي ترغب في شرائها إلى خزينتك. ويمكنك أيضاً بيع الأداة التي ترغب فيها بسحبها إلى نافذة المتجر.

أذا أردت شراء كمية كبيرة من البضائع ستحتاج إلى إدخال الكمية التي ترغب في شرائها. ولكن إذا كنت ترغب في بيع/شراء أداة منفردة فاستخدام مفتاح CTR سيكون مناسباً.
ومع ذلك ستحتاج لأن تكون حذراً لئلا تبيع الأدوات الهامة فلن تظهر لك نافذة التأكيد عند استخدام مفتاح CTRL وستتم التجارة في الحال.
لن تحتاج لدفع الرسوم عندما تأخذ أدواتك من المخزن ولكن سيجب عليك دفع الرسوم عند إيداع أدواتك في المخزن.
وهذه هدية لك من أجل زيارتك Constantiople للمرة الأولى وفي حالة ما احتجت إلى دواء من أجل Balbardo خذ هذه الأموال أيضاً.	Alle Geschäfte gehören einer Kategorie an, es gibt Waffengeschäfte, Rüstungsgeschäfte, Tränkeläden, Fachgeschäfte und Lager.
Im Waffengeschäft kannst du Waffen und Schilde kaufen. Im Rüstungsgeschäft kannst du Rüstungen kaufen. In der Tränkeladen gibt es Gegenstände, die heilen und wiederherstellen. Im Zubehörgeschäft kannst du Dinge kaufen, die deine Ausrüstung verbessern.

 Im Fachgeschäft werden Waren verkauft, die auf Handelsreisen benötigt werden. 
Um ein Geschäft zu benutzen, klicke auf den Geschäfts-NPC, dann auf Kaufen/Verkaufen, um das Fenster des Geschäfts zu öffnen. 
Zieh die Gegenstände, die du willst, in dein Inventar. 
Du kannst dem Geschäft deine Gegenstände verkaufen, indem du sie in das Fenster des Geschäfts ziehst. Wenn du viele Waren kaufen oder verkaufen willst, kannst du die gewünschte Anzahl eingeben. Wenn du deinen gesamten Bestand eines Gegenstands auf einmal verkaufen willst, bietet sich die Strg-Taste an. Aber pass auf, dass du nicht aus Versehen wichtige Gegenstände verkaufst, wenn du die Strg-Taste benutzt, weil sich dann kein Bestätigungsfenster öffnet und der Handel sofort abgeschlossen wird.
Du musst keine Gebühr zahlen, wenn du deine Gegenstände aus dem Lager nimmst, aber eine Gebühr wird fällig, wenn du sie im Lager ablegst.
Und das ist ein Geschenk für deinen ersten Besuch in Constantinople. Und solltest du die Medizin von Balbardo kaufen müssen, ist hier auch Geld für dich.
1	2020	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_22	상점 이용법을 알려드리고 선물도 드렸으니 레탈디에게 가서 제가 부탁한 것을 물어봐 주세요.
그럼 잘 부탁드립니다.	0	0	0	0	0	I've taught you how to use the shop and gave you the gift.  Now go ask Retaldi about my favor .  
Thank you.	0	0	0	Sana dükkanı nasıl kullanacağını öğrettim ve sana bir hediye verdim. Şimdi gidip Retaldi'yle isteğim hakkında konuş.
Teşekkürler.	Ya te he enseñado cómo usar las tiendas. Ve con Retaldi y pregúntale lo que te dije. Gracias.	الآن لقد علمتك كيف تستخدم المتاجر لذا اذهب إلى Retaldi واسئلها بشأن طلبي.
شكراً لك.	Ich habe dir erklärt, wie man Geschäfte benutzt und dir ein Geschenk gegeben. Jetzt frag Retaldi wegen meiner Bitte. 
Danke.
1	2021	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_23	소지품창이 꽉 차있어서 선물을 드릴 수 없네요. 빈 공간을 만들고 다시 찾아오세요.	0	0	0	0	0	I can not give you the gift because your invertory is currently full.  Come back when you have empty space in your invertory.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu olduğu için hediyeni sana veremiyorum. Biraz yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Me gustaría darte el regalo, pero tu inventario está lleno. Por favor, regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario.	لا يمكنك تسلم الهدية لأن خزينتك ممتلئة. عد مرة أخرى بعد إفراغ موضع في خزينتك.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir kein Geschenk geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du Platz in deinem Inventar hast.
1	2022	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_24	레탈디에게 가서 발바드로가 약을 구입해 갔는지 물어보세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go and ask Retaldi if Balbardo has bought the medicine.	0	0	0	Retaldi'ye git ve Balbardo'nun ilaçları alıp almadığını sor.	Ve y pregúnta a Retaldi si Balbardo compró la medicina.	اذهب إلى Retaldi واسألها ما إذا كان تاجر الأسلحة Balbardo قد اشترى منها herbsاً.	Geh zu Retaldi und frag sie, ob Balbardo die Medizin gekauft hat.
1	2023	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_25	레탈디에게 가서 발바르도가 약을 사갔는지 알아봐주세요.
만약 약을 사가지 않았다면 제가 드린 돈으로 약을 사서 발바르도에게 전해주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go and ask Retaldi if Balbardo has bought the medicine.
If he didn't buy medicine yet, then buy the medicine with the money I gave you and giive it to Balbardo.	0	0	0	Retaldi'ye git ve Balbardo'nun ilaçları alıp almadığını sor.
Henüz almamışsa lütfen sana verdiğim parayla ilacı al ve onu Balbardo'ya ver.	Ve y pregúnta a Retaldi si Balbardo compró la medicina. Si no lo ha hecho entonces compra la medicina con el dinero que te di y entrégala a Balbardo	ابحث ما إذا قام تاجر الأسلحة Balbardo قام بشراء herbs من الراهبة Retaldi.
لم يقم بشرائها بعد ثم قم بشراء herbs له بالأموال التي أعطيتها لك وقم بإعطاء herbs لتاجر الأسلحة Balbardo.	Geh zu Retaldi und frag sie, ob Balbardo die Medizin gekauft hat.
Wenn nicht, dann kauf sie mit dem Geld, das ich dir gebe, und gib sie Balbardo.
1	2024	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_26	어머~ 안녕하세요.
게임에 도움이 되는 정보를 확인하고 싶으시면 제가 알려드릴께요.
지금 레탈디에게 가보셔야 한다구요? 레탈디는 광장 북동쪽에 있는 물약상점에서 찾을 수 있어요.	0	0	0	0	0	Oh~ Hello.  You will easily find Movia outsilde of the castle if you want to hunt.  If you want helpful information about the game then I'll give you.  Do you have to go to Retaldi now?  Retaldi can be found at the Potion Shop on northeast of piazza.	0	0	0	Oh~ Merhaba. Oyun hakkında yardımcı bilgiye ihtiyacın olursa ben sana anlatırım. Eğer Balbardo'yu arıyorsan meydanın kuzeyindeki Silah Ticareti Dükkanı'na git.	Oh. Hola. Si quieres cazar Movias, los conseguirás fácilmente en las afueras del castillo. Si necesitas información útil sobre el juego, entonces te la daré. ¿Dices que estás buscando a Retaldi? La puedes encontrar en la tienda de Potionsal noreste de la Piazza.	أوه ... مرحباً... إذا احتجت معلومات مفيدة عن اللعبة سأعطيك إياها. هل ستذهب إلى الراهبة Retaldi الآن؟
ستجد الراهبة Retaldi في متجر الجرعات الموجود شمال شرق الميدان.	Oh, hallo. Wenn du Movia jagen willst, findest du sie einfach in der Umgebung des Schlosses. Wenn du hilfreiche Informationen über das Spiel brauchst, kann ich sie dir geben. Musst du zu Retaldi gehen? Retaldi findest du beim Tränkegeschäft nordöstlich vom Hauptplatz.
1	2025	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_27	안녕하세요.
얼굴 낯이 익지 않은 것을 보니 분명 콘스탄티노플에 입성하신 지 얼마 되지 않으셨죠?
새로운 세계에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
저는 성당에서 만든 물약을 사람들에게 저렴한 가격에 판매하고 있는 수녀 레탈디라고 해요.
그런데 무슨 일이시죠?	0	0	0	0	0	Hello.  
Yon must be new to Constantinople because you don't look familiar.
Welcome to the new world.
I'm Nun Retaldi sells the potion at low price which made from sanctuary.
What's the matter.	0	0	0	Merhaba.
Constantinople'da yeni olmalısın, yüzün tanıdık gelmedi.
Yeni dünyaya hoş geldin.
Ben Rahibe Retaldi, tapınakta yapılan iksirleri ucuza satarım.
Sorun nedir?	Hola, debes ser nuevo en Constantinople porque no te he visto antes. Bienvenido a este nuevo mundo. Soy la Monja Retaldi; vendo Potions hechas en el santuario a bajos precios.¿Cuál es el problema?	مرحباً. 
أنت جديد بالتأكيد في Constantinople لأنك لا تبدو مألوفاً.
مرحباً بك إلى العالم الجديد.
أنا الراهبة Retaldi أبيع الجرعات بأرخص الأسعار.
ما الأمر.	Hallo. 
Du musst neu in Constantinople sein, ich kenne dich nicht.
Willkommen in der neuen Welt.
Ich bin die Nonne Retaldi und verkaufe Tränke zu niedrigen Preisen.
Was gibt es?
1	2026	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_28	혹시 무기점 상인 발바르도가 약을 사가지 않았나요?	0	0	0	0	0	Didn't Weapon Trader Balbardo buy the herb?	0	0	0	Silah Tüccarı Balbardo ilacı almamış mı?	¿El comerciante Balbardo no compró la Herb?	ألم يقم تاجر الجرعات Balbardo بشراء herbs؟	Hat Waffenhändler Balbardo die Kräuter gekauft?
1	2027	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_29	아니요. 그런 일은 없었어요.
발바르도가 몸이 아프다는 소문을 들었는데 단순한 몸살인 것 같았어요.
HP 회복 약초를 사서 먹으면 금방 나을텐데...
아플 때 참지 말고 우리 물약상점에서 약을 사먹고 빨리 회복하는 것이 중요한데 일이 바빠서인지 발바르도는 약을 사러오지 않았어요.	0	0	0	0	0	No. It didn’t happen.
I heard Balbardo was sick but it looked like a normal cold.
He would been better if he had bought the medicine and take them.
Important thing  is that you must buy the medicine and take it to get better quickly when you get sick but may be Balbardo was too busy, he didn't come to get the medicine.	0	0	0	Hayır. Bu olamaz.
Balbardo'nun hasta olduğunu duydum ama bana normal bir soğuk algınlığı gibi gelmişti.
İlacı alıp kullanmış olsaydı iyileşirdi.
Önemli olan hasta olduğunda hızla iyileşmek için ilaç almak ama herhalde Balbardo çok meşguldü, ilacı almaya gelmedi.	No. No lo hizo. Escuché que Balbardo estaba enfermo, pero parece un resfriado normal.Ya estaría bien si hubiera comprado y tomado la medicina. Cuando te enfermas, es importante que compres la medicina y la tomes para recuperarte rápido. Quizá Balbardo está muy ocupado porque no ha venido.	لا لم يحدث هذا.
لقد سمعت أن Balbardo مريضاً ولكن يبدو هذا كما لو كان برداً عادياً.
سيكون أفضل إذا قام بشراء الدواء وأخذه.
شئ هام يجب أن تشتري الدواء وتأخذه له ليتحسن بسرعة وربما تكون أنت مريضاً وBalbardo يكون مشغولاً جداً. فهو لم يأتي للحصول على الدواء.	Nein. Das hat er nicht.
Ich habe gehört, dass Balbardo krank ist, aber es sah nach einer normalen Erkältung aus.
Ihm würde es besser gehen, hätte er die Medizin gekauft und eingenommen.
Es ist wichtig, Medizin schnell zu kaufen und einzunehmen, wenn man krank wird, aber vielleicht hatte Balbardo zu viel zu tun, er hat die Medizin nicht gekauft.
1	2028	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_30	그렇군요. 알려주셔서 감사합니다.
HP 회복 약초를 구입하고 싶은데 어떻게 해야 하는지 알려 주십시오. 그리고 발바르도에게 찾아가는 길도 알고 싶습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Alright.  Thanks for letting me know.
I would like to buy HP recovery herb.  Please tell me how to.  And I want to know how to get to Balbardo's house.	0	0	0	Tamam. Beni haberlendirdiğin için teşekkür ederim.
HP recovery herb'ü almak istiyordum. Lütfen nasıl yapacağımı anlat. Ve Balbardo'nun evine nasıl gideceğimi de bilmek istiyorum.	Bien, gracias por contarme. Me gustaría comprar una HP Recovery Herb. Por favor, dime cómo. También quiero saber cómo llegar a la casa de Balbardo.	حسناً. بفضل إخبارك لي.
أرغب في شراء HP recovery herbs. أخبرني كيفية ذلك أرجوك. وأرغب في أن أعرف كيف أذهب لمنزل Balbardo.	Gut. Danke für die Nachricht.
Ich möchte HP Recovery Herb kaufen. Erklär mir bitte, wie. Und ich will wissen, wie ich Balbardos Haus finde.
1	2029	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_31	약을 구입하시려구요? 그럼 대화창을 종료 한 후 저에게 말을 걸어주세요.
구입 / 판매 중에서 구입을 선택하시면 상점창이 뜰 텐데 원하는 HP 회복 약초를 확인할 수 있을 거에요.
HP 회복 약초를 클릭한 뒤 인벤토리에 옮기면 거래 성립! 쉽죠?
제가 알려드린 대로 한 번 해보시겠어요?
HP 회복 약초를 구입하고 저에게 다시 말을 걸어주세요.
발바르도에게 찾아가는 길은 HP 회복 약초를 구입한 다음에 알려드릴게요.	0	0	0	0	0	Do you want the medicine?  Then close the chatting window and talk to me.
Select Buy from Buy / Sell then shop window will appear.  You can check HP recovery herb there.  
Click HP recovery herb then move it to you inventory.  Deal!  Easy huh?
Would you like to try as I just told you?
Talk to me after buying the HP recovery herb.
I'll tell you how to get to Balbardo's house after you buy HP recovery herb.	0	0	0	İlacı mı istiyorsun? O halde konuşma penceresini kapat ve bana dön.
Al / Sat'tan Al'ı seç, dükkan penceresi açılacak. HP recovery herb'ü orada bulabilirsin.
HP recovery herb'e tıkla ardından envanterine götür. İşte aldın! Kolay değil mi?
Anlattığımı bir de sen denemek ister misin?
HP recovery herb'ü aldıktan sonra benimle konuş.
HP recovery herb'ü aldıktan sonra Balbardo'nun evini nasıl bulacağını anlatacağım.	¿Quieres la medicina? Entonces cierra la ventana de Chat y habla conmigo.Selecciona Comprar en la ventana de Comprar/Vender; aparecerá la ventana de la tienda. Puedes revisar la HP Recovery Herb allí. Haz clic en la Herb para moverla a tu inventario. ¡Listo! Es fácil, ¿verdad? ¿Quieres intentarlo ahora? Habla conmigo después de comprar la HP Recovery Herb. Te diré cómo llegar a donde Balbardo después de que la compres.	هل تريد الدواء؟ إذاً قم بإغلاق نافذة المحادثة وتحدث لي.
قم بتحديد شراء من بيع/شراء وستظهر لك نافذة المتجر. يمكنك تحديد عشب استعادة الصحة من هناك.
أنقر على عشب استعادة الصحة ثم قم بتحريكه إلى خزينتك. اتفقنا!
سهل أليس كذلك.
هل ترغب في تجربة ما أخبرتك؟
تحدث لي بعد أن تجرب شراء عشب استعادة الصحة.
سأخبرك كيف تذهب إلى منزل Balbardo  بعد شرائك لعشب استعادة الصحة.	Möchtest du die Medizin? Dann schließ das Chat-Fenster und sprich mit mir.
Wähl unter Kaufen/Verkaufen die Option Kaufen aus, dann öffnet sich das Geschäftsfenster. Dort siehst du das HP Recovery Herb. 
Klicke auf das HP Recovery Herb, dann zieh es ins Inventar. Geschäft abgeschlossen! Einfach, oder?
Möchtest du es einmal probieren?
Rede wieder mit mir, wenn du das HP Recovery Herb gekauft hast.
Ich werde dir den Weg zu Balbardos Haus erklären, wenn du das HP Recovery Herb gekauft hast.
1	2030	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_32	HP 회복 약초를 구입하셨군요. 그럼 아까 물어보셨던 발바르도가 있는 곳을 알려 드릴께요.
광장 북쪽에 무기상점이 있는데 그 곳의 주인이 발바르도 랍니다. 그 곳에서 발바르도를 찾을 수 있을 거에요.
아무튼 앞으로 몸이 아플 때 참지 말고 저를 꼭 찾아주세요.
신의 은총이 당신과 함께하길 기원합니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You have bought HP recovery herb,  Then I'll tell you how to get to Balbardo's house.
There is a Weapon Trade Shop at the north of piazza and Balbardo is the owner.  You can find balbardo there.
Anyway, do not be patient when you are sick and come to me.
May God bless you.	0	0	0	HP recovery herb'ü aldın, şimdi sana Balbardo'nun evini nasıl bulacağını anlatacağım.
Meydanın kuzeyinde Balbardo'nun sahibi olduğu bir Silah Ticareti Dükkanı var. Balbardo'yu orada bulabilirsin.
Her neyse, hastalanma, kötü hissettiğinde bana gel.
Tanrı seni korusun.	Has comprado la HP Recovery Herb. Ahora, te diré cómo llegar a la casa de Balbardo. Hay una tienda de armas al norte de Piazza y Balbardo es el dueño. Lo puedes encontrar ahí. Me alegra mucho que trates de ayudar.Búscame cuando te enfermes.Que Dios te bendiga.	لقد قمت بشراء عشب استعادة الصحة. سأخبرك كيف تذهب إلى منزل Balbardo.
يوجد متجر أسلحة شمال الميدان وBalbardo هو مالك هذا المتجر. ستجد Balbardo هناك.
على آية حال لا تكن مريضاً عندما تأتي لي.
ليباركك الرب.	Du hast das HP Recovery Herb gekauft. Ich werde dir den Weg zu Balbardos Haus erklären.
Im Norden des Hauptplatzes ist ein Waffengeschäft, Balbardo ist der Besitzer. Dort findest du Balbardo.
Und wenn du je krank wirst, warte nicht zu lange, komm gleich zu mir.
Gott segne dich.
1	2031	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_33	레탈디에게서 HP 회복 약초를 구입하고 다시 레탈디와 대화하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Buy Hp recover herb from Retaldi and talk to Retaldi again.	0	0	0	Retaldi'den HP recovery herb'ü al ve Retaldi'yle tekrar konuş.	Compra la HP Recovery Herb de Retaldi y habla con ella de nuevo.	قم بشراء عشب استعادة الصحة من Retaldi وتحدث إلى Retaldi مرة أخرى.	Kauf das HP Recover Herb von Retaldi und red wieder mit Retaldi.
1	2032	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_34	HP 회복 약초를 발바르도에게 전해주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Deliver HP recover herb to Balbardo.	0	0	0	HP recovery herb'ü Balbardo'ya götür.	Entrega la HP Recovery Herb a Balbardo.	قم بتوصيل عشب استعادة الصحة إلى Balbardo.	Bring Balbardo das HP Recovery Herb
1	2033	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_35	발바르도에게 찾아가시는 것이라면 광장 북쪽에 있는 무기상점으로 가보세요.	0	0	0	0	0	If you are looking for Balbardo, go to Weapon Trade Shop at the north of piazza.	0	0	0	Eğer Balbardo'yu arıyorsan meydanın kuzeyindeki Silah Ticareti Dükkanı'na git.	Si vas a ver a Balbardo, deberías ir a la tienda de armas al norte de la Piazza.	إذا كنت تبحث عن Balbardo اذهب إلى متجر الأسلحة شمال الميدان.	Wenn du Balbardo suchst, geh zum Waffengeschäft im Norden des Hauptplatzes.
1	2034	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_36	어머~ 안녕하세요.
게임에 도움이 되는 정보를 확인하고 싶으시면 제가 알려드릴께요.
그런데 발바르도를 찾으신다구요? 발바르도는 광장 북쪽에 있는 무기상점에서 찾을 수 있어요.	0	0	0	0	0	Oh~ Hello.  You will easily find Movia outsilde of the castle if you want to hunt.  If you want helpful information about the game then I'll give you.  But did you say you are looking for Balbardo?  Balbardo can be found at the Weapon Trade Shop on north of piazza.	0	0	0	Oh~ Merhaba. Oyun hakkında yardımcı bilgiye ihtiyacın olursa ben sana anlatırım. Eğer Balbardo'yu arıyorsan meydanın kuzeyindeki Silah Ticareti Dükkanı'na git.	Oh. Hola. Si quieres cazar Movias, los conseguirás fácilmente en las afueras del castillo. Si necesitas información útil sobre el juego, entonces te la daré. ¿Dices que estás buscando a Balbardo? Lo puedes encontrar en la tienda de armas al norte de la Piazza.	أوه ... مرحباً. ستجد Movias بسهولة خارج القلعة إذا رغبت في اصطيادها. إذا كنت ترغب في الحصول على معلومات مفيدة عن اللعبة سأعلمك إياها ولكن هل تقول بأنك تبحث عن Balbardo؟ ستجد Balbardo في متجر الأسلحة شمال الميدان.	Oh, hallo. Wenn du Movia jagen willst, findest du sie einfach in der Umgebung des Schlosses. Wenn du hilfreiche Informationen über das Spiel brauchst, kann ich sie dir geben. Aber du suchst Balbardo, sagst du? Balbardo findest du beim Waffengeschäft nördlich vom Hauptplatz.
1	2035	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_37	어서오시오. 보아하니 성에 입성한지 얼마 되지 않은 사람같군.
나는 콘스탄티노플 무기점 상인 발바르도라고 하오.
그런데 당신의 얼굴을 보아하니 무슨 할 말이라도 있는 것 같은데 무슨 일이오?	0	0	0	0	0	Welcome.  Looks like you just got to castle.
I'm Weapon Trader Balbardo of Constrantinople. 
Do you have something to say?  What is it?	0	0	0	Hoş geldin. Kaleye yeni gelmiş gibi gözüküyorsun.
Ben Constantinople'li Silah Tüccarı Balbardo.
Söyleyecek bir şeyin mi var? Nedir?	Bienvenido. Parece que acabas de llegar al castillo.Soy Balbardo, el comerciante de Armas de Constantinople. ¿Tienes algo que decirme? ¿Qué es?	مرحباً. يبدو أنك أتيت لتوك إلى القلعة.
أنا تاجر الأسلحة Balbardo في Constantinople.
هل لديك شئ لتقوله؟ ما هو.	Willkommen. Du bist wohl gerade im Schloss angekommen.
Ich bin der Waffenhändler Balbardo aus Constantinople. 
Willst du etwas sagen? Was denn?
1	2036	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_38	누군가 HP 회복 약초를 당신에게 전해달라고 부탁을 받았습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Someone asked a favor to give this medicine to give you.	0	0	0	Birisi benden bir iyilik yapıp bu ilacı sana vermemi istedi.	Alguien me pidió el favor de darte esta medicina.	طلب مني شخص ما خدمة له بإعطائك هذا الدواء.	Jemand bat mich, dir diese Medizin zu bringen.
1	2037	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_39	아니… 어떻게 내가 아픈 것을 알고 이런 것을…
혹시 이 약을 보내주라고 한 사람을 알 수 없겠소?	0	0	0	0	0	Oh…How did someone know that I was sick… Can I ask who sent this herb?	0	0	0	Oh…O her kimse hasta olduğumu nasıl biliyor olabilir… Bu ilacı kimin yolladığını sorabilir miyim?	Oh... ¿Cómo sabían que estaba enfermo? ¿Puedo preguntar quién envió esta Herb?	أوه ... كيف يمكن لأحد أن يعلم بأنني كنت مريض .. هل يمكنني أن أسئل من الذي أرسل هذا العشب؟	Oh… Woher weiß man, dass ich krank bin… Darf ich fragen, wer diese Kräuter schickt?
1	2038	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_40	죄송합니다. 약을 보내준 사람과 약속을 해서 말씀드릴 수 없습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Sorry.  I promised the person not to tell you.	0	0	0	Üzgünüm. Söylemeyeceğime dair söz verdim.	Lo siento, le prometí a esa persona que no te diría.	للأسف. فقد وعدت هذا الشخص بألا أخبرك.	Tut mir leid. Ich versprach, es nicht zu erzählen.
1	2039	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_41	그렇다면 어쩔 수 없군. 혹시 약을 보내라고 부탁한 분을 만나게 되거든 고맙다고 전해주시오.
약을 배달해준 당신에게라도 물약을 전해준 보답을 하고 싶으니 내가 주는 선물을 받아주시오.	0	0	0	0	0	Oh well.  Then Please say thank you if you happen to meet the person who asked to send the medicine.
Alright.  I'll give you a reward for bringing me medicine.  Take the gift I give you,
	0	0	0	Oh peki. O halde lütfen bu ilacı gönderen kişiye rastlarsan ona teşekkür ettiğimi söyle.
Tamam. Bana ilaç getirdğin için hediye vereceğim, lütfen al.	De acuerdo; entonces dale las gracias de mi parte a esa persona cuando la vuelvas a ver. Muy bien, te daré una recompensa muy útil. Toma este regalo.	أوه. حسناً. إذاً بلغ تحياتي للشخص الذي طلب منك توصيل الدواء.
حسناً سأعطيك أخبار ستساعدك كمكافأة لك على إحضارك الدواء لي.  خذ هذه الهدية كمكافأة لك.	Nun gut. Falls du die Person wieder triffst, die die Medizin geschickt hat, danke ihr bitte von mir.
Gut. Ich gebe dir eine Belohnung dafür, dass du mir die Medizin gebracht hast. Nimm dieses Geschenk an.

1	2040	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_42	안내인 라피에게 찾아가세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Guide Raffy.	0	0	0	Rehber Raffy'ye git.	Ve con el Guía Raffy.	اذهب إلى المرشدة Lipria	Geh zu Stadtführer Raffy.
1	2041	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_43	안내인 라피를 찾고 있소? 그녀는 콘스탄티노플 서문에서 찾을 수 있소.	0	0	0	0	0	Are you looking for Guide Raffy?  You can find her at west gate of Constantinople.	0	0	0	Rehber Raffy'yi mı arıyorsun? Onu Constantinople'nin batı kapısında bulabilirsin.	¿Estás buscando al guía Raffy? Lo puedes encontrar en la entrada norte de Constantinople.	هل تبحث عن المرشدة Lipria؟ ستجد Lipria عند بوابة Constantinople الشمالية.	Du suchst Stadtführer Raffy? Du findest ihn am Westtor von Constantinople.
1	2042	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_44	어서오세요.
마을 사람들을 만나고 이곳저곳을 돌아다니면서 콘스탄티노플에 대해서 좋은 인상을 받으셨길 바랍니다.
콘스탄티노플을 둘러보고 어느정도 기본 정보는 얻으셨으니 이제는 성 밖으로 나가고 싶으시겠죠? 하지만 성 밖은 성 안과는 달리 괴물들로 득실거려 곳곳에 위험이 도사리고 있지요. 그래서 초보 여행자들이 괴물에게 공격을 받아 다치는 일이 자주 발생하고 있어요.
게다가 최근에는 성 밖에 살고 있는 모비하라는 괴물이 있는데 어쩐 일인지 갑작스레 그 수가 늘어서 사람들을 위협하고 있는데 나라에서는 초보 여행자들에게 괴물의 위험함을 알리기 좋은 기회라고 생각하여 모비하 20마리를 사냥해오는 초보 여행자들에게 보상을 해주고 있어요.
당신이라면 어렵지 않게 수행할 수 있을 것 같네요. 전투 방법이라면 제가 설명해 드릴께요.	0	0	0	0	0	Welcome.
Hope you enjoyed talking to the village people in Constantinople.
You probably want to go out of the castle now that you got the basic information, don’t you? But danger lurks outside the castle with monsters every here and there. That is why novice travelers get injured from monsters.
And recently the number of monsters called Movia has increased, threatening people. The country is rewarding novice travelers if they hunt 20 Movias, to show them how dangerous a monster can be.
Doesn't seem like it'll be a hard task for you. I'll teach you how to battle.
	0	0	0	Hoş geldin.
Umarım Constantinople'daki köylülerle sohbet etmekten zevk almışsındır. Temel bilgileri aldığına göre artık muhtemelen kalenin dışına çıkmak istersin, değil mi? Fakat heryerde canavarlarla tehlikeler yatıyor. Acemi gezginler canavarlar tarafından bu sepeble zarar görüyor. Movia denilen canavar kalenin dışında yaşıyor ve Movia'ların sayısı aniden artarak insanları tehdit ediyor. Ülke ne kadar tehlikeli bir canavar olduğunu göstermek için acemi gezginlere 20 Movia avlamaları durumunda ödül veriyor.
Zor bir görev gibi görme. Sana nasıl savaşacağını anlatacağım.	Bienvenido. Espero que hayas disfrutado hablar con los ciudadanos de Constantinople. Probablemente quieres salir del castillo ahora que has obtenido la información básica ¿cierto? Te advierto que hay mucho peligro fuera del castillo, pues los monstruos merodean por todos lados. Por eso, los viajeros novatos son lastimados por los monstruos. Recientemente, el número de monstruos llamados Movias ha incrementado y se han convertido en una amenaza para la gente. El país recompensará a los viajeros novatos si cazan 20 Movias para mostrarles lo peligroso que puede ser un monstruo. No parece ser una difícil tarea para ti. Te enseñaré cómo combatir.	مرحباً.
آمل أن تكون قد استمتعت بالتحدث إلى القرووين في Constantinople.
ربما ترغب في الذهاب خارج القلعة الآن وقد حصلت على المعلومات الأساسية أليس كذلك؟ ولكن الخطر الكامن خارج القلعة في الوحوش هنا وهناك. هذا سبب إصابة المسافرون المبتدئون من هذه الوحوش.
بما أن عدد الوحوش المسماة Movias في تزايد مؤخراً وتتزايد تهديدها للناس فالدولة تخصص جائزة للمسافرين المبتدئين إذا قاموا باصطياد 20 Movias ليروا مدى خطورة هذه الوحوش.
لا يبدو أنني طلبت منك مهمة عسيرة سأعلمك كيفية القتال.	Willkommen.
Ich hoffe, du hast gerne mit den Leuten in Constantinople gesprochen.
Da du jetzt alle grundlegenden Informationen hast, willst du jetzt wohl das Schloss verlassen? Aber außerhalb des Schlosses lauern überall Gefahren. Deswegen werden neue Reisende oft von Monstern verletzt.
In letzter Zeit wurden es plötzlich immer mehr dieser Menschen bedrohenden Monster, die Movia genannt werden. Wenn neue Reisende 20 Movias jagen, belohnt sie das Land, um ihnen zu zeigen, wie gefährlich Monster sein können.
Es sollte nicht zu schwer für dich sein. Ich werde dir beibringen, wie man kämpft.

1	2043	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_45	전투방법	0	0	0	0	0	Battle Method	0	0	0	Savaşma Yöntemi	Método de combate	طريقة القتال	Wie man kämpft
1	2044	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_46	전투는 몬스터를 먼저 공격하거나 몬스터에게 공격을 받게되면 시작해요. 몬스터를 한번 클릭하면 몬스터가 선택이 되는데 이때 화면 상단에 몬스터의 정보가 나온답니다. 이 때 몬스터의 이름이 파란색일수록 자신보다 저레벨 몬스터이고 빨간색일수록 고레벨, 흰색은 동레벨 몬스터를 나타내는 것이니 이름이 흰색인 몬스터를 사냥하는 것이 가장 자신에게 적합한 사냥일 것이에요. 공격은 몬스터를 마우스 왼쪽 버튼으로 더블 클릭하거나 CTRL+왼쪽클릭을 하면 공격을 시작해요. 전투중에 HP가 부족하게 될 때를 대비해 회복아이템을 퀵슬롯창에 등록시켜 놓고 싸우는 것이 안전할 것이에요. 전투 후에 회복약을 아끼고 싶을때는 앉아서 회복하면 금방 회복이 될 것이니 잘 기억해 두세요.
전투 방법을 알려 드렸으니 이제 직접 모비하 20마리를 사냥하고 오세요.
그리고 이것은 HP가 빠르게 회복되는데 도움을 주는 물건이니 전투를 하기전에 사용하면 도움이 될 거에요.	0	0	0	0	0	Combat begins when you attack a monster first or am attacked by a monster. Monsters can be targeted when you click on them.
Targeting them will have their stats appear in the upper side of your screen. If the selected monster's name has a blue colour, it means that it is lower-level than you. If it is red-coloured, it is higher-level than you. And if it is white-coloured, it means that it is the same level. So it is desirable for you to hunt a monster whose name is white-coloured. 
You can attack a monster by double-clicking the left button on it or left-clicking on it with the control key held.
It is safer to register you recovery/health potion to the quick slot interface to prepare for the inevitable reduction of your HP/MP. If you want to heal without using potions after combat, just sit down and you will be recovered soon. 
Now I taught you how to do a combat so go hunt 20 Movia by yourself.
And this will help to recover HP fasster so it will be helpful if you use it before the combat.	0	0	0	Dövüş, sen canavara saldırdığında ya da canavar sana saldırdığında başlar. Canavarlar üstlerine tıkladığında hedef alınır.
Onlara hedef aldığında ekranın üst tarafında durumları belirir. Eğer canavarın ismi mavi ise, bu senden seviye olarak düşük demektir. Kırmızı ise seviyesi senden yüksek, beyaz ise seviyeler eşit demektir. Bu yüzden ismi beyaz yazılı bir canavara saldırıp saldırmamak sana bağlı.
Canavarın üzerine sol tuşu çift tıklayarak ya da kontrol tuşunu basılı tutarken sol tıklayarak ona saldırabilirsin.
HP/MP'nin aniden bitmemesi için iyileşme/sağlık iksirlerini hızlı arabirime atayarak kendine tedbir alabilirsin. İksir kullanmadan iyileşmek istersen oturarak sağlığını geri kazanabillirsin.
Artık sana nasıl dövüşeceğini öğrettiğime göre yalnız başına gidip 20 Movia avlayabilirsin.
Bu HP'nin daha hızlı dolmasına yardımcı olur bu yüzden dövüşten önce kullanmanın çok faydası olur.	El combate empieza cuando atacas a un monstruo o eres atacado por uno. Al hacer clic sobre un monstruo, lo apuntas. El estado del monstruo aparecerá en la parte superior de la pantalla. Si su nombre es de color azul, significa que el monstruo tiene un nivel más bajo que el tuyo; si es de color rojo, su nivel es más alto que el tuyo; y si es de color blanco quiere decir que es de tu mismo nivel y puedes decidir enfrentarlo o no. Para atacar a un monstruo, haz doble clic izquierdo o mantén presionada la tecla CTRL. Es recomendable que coloques tus Health/Recovery Potions en la interfaz de espacios rápidos para que estés preparado, pues tu HP y MP se pueden reducir repentinamente durante el combate. Si te quieres recuperar de un combate sin usar Potions, sólo siéntate y te recuperarás pronto. Ya te enseñé el método de combate, así que ve a cazar los Movias. Esto te ayudará a recuperar tu HP más, será muy útil que lo uses antes del combate.	تبدأ المعركة عند قيامك بالهجوم الأول على الوحش أو عند قيام الوحش بمهاجمتك. يمكنك تحديد الوحوش كهدف عند النقر عليهم.

باستهداف الوحوش ستظهر حالتهم في الجانب العلوي من شاشتك. إذا قمت بالنقر على اسم الوحش وكان بلون أزرق فهذا يعني أنه بمستوى أقل من مستواك وإذا كان باللون الأحمر فهذا يعني أن مستواه أعلى من مستواك وإذا كان باللون الأبيض فهذا يعني أنه في نفس المستوى. لذا فمن المفضل لك اصطياد الوحوش التي أسماؤها باللون الأبيض.
يمكنك مهاجمة الوحوش بالنقر المزدوج على المفتاح الأيسر للفأرة على الوحش أو النقر بالمفتاح الأيسر مرة واحدة مع الضغط والاستمرار على مفتاح Ctrl.
من الآمن أن تضع جرعات استرجاع الصحة إلى شريط المواضع السريعة لتكون جاهزاً لمواجه نقص الصحة/ السحر. إذا أردت الشفاء بدون استخدام الجرعات بعد المعركة فالجلوس أرضاً سيساعدك في الشفاء.
الآن قد علمتك كيفية القتال. لذا فاذهب وقم باصطياد 20 Movias بنفسك.
وهذا سيساعدك على استرجاع صحتك أسرع لذا فسيكون مفيداً لك إذا استخدمته قبل القتال.	Der Kampf beginnt, wenn du ein Monster angreifst oder von einem Monster angegriffen wirst. Du zielst auf ein Monster, indem du darauf klickst.
Die Statistiken eines ausgewähltes Monsters werden oben auf deinem Bildschirm angezeigt. Wenn der Name des ausgewählten Monsters blau ist, ist sein Level niedriger als deiner. Wenn er rot ist, hat es einen höheren Level. Und ist er weiß, dann habt ihr beide den gleichen Level. Du solltest also Monster jagen, deren Namen weiß sind. 
Du kannst ein Monster entweder mit einem Doppelklick oder mit einem Klick bei gedrückter Strg-Taste angreifen.
Du solltest deine Heil- und Wiederherstellungstränke in die Schnellauswahl aufnehmen, um dich auf die Verringerung deiner HP/MP vorzubereiten. Wenn du dich nach dem Kampf heilen willst, ohne einen Trank zu benutzen, setz dich einfach hin, das wird deine Punkte schnell wiederherstellen. 
Ich habe dir erklärt, wie man kämpft, also jage 20 Movia.
Das wird deine HP schneller wiederherstellen, also ist es hilfreich, wenn du es vor dem Kampf benutzt.
1	2045	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_47	소지품창이 꽉 차서 도움이 되는 물건을 드릴 수 없어요. 빈 공간을 두 칸이상 만들고 다시 찾아오세요.	0	0	0	0	0	I can't give you helpful item because your inventory is currently full.  Please come back when you have at least two empty spaces in your inventory.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu olduğu için sana faydalı itemi veremiyorum. Biraz boş yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Me gustaría darte algo útil, pero tu inventario está lleno. Por favor, regresa cuando tengas espacio en tu inventario.	لا يمكن أن تحصل على أدوات مساعدة لأن خزينتك ممتلئة حالياً. عد مرة أخرى عندما تقوم بإفراغ مواضع في خزينتك.	Dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir den hilfreichen Gegenstand nicht geben. Bitte komm wieder, wenn du mindestens zwei Plätze in deinem Inventar hast.
1	2046	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_48	모비하 20마리를 사냥하고 안내인 라피에게 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Report to Guide Raffy after hunting 20 Movia.	0	0	0	20 Movia avla ve Rehber Raffy'ye bildir.	Caza 20 Movias e infórmalo al guía Raffy.	قم باصطياد 20 Movias وأخبر المرشدة Lipria.	Erstatte Stadtführer Raffy Bericht, nachdem du 20 Movia gejagt hast.
1	2047	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_49	모비하 사냥이 완료되었습니다. 안내인 라피에게 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Movia hunt is completed.  Report to Guide Raffy.	0	0	0	Movia avı tamamlandı. Rehber Raffy'ye bildir.	Has terminado de derrotar a los Movias. Infórmalo al Guía Raffy.	تم اصطياد Movias. أخبر المرشدة Lipria.	Die Jagd auf die Movia ist abgeschlossen. Erstatte Stadtführer Raffy Bericht.
1	2048	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_50	아직 모비하 20마리 사냥이 완료되지 않았어요. 완료 후 다시 찾아 오시면 좋은 선물을 드릴께요.
만약 게임에 도움이 되는 정보를 확인하고 싶으시면 원하는 목록을 클릭해 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Hunt 20 Movia is not completed.  I'll give you a great gift if you come back after you complete the Movia hunt.
If you want to check out a helpful information, click the list you want to check.	0	0	0	Movia avını tamamlamadın. Movia avını tamamlayıp bana döndükten sonra sana güzel bir hediye vereceğim. Faydalı olacak bilgileri kontrol etmek istersen talep listesini seç.	La caza de Movias no está completa. Te daré un gran regalo después de que los derrotes. Si quieres revisar información útil, haz clic en la lista que quieres revisar.	تم اصطياد Movias. سأعطيك هدية رائعة إذا عدت بعد إتمام اصطياد Movias.
إذا رغبت في الحصول على معلومات مفيدة أنقر على القائمة التي ترغب في فحصها.	Die Jagd auf 20 Movia ist noch nicht abgeschlossen. Ich gebe dir ein tolles Geschenk, wenn die Jagd auf die Movia abgeschlossen ist.
Wenn du hilfreiche Informationen brauchst, klicke auf die Liste.
1	2049	SN_TALK_QTUTORIAL_EU_2_51	모비하 사냥을 완료하고 오셨군요.
그럼 마지막으로 당신에게 필요한 정보를 하나 더 알려드릴께요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've completed Movia hunt.
Then I'll give you one more helpful information for the last time.	0	0	0	Movia avını tamamladın.
Son olarak sana bir bilgi daha vereceğim.	Has completado la caza de Movias. Entonces, por último, te daré una información más que necesitas.	لقد أتممت اصطياد Movias.
سأخبرك معلومات مفيدة للمرة الأخيرة.	Die Jagd auf die Movia ist abgeschlossen.
Dann werde ich dir noch eine letzte Information geben.
