1	9900	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_HA_B_RARE	플라티나 아멧	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Armet	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9901	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_HA_C_RARE	플라티나 아멧	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Armet	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9902	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_SA_A_RARE	플라티나 폴드론	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Pauldron	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9903	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_SA_B_RARE	플라티나 폴드론	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Pauldron	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9904	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_SA_C_RARE	플라티나 폴드론	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Pauldron	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9905	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_BA_A_RARE	플라티나 플레이트 아머	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Plate Armor	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9906	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_BA_B_RARE	플라티나 플레이트 아머	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Plate Armor	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9907	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_BA_C_RARE	플라티나 플레이트 아머	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Plate Armor	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9908	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_LA_A_RARE	플라티나 플레이트 폴린	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Plate Poleyn	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9909	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_LA_B_RARE	플라티나 플레이트 폴린	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Plate Poleyn	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9910	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_LA_C_RARE	플라티나 플레이트 폴린	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Plate Poleyn	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9911	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_AA_A_RARE	플라티나 건틀릿	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Gauntlet	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9912	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_AA_B_RARE	플라티나 건틀릿	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Gauntlet	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9913	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_AA_C_RARE	플라티나 건틀릿	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Gauntlet	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9914	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_FA_A_RARE	플라티나 그리브	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Greave	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9915	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_FA_B_RARE	플라티나 그리브	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Greave	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9916	SN_ITEM_EU_HEAVY_17_FA_C_RARE	플라티나 그리브	0	0	0	0	0	Platina Greave	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9917	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_HA_A_RARE	오르비스 모리안	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Morion	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9918	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_HA_B_RARE	오르비스 모리안	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Morion	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9919	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_HA_C_RARE	오르비스 모리안	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Morion	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9920	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_SA_A_RARE	오르비스 얼렛	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Alette	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9921	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_SA_B_RARE	오르비스 얼렛	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Alette	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9922	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_SA_C_RARE	오르비스 얼렛	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Alette	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9923	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_BA_A_RARE	오르비스 메일	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Mail	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9924	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_BA_B_RARE	오르비스 메일	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Mail	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9925	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_BA_C_RARE	오르비스 메일	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Mail	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9926	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_LA_A_RARE	오르비스 테싯	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Tasset	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9927	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_LA_B_RARE	오르비스 테싯	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Tasset	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9928	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_LA_C_RARE	오르비스 테싯	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Tasset	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9929	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_AA_A_RARE	오르비스 글러브	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Glove	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9930	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_AA_B_RARE	오르비스 글러브	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Glove	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9931	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_AA_C_RARE	오르비스 글러브	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Glove	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9932	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_FA_A_RARE	오르비스 부츠	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Boots	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9933	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_FA_B_RARE	오르비스 부츠	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Boots	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9934	SN_ITEM_EU_LIGHT_17_FA_C_RARE	오르비스 부츠	0	0	0	0	0	Orbis Boots	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9935	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_HA_A_RARE	토니트루스 매직 햇	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Magic Hat	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9936	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_HA_B_RARE	토니트루스 매직 햇	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Magic Hat	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9937	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_HA_C_RARE	토니트루스 매직 햇	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Magic Hat	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9938	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_SA_A_RARE	토니트루스 히마티온	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Himation	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9939	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_SA_B_RARE	토니트루스 히마티온	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Himation	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9940	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_SA_C_RARE	토니트루스 히마티온	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Himation	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9941	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_BA_A_RARE	토니트루스 로브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Robe	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9942	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_BA_B_RARE	토니트루스 로브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Robe	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9943	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_BA_C_RARE	토니트루스 로브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Robe	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9944	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_LA_A_RARE	토니트루스 언더 로브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Under Robe	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9945	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_LA_B_RARE	토니트루스 언더 로브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Under Robe	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9946	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_LA_C_RARE	토니트루스 언더 로브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Under Robe	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9947	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_AA_A_RARE	토니트루스 미튼	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Mitten	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9948	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_AA_B_RARE	토니트루스 미튼	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Mitten	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9949	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_AA_C_RARE	토니트루스 미튼	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Mitten	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9950	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_FA_A_RARE	토니트루스 위브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Weave	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9951	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_FA_B_RARE	토니트루스 위브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Weave	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9952	SN_ITEM_EU_CLOTHES_17_FA_C_RARE	토니트루스 위브	0	0	0	0	0	Tonitrus Weave	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9953	SN_ITEM_EU_RING_17_A_RARE	홀리 로드 링	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Ring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9954	SN_ITEM_EU_RING_17_B_RARE	홀리 로드 링	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Ring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9955	SN_ITEM_EU_RING_17_C_RARE	홀리 로드 링	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Ring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9956	SN_ITEM_EU_EARRING_17_A_RARE	홀리 로드 이어링	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Earring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9957	SN_ITEM_EU_EARRING_17_B_RARE	홀리 로드 이어링	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Earring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9958	SN_ITEM_EU_EARRING_17_C_RARE	홀리 로드 이어링	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Earring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9959	SN_ITEM_EU_NECKLACE_17_A_RARE	홀리 로드 네클리스	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Necklace	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9960	SN_ITEM_EU_NECKLACE_17_B_RARE	홀리 로드 네클리스	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Necklace	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9961	SN_ITEM_EU_NECKLACE_17_C_RARE	홀리 로드 네클리스	0	0	0	0	0	Holy Lord Necklace	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9962	SN_ITEM_EU_DAGGER_21_A_RARE	제누스 시카	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Genus Sica	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9963	SN_ITEM_EU_DAGGER_21_B_RARE	제누스 시카	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Genus Sica	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9964	SN_ITEM_EU_DAGGER_21_C_RARE	제누스 시카	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Genus Sica	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9965	SN_ITEM_EU_SWORD_21_A_RARE	제누스 엔시스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Genus Ensis	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9966	SN_ITEM_EU_SWORD_21_B_RARE	제누스 엔시스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Genus Ensis	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9967	SN_ITEM_EU_SWORD_21_C_RARE	제누스 엔시스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Genus Ensis	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9968	SN_ITEM_EU_TSWORD_21_A_RARE	레그눔 익투스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Regnum Ictus	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9969	SN_ITEM_EU_TSWORD_21_B_RARE	레그눔 익투스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Regnum Ictus	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9970	SN_ITEM_EU_TSWORD_21_C_RARE	레그눔 익투스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Regnum Ictus	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9971	SN_ITEM_EU_AXE_21_A_RARE	임페리움 아페르	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Imperium Afer	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9972	SN_ITEM_EU_AXE_21_B_RARE	임페리움 아페르	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Imperium Afer	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9973	SN_ITEM_EU_AXE_21_C_RARE	임페리움 아페르	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Imperium Afer	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9974	SN_ITEM_EU_CROSSBOW_21_A_RARE	해븐스 크로우	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Heaven's Crow	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9975	SN_ITEM_EU_CROSSBOW_21_B_RARE	해븐스 크로우	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Heaven's Crow	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9976	SN_ITEM_EU_CROSSBOW_21_C_RARE	해븐스 크로우	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Heaven's Crow	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9977	SN_ITEM_EU_DARKSTAFF_21_A_RARE	해븐스 크리스탈	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Heaven's Cristal	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9978	SN_ITEM_EU_DARKSTAFF_21_B_RARE	해븐스 크리스탈	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Heaven's Cristal	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9979	SN_ITEM_EU_DARKSTAFF_21_C_RARE	해븐스 크리스탈	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Heaven's Cristal	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9980	SN_ITEM_EU_TSTAFF_21_A_RARE	키메라 레그나토르	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Chimera Regnator	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9981	SN_ITEM_EU_TSTAFF_21_B_RARE	키메라 레그나토르	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Chimera Regnator	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9982	SN_ITEM_EU_TSTAFF_21_C_RARE	키메라 레그나토르	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Chimera Regnator	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9983	SN_ITEM_EU_HARP_21_A_RARE	카루스 다프네	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Carus Daphne	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9984	SN_ITEM_EU_HARP_21_B_RARE	카루스 다프네	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Carus Daphne	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9985	SN_ITEM_EU_HARP_21_C_RARE	카루스 다프네	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Carus Daphne	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9986	SN_ITEM_EU_STAFF_21_A_RARE	임메모라빌리스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Immemorabilis	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9987	SN_ITEM_EU_STAFF_21_B_RARE	임메모라빌리스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Immemorabilis	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9988	SN_ITEM_EU_STAFF_21_C_RARE	임메모라빌리스	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Immemorabilis	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9989	SN_ITEM_EU_SHIELD_21_A_RARE	엑사르 마티오	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Exarmatio	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9990	SN_ITEM_EU_SHIELD_21_B_RARE	엑사르 마티오	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Exarmatio	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9991	SN_ITEM_EU_SHIELD_21_C_RARE	엑사르 마티오	0	0	0	0	0	Ultimate Exarmatio	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9992	SN_ITEM_EU_RING_21_A_RARE	엔젤 로드 링	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Ring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9993	SN_ITEM_EU_RING_21_B_RARE	엔젤 로드 링	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Ring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9994	SN_ITEM_EU_RING_21_C_RARE	엔젤 로드 링	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Ring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9995	SN_ITEM_EU_EARRING_21_A_RARE	엔젤 로드 이어링	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Earring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9996	SN_ITEM_EU_EARRING_21_B_RARE	엔젤 로드 이어링	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Earring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9997	SN_ITEM_EU_EARRING_21_C_RARE	엔젤 로드 이어링	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Earring	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9998	SN_ITEM_EU_NECKLACE_21_A_RARE	엔젤 로드 네클리스	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Necklace	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	9999	SN_ITEM_EU_NECKLACE_21_B_RARE	엔젤 로드 네클리스	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Necklace	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10000	SN_ITEM_EU_NECKLACE_21_C_RARE	엔젤 로드 네클리스	0	0	0	0	0	Angle Lord Necklace	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10001	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_NECKLACE_13	한계돌파 데미지 증가	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10002	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_NECKLACE_14	한계돌파 데미지 증가	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10003	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_NECKLACE_15	한계돌파 데미지 증가	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10004	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_NECKLACE_13_TT_DESC	룬스톤에 의해 한계돌파가 된 목걸이에서 사용할 수 있는 숨겨진 스킬	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10005	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_NECKLACE_14_TT_DESC	룬스톤에 의해 한계돌파가 된 목걸이에서 사용할 수 있는 숨겨진 스킬	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10006	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_NECKLACE_15_TT_DESC	룬스톤에 의해 한계돌파가 된 목걸이에서 사용할 수 있는 숨겨진 스킬	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10007	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_RING	한계돌파 데미지 증가	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10008	SN_SKILL_ENHANCER_RING_TT_DESC	룬스톤에 의해 한계돌파가 된 반지에서 사용할 수 있는 숨겨진 스킬	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	10009	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_WARRIOR_A_DD_TT_DESC	물러서지 않는 용기의 감정이 실린 춤을 춰서 근방에 있는 파티원들의 사기를 올려주고 근거리 물리 데미지를 증가시킨다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Increases party members' morale and short distance physical damage by expressing valor in dance. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Cesaretini dansla göstererek parti üyelerinin moralini ve kısa menzilli fiziksel hasar gücünü arttırır. Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Con expresiones de valentía al bailar, se levanta el ánimo de los miembros del grupo y se incrementa el daño físico que produzcan a corta distancia. No puedes utilizar esta habilidad con otras simultáneamente; su efecto desaparecerá si sufres un ataque. Cuando otras personas interpretan la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	يزيد من معنويات أفراد الفريق وقوة التدمير البدني الذي يحدثونه بالتعبير عن الشجاعة بالرقص. ولا يمكنك استخدام هذه المهارة مع مهارة أخرى في نفس الوقت وسيختفي تأثيرها عندما يتم مهاجمتك. وعندما يعزف الآخرون الموسيقى ستعمل هذه المهارة فقط في نطاق تأثير الموسيقى.	Erhöht die Moral von Gruppenmitgliedern und die physischen Schäden auf kurze Entfernung, durch den Ausdruck von Tapferkeit im Tanz. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10010	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_WARRIOR_B_DD_TT_DESC	투지가 넘치는 감정을 춤에 실어 근방에 파티원들의 사기를 올려주고 근거리 물리 데미지를 증가시킨다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Increases the morale of party members around by dancing with combative spirit, increasing the physical damage of short distance attacks. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Savaşçı ruhla dans edilmesiyle çevredeki parti üyelerinin moralini ve kısa menzilli fiziksel hasar gücünü yükseltir. Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Al bailar con un espíritu combativo, se levanta el ánimo de los miembros del grupo que se encuentren a tu alrededor y se incrementa el daño físico producido en los ataques a corta distancia. No se puede utilizar simultáneamente con otras habilidades; su efecto desaparecerá cuando te atacan. Si otro jugador interpreta la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	تزيد من معنويات أعضاء الفريق حولك بالرقص بروح قتالية وتزيد التدمير البدني للهجمات قصيرة المدى. ولا يمكنك استخدام هذه المهارة مع مهارة أخرى في نفس الوقت وسيختفي تأثيرها عندما يتم مهاجمتك. وعندما يعزف الآخرون الموسيقى ستعمل هذه المهارة فقط في نطاق تأثير الموسيقى.	Erhöht die Moral von Gruppenmitgliedern in der Nähe, wenn voller Kampfesgeist getanzt wird. Dadurch erhöht sich der physische Schaden bei Angriffen auf kurze Distanz. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10011	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_WARRIOR_C_DD_TT_DESC	전장의 승리를 기원하는 기도의 춤을 춰서 파티원들의 물리 데미지를 상승시키는 스킬이다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	It is a skill to dance for victory in the battle in order to increase the physical damage of party members. This skill  can't be used with other skills together. Once being attacked, its effect will disappear. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Bu, parti üyelerinin bedensel hasarını artırmak için savaş başarısını kutlayan bir oyundur. Bu beceri, diğer beceriler ile birlikte kullanılamaz. Saldırıldığında, etkisi kaybolacaktır. Bu beceri, diğerleri oynatılırken sadece oynatma etkisi aralığında kullanılabilir.	Es una destreza creada para bailar por la victoria en la batalla, con el fin de aumentar el poder de daño físico de los camaradas. Esta destreza no podrá ser usada junto a otras destrezas al mismo tiempo. Una vez atacado, sus efectos desaparecerán. Esta destreza solo podrá ser usada dentro del rango de alcance del efecto de juego, mientras otros estén jugando.	هي مهارة الرقص احتفالاً بالنصر في المعركة من أجل زيادة الضرر المادي لأفراد الفريق. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة مع المهارات الأخرى معًا، كما يختفي تأثيرها فور مهاجمتها. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة إلا ضمن نطاق تأثير العزف بينما يقوم الآخرون بالعزف.	Es ist die Fähigkeit den Tanz des Siegs auf dem Schlachtfeld zu tanzen, um den physischen Schaden der Gruppenmitglieder zu erhöhen.  Diese Fähigkeit kann nicht mit anderen Fähigkeiten zusammen verwendet werden.  Einmal angegriffen verschwindet seine Wirkung. Diese Fähigkeit kann nur im Bereich der Spieleffekte, während andere spielen, verwendet werden.
1	10012	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_CASTER_A_DD_TT_DESC	섬세한 감정의 변화를 실은 춤을 춰서 파티원들의 정신을 자극하여 마법 공격력을 증가시킨다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 타인이 연주 중일 때 연주의 효과가 미치는 범위에서만 사용할 수 있다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Stimulates party members' mentality to enhance their offensive magic power by expressing delicate emotional change in dance. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Dansta hafif bir duygusal değişim yaratarak ofansif büyü gücünü arttırmak üzere parti üyelerinin zihnini canlandırır. Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Expresando un delicado cambio emocional a través del baile, se estimula la mentalidad de los miembros del grupo para aumentar su poder ofensivo mágico. No puedes utilizar esta habilidad simultáneamente con otras. El efecto desaparece si sufres un ataque. Cuando otras personas interpretan la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	محاكاة أذهان أعضاء الفريق لتحسين قوتهم الهجومية السحرية  بالتعبير عن تغير المعازف المرهفة بالرقص. ولا يمكنك استخدام هذه المهارة مع مهارة أخرى في نفس الوقت وسيختفي تأثيرها عندما يتم مهاجمتك. وعندما يعزف الآخرون الموسيقى ستعمل هذه المهارة فقط في نطاق تأثير الموسيقى.	Regt die geistige Haltung der Gruppenmitglieder an, um deren Angriffskraft durch kleine gefühlsbetonte Veränderungen im Tanz zu stärken. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10013	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_CASTER_B_DD_TT_DESC	격한 감정의 기류를 실은 춤은 춤을 춰서 파티원들의 정신에 큰 자극을 주어 마법 공격력을 증가시킨다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Stimulating the mind of party members by dancing a with powerful emotional stream of air, increasing the damage of magical attacks. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Güçlü duygusal havayla dans ederek parti üyelerinin zihnini canlandırır, büyülü saldırıların hasarını arttırır.Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Estimula la mente de los miembros del grupo realizando un baile con un fuerte flujo de aire emocional, con lo que se incrementa el daño de los ataques mágicos. No se puede utilizar simultáneamente con otras habilidades. Su efecto desaparecerá cuando te atacan. Cuando otro jugador interpreta la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	محاكاة أذهان أعضاء الفريق برقص رقصة بها تدفق معازف قوي لتزيد من التدمير الذي تسببه الهجمات السحرية. ولا يمكنك استخدام هذه المهارة مع مهارة أخرى في نفس الوقت وسيختفي تأثيرها عندما يتم مهاجمتك. وعندما يعزف الآخرون الموسيقى ستعمل هذه المهارة فقط في نطاق تأثير الموسيقى	Regt den Geist der Gruppenmitglieder durch einen Tanz mit mächtigem emotionalem Luftstrom an. Das vermehrt den Schaden von magischen Angriffen. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10014	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_CASTER_C_DD_TT_DESC	마력의 기본인 원소의 힘을 끌어내는 춤을 춰서 파티원들의 마법 데미지를 상승시키는 스킬이다.
다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	It is a skill to dance for drawing the power of basic elements of magic so as to increase the magic damage of party members. This skill  can't be used with other skills together. Once being attacked, its effect will disappear. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Bu, parti üyelerinin sihir hasarını artırmak amacıyla sihrin temel bileşenlerinin gücünü çekmek için dans etme becerisidir. Bu beceri, diğer beceriler ile birlikte kullanılamaz. Saldırıldığında, etkisi kaybolacaktır. Bu beceri, diğerleri oynatılırken sadece oynatma etkisi aralığında kullanılabilir.	Es una destreza creada para bailar y atraer el poder de los elementos básicos de la magia, con el fin de aumentar el poder de daño mágico de los camaradas. Esta destreza no podrá ser usada junto a otras destrezas al mismo tiempo. Una vez atacado, sus efectos desaparecerán. Esta destreza solo podrá ser usada dentro del rango de alcance del efecto de juego, mientras otros estén jugando.	هي مهارة الرقص لسحب قوة العناصر الأساسية للسحر من أجل زيادة الضرر السحري لأفراد الفريق. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة مع المهارات الأخرى معًا، كما يختفي تأثيرها فور مهاجمتها. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة إلا ضمن نطاق تأثير العزف بينما يقوم الآخرون بالعزف.	Es ist eine Fähigkeit den Tanz für das Zeichen der Macht durch grundlegende Elemente durchzuführen, um den magischen Schaden der Gruppenmitglieder zu erhöhen.  Diese Fähigkeit kann nicht mit anderen Fähigkeiten zusammen verwendet werden. Einmal angegriffen verschwindet seine Wirkung. Diese Fähigkeit kann nur im Bereich der Spieleffekte, während andere spielen, verwendet werden.
1	10015	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_CLERIC_A_DD_TT_DESC	차분하고 절제된 감정의 춤을 춰서 근방에 있는 파티원들의 심신을 안정시키고 힐을 받았을 때 그 효과를 좋게 한다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Comforts party members' bodies and souls, and increases the effect of healing by expressing calm and oppressed emotions in dance. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Parti üyelerinin beden ve ruhlarını rahatlatır ve dansla sakin, sıkıştırılmış duyguları ifade ederek şifa etkisini arttırır. Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Reconforta a los miembros del grupo en cuerpo y alma; además, aumenta el efecto curativo expresando emociones reprimidas y tranquilidad en el baile. No puedes utilizar esta habilidad con otras simultáneamente. Su efecto desaparece cuando sufres un ataque. Cuando otro jugador interpreta la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	تريح أجسام أعضاء الفريق بالجوار عبر التعبير عن المشاعر الهادئة بالرقص لتزيد تأثير الشفاء. لا يمكن استعمال هذه المهارة في وقت واحد مع المهارات الأخرى وسيزول تأثيرها عند مهاجمتك. تعمل هذه المهارة فقط عندما تكون داخل نطاق تأثير عزف الموسيقى لعازف موسيقى آخر.	Tröstet die Körper von Mitgliedern und Seelen und erhöht die Heilwirkung durch den Ausdruck ruhiger und unterdrückter Gefühle in Tanz. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10016	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_CLERIC_B_DD_TT_DESC	평온하고 안정적인 감정을 춤으로 표현하여 근방에 있는 파티원들의 마음을 평정시키고 힐을 받았을 때 그 효과를 좋게 한다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Calms the mind of nearby party members through a dance with tranquil and stable emotion, increasing the effects of healing. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Sakin ve sabit duygulu bir dansla yakın çevredeki parti üyelerini sakinleştirir, şifa etkisini arttır.  Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Mediante un baile con emociones tranquilas y estables, calma la mente de los miembros del grupo que se encuentren cerca e incrementa sus efectos curativos. No puede ser usada simultáneamente con otras habilidades. Si eres atacado, se disipará su efecto. Cuando otro jugador interpreta la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	تريح عقول أعضاء الفريق بالجوار عبر الرقص الهادئ بالمشاعر المستقرة لتزيد تأثير الشفاء. لا يمكن استعمال هذه المهارة في وقت واحد مع المهارات الأخرى وسيزول تأثيرها عند مهاجمتك. تعمل هذه المهارة فقط عندما تكون داخل نطاق تأثير عزف الموسيقى لعازف موسيقى آخر.	Beruhigt den Geist der Gruppenmitglieder in der Nähe durch einen Tanz mit ruhigem und ausgeglichenem Gefühl. Hierdurch wird die Heilwirkung verstärkt. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10017	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_CLERIC_C_DD_TT_DESC	몸의 회복력을 끌어올리는 기적의 춤을 춰서 파티원들이 힐을 받았을 때 그 효과를 증가시키는 스킬이다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	It is a skill to perform dance of miracle for raising the resilience of the body so as to increase healing effect for party members. This skill  can't be used with other skills together. Once being attacked, its effect will disappear. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Bu, parti üyelerini iyileştirme etkisini artırmak üzere vücut elastikliğini artırmak için mucize dansı etme becerisidir. Bu beceri, diğer beceriler ile birlikte kullanılamaz. Saldırıldığında, etkisi kaybolacaktır. Bu beceri, diğerleri oynatılırken sadece oynatma etkisi aralığında kullanılabilir.	Es una destreza creada para llevar a cabo una danza milagrosa y así aumentar la capacidad de resistencia del cuerpo, a fin de aumentar el efecto de sanación de los camaradas. Esta destreza no podrá ser usada junto a otras destrezas al mismo tiempo. Una vez atacado, sus efectos desaparecerán. Esta destreza solo podrá ser usada dentro del rango de alcance del efecto de juego, mientras otros estén jugando.	هي مهارة أداء رقصة المعجزة لزيادة مرونة الجسم من أجل زيادة التأثير الشفائي لأفراد الفريق. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة مع المهارات الأخرى معًا، كما يختفي تأثيرها فور مهاجمتها. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة إلا ضمن نطاق تأثير العزف بينما يقوم الآخرون بالعزف.	Es ist eine Fähigkeit den Tanz der Wunder für die Erhöhung der Widerstandsfähigkeit des Körpers aufzuführen, um die heilende Wirkung für die Gruppenmitglieder zu erhöhen.  Diese Fähigkeit kann nicht mit anderen Fähigkeiten zusammen verwendet werden. Einmal angegriffen verschwindet seine Wirkung. Diese Fähigkeit kann nur im Bereich der Spieleffekte, während andere spielen, verwendet werden.
1	10018	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_ROG_A_DD_TT_DESC	삶의 활력을 춤으로 표현하여 파티원들의 기분을 밝게하고 MP를 사용할 때 MP 소모량을 감소시킨다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Brightens party members' feelings by expressing vitality of life in dance, and saves MP when using it. Cannot be used simultaneously with other skills, and the effect will disappear when attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Dansla hayatın canlılığını ifade ederek parti üyelerinin duygularını aydınlatır ve kullanımında MP biriktirir. Diğer yeteneklerle aynı anda kullanılamaz ve saldırıya uğranıldığında etki yok olur. Bu yetenek yalnızca başka bir oyuncunun çaldığı müziğin etkisine belli bir mesafedeyseniz işe yarar.	Ilumina los sentimientos del grupo expresando la energía de la vida en el baile; ahorrarás MP al hacer uso de esta habilidad. No puedes utilizar esta habilidad con otras simultáneamente. Su efecto desaparece cuando sufres un ataque. Cuando otro jugador interpreta la música, la habilidad sólo será efectiva si te encuentras dentro del alcance de su funcionamiento.	إسعاد أحاسيس أعضاء الفريق بالتعبير عن حيوية ونشاط الحياة بالرقص وتحتفظ بالسحر عند استخدامها. ولا يمكن استعمال هذه المهارة في وقت واحد مع المهارات الأخرى وسيزول تأثيرها عند مهاجمتك. تعمل هذه المهارة فقط عندما تكون داخل نطاق تأثير عزف الموسيقى لعازف موسيقى آخر.	Erhellt die Gemüter der Gruppenmitglieder, indem Lebenskraft im Tanz ausgedrückt wird. Das spart MP, wenn die Fähigkeit eingesetzt wird. Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten benutzt werden. Die Wirkung verschwindet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Diese Fähigkeit funktioniert nur, wenn du innerhalb der Reichweite der Musik eines anderen Spielers bist.
1	10019	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_ROG_B_DD_TT_DESC	삶의 기쁨을 춤으로 승화시켜 파티원들의 정신을 맑게 하여 MP를 사용할 때 MP 소모량을 감소시킨다. 다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The joy of life is transcended to a form of a dance.  This clears the minds of the team members, reducing the amount of MP spent. This skill cannot be overlapped with other skills and is dispelled if attacked. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Hayatın neşesi dansa bürünür. Parti üyelerinin zihinlerini arındırır, harcanan MP miktarını düşürür. Bu yetenek diğer yeteneklere yüklenilemez ve saldırıldığı zaman etkisini yitirir. Yetenekten faydalanan kişi yeteneğin etki alanı içinde olmalıdır.	El goce de la vida es trascendido para crear un baile, lo que libera las mentes de los miembros del equipo para reducir la cantidad del MP que se haya gastado. Esta habilidad no se puede usar con otras simultáneamente. Sus efectos desaparecen si eres atacado. Quien reciba el beneficio de la habilidad debe estar dentro del rango de su efecto.	لقد تجاوزت متعة الحياة إلى شكل من أشكال الرقص. وهذه العقول الصافية لأعضاء الفريق تقلل من كمية استنفاذ السحر.
ولا يمكن استعمال هذه المهارة في وقت واحد مع المهارات الأخرى وسيزول تأثيرها عند مهاجمتك. تعمل هذه المهارة فقط عندما تكون داخل نطاق تأثير عزف الموسيقى لعازف موسيقى آخر.	Die Freude des Lebens ist zu einer Form des Tanzes aufgestiegen.  Dies reinigt die Gemüter der Gruppenmitglieder, was den Betrag der ausgegeben MP verringert. Diese Fähigkeit kann nicht gleichzeitig mit anderen Fähigkeiten eingesetzt werden und endet, wenn du angegriffen wirst. Derjenige, dem die Fähigkeit zu Gute kommen soll, muss in Reichweite ihrer Wirkung sein.
1	10020	SN_SKILL_EU_BARD_DANCEA_ROG_C_DD_TT_DESC	정신 집중 능력을 향상시키는 마력의 춤을 춰서 파티원들의 MP 소모량을 감소시키는 스킬이다.
다른 스킬들과 중복해서 사용할 수 없고 공격 당하면 효과가 사라진다. 어썸 월드 스킬로 인해 효과가 반감 되어있다.	0	0	0	0	0	It is a skill to perform dance of magic for improving concentration so as to decrease MP consumption of party members. This skill  can't be used with other skills together. Once being attacked, its effect will disappear. The effect is halved due to the Awesome World Skill.	0	0	0	Bu, parti üyelerinin MP tüketimini azaltmak için konsantrasyonu iyileştirmek amacıyla sihir dansı etme becerisidir. Bu beceri, diğer beceriler ile birlikte kullanılamaz. Saldırıldığında, etkisi kaybolacaktır. Bu beceri, diğerleri oynatılırken sadece oynatma etkisi aralığında kullanılabilir.	Es una destreza creada para llevar a cabo una danza mágica para mejorar la concentración, y así disminuir el consumo de MP de los camaradas. Esta destreza no podrá ser usada junto a otras destrezas al mismo tiempo. Una vez atacado, sus efectos desaparecerán. Esta destreza solo podrá ser usada dentro del rango de alcance del efecto de juego, mientras otros estén jugando.	هي مهارة أداء رقصة السحر لتحسين التركيز من أجل خفض استهلاك نقاط MP لأفراد الفريق. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة مع المهارات الأخرى معًا، كما يختفي تأثيرها فور مهاجمتها. ولا يمكن استخدام هذه المهارة إلا ضمن نطاق تأثير العزف بينما يقوم الآخرون بالعزف.	Es ist eine Fähigkeit den Tanz der Magie zur Verbesserung der Konzentration durchzuführen, um den MP Verbrauch der Gruppenmitglieder zu verringern.  Diese Fähigkeit kann nicht mit anderen Fähigkeiten zusammen verwendet werden. Einmal angegriffen verschwindet seine Wirkung. Diese Fähigkeit kann nur im Bereich der Spieleffekte, während andere spielen, verwendet werden.
