1	1800	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_V	V (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	V (olay öğesi)	NULL	0	0
1	1801	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_A	A (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	A (olay öğesi)	NULL	0	0
1	1802	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_L	L (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	L (olay öğesi)	NULL	0	0
1	1803	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP20_M	체력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Bambu sağlık şapkası (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1804	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP20_F	체력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Bambu Sağlık Şapkası (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1805	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP30_M	체력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Bambu sağlık şapkası (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1806	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP30_F	체력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Bambu Sağlık Şapkası (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1807	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP40_M	체력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Güneşi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1808	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP40_F	체력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Güneşi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1809	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP50_M	체력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Güneşi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1810	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_HP50_F	체력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Güneşi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1811	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP20_M	마력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1812	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP20_F	마력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1813	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP30_M	마력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1814	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP30_F	마력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1815	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP40_M	마력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1816	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP40_F	마력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1817	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP50_M	마력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1818	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_MP50_F	마력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga Ülkesi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1819	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR1_M	완력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1820	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR1_F	완력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1821	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR2_M	완력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1822	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR2_F	완력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1823	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR3_M	완력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1824	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR3_F	완력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1825	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR2_2_M	완력의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1826	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_STR2_2_F	완력의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın Karı (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1827	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT1_M	지혜의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1828	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT1_F	지혜의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1829	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT2_M	지혜의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1830	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT2_F	지혜의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1831	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT3_M	지혜의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1832	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT3_F	지혜의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1833	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT2_2_M	지혜의 방갓 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1834	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_SATGAT_INT2_2_F	지혜의 방갓 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Banga'nın derin denizi (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1835	SN_ITEM_ETC_TAIWAN_50000_GOLD	5만골드	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	50000 Altın	0	0	0
1	1836	SN_ITEM_ETC_E0600901_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_STAR	별문양	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Yıldız	NULL	0	0
1	1837	SN_ITEM_ETC_E0600901_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_RED_FABRIC	붉은 천조각	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Kırmızı Kumaş	NULL	0	0
1	1838	SN_ITEM_ETC_E0600901_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_STAFF	깃대	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Demir Asa	NULL	0	0
1	1839	SN_ITEM_ETC_E0600901_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_YELLOWSTARFLAG	별문양 깃발	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Altın Yıldız Bayrağı	NULL	0	0
1	1840	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060927_SONGPYON	맛있는 송편	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Lezzetli pirinç keki	NULL	0	0
1	1841	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070214_REDPIG	빨간 복 돼지	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Kırmızı domuz	NULL	0	0
1	1842	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070214_YELLOWPIG	노란 복 돼지	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Sarı Domuz	NULL	0	0
1	1843	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070214_BLUEPIG	파란 복 돼지	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Mavi Domuz	NULL	0	0
1	1844	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070214_BLACKPIG	검정 복 돼지	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Siyah Domuz	NULL	0	0
1	1845	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070523_LEFT_HEART	사랑의 증표(왼쪽)	0	0	0	0	0	Pledge of Love(Left)	0	0	0	Pledge of Love(Left)	Pledge of Love(Left)	Pledge of Love(Left)	Pledge of Love(Left)
1	1846	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070523_RIGHT_HEART	사랑의 증표(오른쪽)	0	0	0	0	0	Pledge of Love(Right)	0	0	0	Pledge of Love(Right)	Pledge of Love(Right)	Pledge of Love(Right)	Pledge of Love(Right)
1	1847	SN_ITEM_ETC_E071225_SANTASOCKS	빨간 산타 양말	0	0	0	0	0	Red Santa Socks	0	0	0	Red Santa Socks	Red Santa Socks	Red Santa Socks	Red Santa Socks
1	1848	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SUMMER_S	S (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	S (Event Item)	0	0	0	S (etkinlik eşyası)	S (Event Item)	S (أداة في مناسبة)	S (Event Item)
1	1849	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SUMMER_U	U (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	U (Event Item)	0	0	0	U (etkinlik eşyası)	U (Event Item)	U (أداة في مناسبة)	U (Event Item)
1	1850	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SUMMER_M_1	M (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	M (Event Item)	0	0	0	M (etkinlik eşyası)	M (Event Item)	M (أداة في مناسبة)	M (Event Item)
1	1851	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SUMMER_M_2	M (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	M (Event Item)	0	0	0	M (etkinlik eşyası)	M (Event Item)	M (أداة في مناسبة)	M (Event Item)
1	1852	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SUMMER_E	E (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	E (Event Item)	0	0	0	E (etkinlik eşyası)	E (Event Item)	E (أداة في مناسبة)	E (Event Item)
1	1853	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SUMMER_R	R (이벤트 아이템)	0	0	0	0	0	R (Event Item)	0	0	0	R (etkinlik eşyası)	R (Event Item)	R (أداة في مناسبة)	R (Event Item)
1	1854	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_MENTAL_SCROLL	지능의 두루마리	0	0	0	0	0	Intelligence Scroll	0	0	0	Intelligence Scroll	Intelligence Scroll	Scroll الذكاء	Intelligence Scroll
1	1855	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_STRENGTH_SCROLL	완력의 두루마리	0	0	0	0	0	Strength Scroll	0	0	0	Strength Scroll	Strength Scroll	Scroll القوة	Strength Scroll
1	1856	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_HP_1000	진짜 시원한 빙수	0	0	0	0	0	Very Cold Ice Flakes	0	0	0	Very Cold Ice Flakes	Very Cold Ice Flakes	Very Cold Ice Flakes	Very Cold Ice Flakes
1	1857	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_MP_1000	시원한 빙수	0	0	0	0	0	Cold Ice Flakes	0	0	0	Cold Ice Flakes	Cold Ice Flakes	Cold Ice Flakes	Cold Ice Flakes
1	1858	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_HPMP_1000	꽁꽁 얼은 빙수	0	0	0	0	0	Frozen Ice Flakes	0	0	0	Frozen Ice Flakes	Frozen Ice Flakes	Frozen Ice Flakes	Frozen Ice Flakes
1	1859	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050715_ICEDVERMICELLI_FROZEN	꽁꽁 얼은 냉면	0	0	0	0	0	Frozen Noodles	0	0	0	Frozen Noodles	Frozen Noodles	Frozen Noodles	Frozen Noodles
1	1860	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_HWAN_POTION	환 재생 물약	0	0	0	0	0	Berserker Regeneration Potion	0	0	0	Berserker Regeneration Potion	Berserker Regeneration Potion	Berserker Regeneration Potion	Berserker Regeneration Potion
1	1861	SN_ITEM_ETC_HWAN_POTION_JAPAN	환 재생 물약 (개정판)	0	0	0	0	0	Berserker Regeneration Potion	0	0	0	Berserker Regeneration Potion	Berserker Regeneration Potion	Berserker Regeneration Potion	Berserker Regeneration Potion
1	1862	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SKILL_EXP_20	스킬 경험치 20% 증가 주문서	0	0	0	0	0	20% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	0	0	0	20% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	20% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	20% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	20% Skill Exp Increase Scroll
1	1863	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SKILL_EXP_15	스킬 경험치 15% 증가 주문서	0	0	0	0	0	15% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	0	0	0	15% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	15% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	15% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	15% Skill Exp Increase Scroll
1	1864	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SKILL_EXP_10	스킬 경험치 10% 증가 주문서	0	0	0	0	0	10% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	0	0	0	10% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	10% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	10% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	10% Skill Exp Increase Scroll
1	1865	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SKILL_EXP_5	스킬 경험치 5% 증가 주문서	0	0	0	0	0	5% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	0	0	0	5% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	5% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	5% Skill Exp Increase Scroll	5% Skill Exp Increase Scroll
1	1866	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_EXP_5	경험치 5% 증가 주문서	0	0	0	0	0	5% Exp Increase Scroll	0	0	0	5% Exp Increase Scroll	5% Exp Increase Scroll	5% Exp Increase Scroll	5% Exp Increase Scroll
1	1867	SN_ITEM_ETC_BALLOON_MANGNYANG	망량 풍선	0	0	0	0	0	Mangnyang Balloon	0	0	0	Mangnyang Balloon	Mangnyang Balloon	Mangnyang Balloon	Mangyang Balloon
1	1868	SN_ITEM_ETC_BALLOON_MOVOI	모보이 풍선	0	0	0	0	0	Movoi Balloon	0	0	0	Movoi Balloon	Movoi Balloon	Movoi Balloon	Movoi Balloon
1	1869	SN_ITEM_EVENT_E081126_SILKROAD_PLAG_M	실사모 휘장 (남)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Kara Haydut Bayrağı (M)	NULL	0	0
1	1870	SN_ITEM_EVENT_E081126_SILKROAD_PLAG_W	실사모 휘장 (여)	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Kara Haydut Bayrağı (F)	NULL	0	0
1	1871	SN_ITEM_ETC_E081217_SANTAGIFTBOX	산타의 선물상자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Noel Baba hediye kutusu	NULL	0	0
1	1872	SN_ITEM_ETC_HP_POTION_02_BASIC	초보자의 HP 회복약(소)	0	0	0	0	0	Beginner's HP potion(small)	0	0	0	Beginner's HP potion(small)	Beginner's HP potion(small)	Beginner's HP potion(small)	Beginner's HP potion(small)
1	1873	SN_ITEM_ETC_MP_POTION_02_BASIC	초보자의 MP 회복약(소)	0	0	0	0	0	Beginner's MP potion(small)	0	0	0	Beginner's MP potion(small)	Beginner's MP potion(small)	Beginner's MP potion(small)	Beginner's MP potion(small)
1	1874	SN_ITEM_ETC_ARCHEMY_MAGICSTONE_STR_05_BASIC	초보자의 완력의 연금석(5차)	0	0	0	0	0	Magic stone of Str (Lvl.5)	0	0	0	Magic stone of Str (Lvl.5)	Magic stone of Str (Lvl.5)	Magic stone of Str (Lvl.5)	Magic stone of Str (Lvl.5)
1	1875	SN_ITEM_ETC_ARCHEMY_MAGICSTONE_INT_05_BASIC	초보자의 지혜의 연금석(5차)	0	0	0	0	0	Magic stone of Int (Lvl.5)	0	0	0	Magic stone of Int (Lvl.5)	Magic stone of Int (Lvl.5)	Magic stone of Int (Lvl.5)	Magic stone of Int (Lvl.5)
1	1876	SN_ITEM_ETC_STATS_POINT_RECALL_50LV_BASIC	초보자의 스탯 회수약(41~50)	0	0	0	0	0	Biginner's Stat reset potion (41~50)	0	0	0	Biginner's Stat reset potion (41~50)	Biginner's Stat reset potion (41~50)	Biginner's Stat reset potion (41~50)	Biginner's Stat reset potion (41~50)
1	1877	SN_ITEM_QEV_ALL_BASIC2_6	돈황석굴 정화의 깃발	0	0	0	0	0	Purification flag of Donwhang	0	0	0	Purification flag of Donwhang	Purification flag of Donwhang	Purification flag of Donwhang	Purification flag of Donwhang
1	1878	SN_ITEM_ETC_GLOBAL_CHATTING_BASIC	초보자의 전체채팅	0	0	0	0	0	Beginner Global Chat	0	0	0	Beginner Global Chat	Beginner Global Chat	Beginner Global Chat	Beginner Global Chat
1	1879	SN_ITEM_ETC_SCROLL_RETURN_03_BASIC	초보자의 순간 귀환서	0	0	0	0	0	Beginner instant recall scroll	0	0	0	Beginner instant recall scroll	Beginner instant recall scroll	Beginner instant recall scroll	Beginner instant recall scroll
1	1880	SN_ITEM_ETC_E080723_SKILL_EXP_10_BASIC	초보자의 스킬경험치 10% 증가 주문서	0	0	0	0	0	Beginner 10% Exp Increase Scroll	0	0	0	Beginner 10% Exp Increase Scroll	Beginner 10% Exp Increase Scroll	Beginner 10% Exp Increase Scroll	Beginner 10% Exp Increase Scroll
1	1881	SN_ITEM_EVENT_ASTRAL	아스트랄의 연금석	0	0	0	0	0	Magic stone of Astral	0	0	0	Magic stone of Astral	Magic stone of Astral	Magic stone of Astral	Magic stone of Astral
1	1882	SN_ITEM_EVENT_CANDY	화이트데이 보석 상자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	Şeker	0	0	0
1	1883	SN_ITEM_ETC_E041225_RED_SOCKS_TT_DESC	산타가 잃어버린 양말!\n각 마을에 있는 예쁜 산타에게 꼭! 가져다주자.	0	0	0	0	0	The socks that Santa has lost!\nMake sure to bring it to the pretty Santa in each town.	0	0	0	Santa'nın kaybettiği çoraplar!\n Her bir kasabadaki güzel Santaya verdiğinden emin ol.	¡Los calcetines que Santa perdió!\nAsegúrate de llevarlos al Santa bonito en cada pueblo.	الجوارب التي فقدها Santa ! تأكد من إحضارها إلى Santa  الجميل في كل مدينة.	Die Socken, die der Weihnachtsmann verloren hat!\nBring sie schnell zum Weihnachtsmann in jeder Stadt.
1	1884	SN_ITEM_ETC_E041225_SANTA_WINGS_TT_DESC	산타의 마력으로 마을까지 순간적으로 귀환할 수 있도록 도와준다.\n귀환하는데 5초가 걸린다.	0	0	0	0	0	Can be teleported to the town instantly with the help of Santa's magic.\nIt takes 5 seconds.	0	0	0	Santa'nın büyüsünün yardımıyla kasabaya anında ışınlanılır.\nIt 5 dakika sürer.	Puedes teletransportarte al pueblo instantáneamente con la ayuda de la magia de Santa.\nToma 5 segundos.	يمكنك بمساعدة سحر Santa  الانتقال إلى المدينة في الحال. تأخذ 5 ثوان.	Kann mithilfe vom Weihnachtsmannzauber sofort in die Stadt teleportiert werden.\nDauert 5 Sekunden.
1	1885	SN_ITEM_ETC_E041225_SANTA_HAT_M_TT_DESC	산타가 쓰고 다니는 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The hat that Santa wears has no special ability./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santa'nın giydiği şapkanın özel bir yeteneği yok./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	El gorro que Santa utiliza no tiene habilidades especiales./n Puede ser colocado en un espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	القبعة التي يرتديها Santa  وليست لها قدرات مميزة /n
يمكن وضعها في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhut hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1886	SN_ITEM_ETC_E041225_SANTA_HAT_F_TT_DESC	산타가 쓰고 다니는 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The hat that Santa wears has no special ability./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santa'nın giydiği şapkanın özel bir yeteneği yok./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	El gorro que Santa utiliza no tiene habilidades especiales./n Puede ser colocado en un espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	القبعة التي يرتديها Santa  وليست لها قدرات مميزة /n
يمكن وضعها في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhut hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1887	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_M_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'un kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1888	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_M_BLUE_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'uni kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1889	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_M_RED_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'un kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1890	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_M_BLACK_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'uni kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1891	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_W_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'un kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1892	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_W_BLUE_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'un kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1893	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_W_RED_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'un kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1894	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050526_W_BLACK_EGHEAD_TT_DESC	토귀의 머리로 만든 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	The helmet made from an Earth Ghost's head that has no special power.\nEquippable into the avatar slot.	0	0	0	Earth Ghost'un kafasından yapılmış, özel bir gücü olmayan helmet.\n avatar slota giyilebilir.	El casco hecho con la cabeza del Earth Ghost que no tiene poderes especiales.\nUbícable  en el espacio de avatar.	الخوذة المصنوعة من رأس Earth Ghost's وليست لها أي قوى مميزة. يمكن التزود بها في موضع الحلة.	Der Helm wurde aus dem Kopf eines Earth Ghost gemacht und hat keine besondere Kraft.\nPasst in den Avatar-Slot.
1	1895	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050618_TREASUREBOX_TT_DESC	신기한 선물상자.\nNPC 소옥에게 갖다주자.	0	0	0	0	0	Marvelous Jewel Box. Let's bring it to So-Ok.	0	0	0	Harika bir Jewel Box. Hadi onu So-ok'a ver.	Maravilloso Jewel Box. Llevémoslo a So-Ok.	Jewel Boxالرائع. دعنا نأتي بهاه إلى So-Ok.	Wunderbare Jewel Box. Bringen wir sie zu So-Ok.
1	1896	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050715_ICEDVERMICELLI_VERYCOOL_TT_DESC	진짜 시원해 보이는 냉면이다. 무언가 특별한 효과가 있을 것 같다. 냉면을 먹고 여름을 극복하자.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>good iced noodles<br>the iced noodles looks tasty. and  it seems to have some special effects. lets eat it and forget the heat of summer.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">effect</font></strong><br>increases maximum hp by 500 for 1 hour.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>good iced noodles<br>iced noodles lezzetli görünüyor. Özel bir etki yaratacağa benziyor. Hadi yiyelim ve yaz sıcağını unutalım.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">effect</font></strong><br>Maksimum HP'yi bir saatliğine 500'e çıkarır.</sml2>	<sml2>Good Iced Noodles<br>Estos tallarines helados se ven deliciosos y parece que tienen algunos efectos. Vamos a comerlos y olvidar el calor del verano.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Efecto</font></strong><br>Incrementa el máximo HP por 500 durante 1 hora.</sml2>	<sml2>شعرية مثلجة جيدة<br>الشعرية المثلجة طعمها جيد. وتبدو أن لها بعض التأثيرات الخاصة. دعنا نأكلها وننسى حرارة  الصيف<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">التأثير</font></strong><br>تزيد الصحة القصوى بـ 500 نقطة لدة 1 ساعة.</sml2>	<sml2>Gute Iced Noodles<br>Die Iced Noodles sehen lecker aus. Sie scheinen ein paar besondere Effekte zu haben. Essen wir sie und vergessen wir die Sommerhitze.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Effekt</font></strong><br>Erhöht die Maximal-HP für 1 Stunde um 500.</sml2>
1	1897	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050715_ICEDVERMICELLI_COOL_TT_DESC	시원해 보이는 냉면이다. 일단 먹고 보자. 무슨 효과가 있을지도…	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>iced noodles<br>the iced nooldes looks cool. lets have it anyway. who knows if it has some effects…<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">effect</font></strong><br>increases maximum mp by 500 for 1 hour.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>iced noodles<br>iced noodles mükemmel görünüyor. Hadi ne olursa olsun alalım. Etkileri olduğunu kim bilebilir ki.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">effect</font></strong><br>Maksimum HP'yi bir saatliğine 500'e çıkarır.</sml2>	<sml2>Iced Noodles<br>Estos tallarines helados se ven más bien fríos. Comámoslos de igual manera, tal vez tengan algún efecto.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Efecto</font></strong><br>Incrementa el máximo MP por 500 durante 1 hora.</sml2>	<sml2>شعرية مثلجة <br>الشعرية المثلجة تبدو رائعة. دعنا نأكلها على آية حال. من يعرف إذا كان بها بعض التأثيرات ...<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">التأثير</font></strong><br>تزيد الصحة القصوى بـ 500 نقطة لدة 1 ساعة.</sml2>	<sml2>Iced Noodles<br>Die Iced Noodles sehen kalt aus. Essen wir sie einfach. Wer weiß, vielleicht haben sie Effekte…<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Effekt</font></strong><br>Erhöht die Maximal-MP für 1 Stunde um 500.</sml2>
1	1898	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050715_ICEDVERMICELLI_TEPID_TT_DESC	미지근한 냉면이다. 시간이 지나버려 미지근해진 것 같다. 하지만 먹어보자…	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>Tepid iced noodles<br>Tepid iced noodles. It became tepid because time had passed. But lets have it….</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Tepid iced noodles<br>Tepid iced noodles. Zaman geçtikçe ılık bir hale gelmiş. Yine de hadi alalım….</sml2>	<sml2>Tepid Iced Noodles<br>Estos tallarines se pusieron tibios debido a que ha transcurrido tiempo. Comámoslos..</sml2>	<sml2>الشعرية المثلجة الفاترة<br>الشعرية المثلجة تصبح فاترة بمرور الوقت. ولكن دعنا نأكلها….</sml2>	<sml2>Tepid iced noodles<br>Tepid iced noodles. Sie wurden lauwarm, weil die Zeit verging. Aber essen wir sie...</sml2>
1	1899	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050729_SUMMON_SCROLL_TT_DESC	<sml2>주문서에 알 수 없는 글들이 기록되어있다. 이 주문을 외우면 강한 몬스터가 나타난다고 한다. 혹시 모르니 철저한 준비를 하고 오른쪽 마우스 버튼을 눌러 사용해보자.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용가능레벨: 10 레벨이상</font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용조건: 1인이거나 경험치/아이템 균등분배</font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>This is a summoning scroll covered with unreadable letters. If you use this a powerfully dangerous monster will appear.<br>
*The summoned monster will disappear after 5 minutes.<br><br>
Eligible Levels: Lvl.10 and up</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Bu, okunamayan harflerle kaplı bir summoning scroll. Bunu kullanırsan, tehlikeli canavarlar ortaya çıkacaktır.<br>*Çağrılan canavarlar 5 dakika sonra gözden kaybolacaktır.<br><br>
Uygun Seviyeler: Seviye 10 ve yukarısı</sml2>	<sml2>Este es un Summoning Scroll cubierto con letras ilegibles. Si lo utilizas, aparecerá un fuerte y peligroso monstruo.<br>*El monstruo invocado desaparece después de 5 minutos.<br><br>Niveles Elegibles: Nivel 10 y superior a 10</sml2>	<sml2>هذه رسالة استدعاء مغطاه بحروف غير مقروءة. إذا قمت باستخدامها فستظهر لك الوحوش القوية الخطيرة <br>
*ستختفي الوحوش المستدعاة بعد 5 دقائق<br><br>
المستويات المؤهلة: مستوى 10 فأعلى</sml2>	<sml2>Das ist eine Summon Scroll, bedeckt mit unlesbaren Zeichen. Wenn du sie benutzt, wird ein sehr gefährliches Monster erscheinen.<br>
*Das gerufene Monster wird nach 5 Minuten verschwinden.<br><br>
Geeignete Level: Lvl.10 und höher</sml2>
1	1900	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050729_SUMMON_ONE_SCROLL_TT_DESC	<sml2>주문서에 알 수 없는 글들이 기록되어있다. 이 주문을 외우면 강한 몬스터가 나타난다고 한다. 혹시 모르니 철저한 준비를 하고 오른쪽 마우스 버튼을 눌러 사용해보자.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용가능레벨: 10 레벨이상</font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>This is a summoning scroll covered with unreadable letters. If you use this a powerfully dangerous monster will appear.<br>
*The summoned monster will disappear after 5 minutes.<br><br>
Eligible Levels: Lvl.10 and up</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Bu, okunamayan harflerle kaplı bir summoning scroll. Bunu kullanırsan, tehlikeli canavarlar ortaya çıkacaktır.<br>*Çağrılan canavarlar 5 dakika sonra gözden kaybolacaktır.<br><br>
Uygun Seviyeler: Seviye 10 ve yukarısı</sml2>	<sml2>Este es un Summoning Scroll cubierto con letras ilegibles. Si lo utilizas, aparecerá un fuerte y peligroso monstruo.<br>*El monstruo invocado desaparece después de 5 minutos.<br><br>Niveles Elegibles: Nivel 10 y superior a 10</sml2>	<sml2>هذه رسالة استدعاء مغطاه بحروف غير مقروءة. إذا قمت باستخدامها فستظهر لك الوحوش القوية الخطيرة <br>
*ستختفي الوحوش المستدعاة بعد 5 دقائق<br><br>
المستويات المؤهلة: مستوى 10 فأعلى</sml2>	<sml2>Das ist eine Summon Scroll, bedeckt mit unlesbaren Zeichen. Wenn du sie benutzt, wird ein sehr gefährliches Monster erscheinen.<br>
*Das gerufene Monster wird nach 5 Minuten verschwinden.<br><br>
Geeignete Level: Lvl.10 und höher</sml2>
1	1901	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050729_SUMMON_TWO_SCROLL_TT_DESC	<sml2>주문서에 알 수 없는 글들이 기록되어있다. 이 주문을 외우면 강한 몬스터가 나타난다고 한다. 혹시 모르니 철저한 준비를 하고 오른쪽 마우스 버튼을 눌러 사용해보자.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용가능레벨: 10 레벨이상</font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용조건: 경험치/아이템 균등분배파티에서 2인일 경우만 사용가능</font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>This is a summoning scroll covered with unreadable letters. If you use this a powerfully dangerous monster will appear.<br>
*The summoned monster will disappear after 5 minutes.<br><br>
Eligible Levels: Lvl.10 and up</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Bu, okunamayan harflerle kaplı bir summoning scrolli. Bunu kullanırsan, tehlikeli canavarlar ortaya çıkacaktır.<br>*Çağrılan canavarlar 5 dakika sonra gözden kaybolacaktır.<br><br>
Uygun Seviyeler: Seviye 10 ve yukarısı</sml2>	<sml2>Este es un Summoning Scroll cubierto con letras ilegibles. Si lo utilizas, aparecerá un fuerte y peligroso monstruo.<br>*El monstruo invocado desaparece después de 5 minutos.<br><br>Niveles Elegibles: Nivel 10 y superior a 10</sml2>	<sml2>هذه رسالة استدعاء مغطاه بحروف غير مقروءة. إذا قمت باستخدامها فستظهر لك الوحوش القوية الخطيرة <br>
*ستختفي الوحوش المستدعاة بعد 5 دقائق<br><br>
المستويات المؤهلة: مستوى 10 فأعلى</sml2>	<sml2>Das ist eine Summon Scroll, bedeckt mit unlesbaren Zeichen. Wenn du sie benutzt, wird ein sehr gefährliches Monster erscheinen.<br>
*Das gerufene Monster wird nach 5 Minuten verschwinden.<br><br>
Geeignete Level: Lvl.10 und höher</sml2>
1	1902	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_FABRIC_TT_DESC	천조각이다. 조금 지저분하긴 하지만, 잘 빨면 쓸만할 것 같다. 소옥이가 필요하다고 한 것 같으니 갖다 주자.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>a piece of cloth<br>a piece of cloth. looks a bit dirty but seems to be ok if washed. lets bring it to so-ok because she seems to need it.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Bir kumaş parçası<br>bir kumaş parçası. Biraz kirli görünüyor ancak yıkanırsa iyi gözükecek. Hadi onu So-ok'a götür çünkü ona ihtiyacı var gibi görünüyor.</sml2>	<sml2>A piece of cloth<br>Una pieza de tela. Se ve un poco sucia pero parece que se verá buena si se lava. Llevémosla a So-Ok; parece que ella la necesita.</sml2>	<sml2>قطعة نسيج<br>قطعة نسيج تبدو متسخة قليلاً ولكن يبدو أنها ستصبح جيدة عند غسلها. دعنا نأخذها إلى سو - لأنها تبدو أنها بحاجة إليها</sml2>	<sml2>Ein Stück Stoff<br>Ein Stück Stoff. Es sieht etwas schmutzig aus, ist aber sicher ok, wenn es gewaschen ist. Bringen wir es So-Ok, weil sie es zu brauchen scheint.</sml2>
1	1903	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_FLAGPLE_TT_DESC	착지가 들고 있는 창을 잘 다듬어 만든 깃대. 매우 튼튼해 보인다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>solid pole<br>a flag pole made by refining the spear chakji had hold. it looks very solid.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>solid pole<br>Chakji'nin taşıdığı mızrak düzeltilerek yapılan bir flag pole. Çok sağlam gözüküyor.</sml2>	<sml2>Solid Pole<br>Un asta de bandera hecha al refinar la jabalina que sostuvo Chakji. Se ve muy sólida.</sml2>	<sml2>سارية صلبة<br>سارية العلم صنعها صاقل الرماح شاكجي. وهي تبدو صلبة جداً</sml2>	<sml2>Fester Mast<br>Ein Flaggenmast, der aus dem veredelten Speer gemacht wurde, den Chakji hielt. Er sieht sehr fest aus.</sml2>
1	1904	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_KOREAFLAG_M_TT_DESC	태극문양과 건곤이감 4괘가 그려진 태극기. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuki<br>taegeuki with taegeuk circle and four signs of geon, gon, i, gam.. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuki<br>taegeuk çemberi ve geon, gon, i, gam'ın dört işaretiyle taegeuki... job slot'un eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki con círculo Taegeuk y cuatro signos de geon, gon, i, gam. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2>تايوجيوكي<br>taegeuki مع دائرة taegeuki وأربعة علمات جيون و جون و جام ويمكن استخدامها عند وضعها في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki mit Taegeuk-Kreis und vier Zeichen von Geon, Gon, I, Gam.. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1905	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_GOLDKOREAFLAG_M_TT_DESC	태극문양과 건곤이감 4괘가 그려진 태극기. 태극기 주변으로 멋진 황금색 자수가 새겨져 있어 저 고급스럽게 보인다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>golden embroidered taegeuki<br>taegeukiwith taegeuk circle and four signs of geon, gon, i, gam. it is nicely golden embroidered around the edge. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>altın işlemeli taegeuki<br>taegeuk çemberi ve geon, gon, i, gam'ın dört işaretiyle taegeuki. Kenarındaki altın işlemeler güzel. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Golden Embroidered Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki con circulo Taegeuk y cuatro signos de geon, gon, i, gam. Tiene una hermosa costura dorada alrededor del borde. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2>taegeuki مطرزة بالذهب<br>taegeuki مع دائرة taegeuki وأربعة علمات جيون و جون و جام وبها تطريز ذهبي أنيق حول حافتها. ويمكن استخدامها عند وضعها في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Golddurchwirkter Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki mit Taegeuk-Kreis und vier Zeichen von Geon, Gon, I, Gam. Er ist an den Rändern mit Gold durchwirkt. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1906	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_TAEGUKBUNTING_M_TT_DESC	거대한 태극기가 걸려있는 휘장이다. 웅장한 모습이 그 가치를 더하고 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk curtain<br>a huge curtain on which the taegeuki is hanged. its magnificent view adds the value to it. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk curtain<br>üzerinde taegeukinin asılı durduğu büyük bir curtain. İhtişamlı görüntüsü ona değer katıyor. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuk Courtain<br>Una gran cortina para colgar el Taegeuki. Su magnífica vista le da valor. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2> غطاء ايوجيوكي<br>غطاء كبير يعلقه taegeuki. منظرها رائع وقيمتها عالية. ويمكن استخدامه عند وضعه في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuk-Vorhang<br>Ein großer Vorhang, auf den der Taegeuki gehängt wird. Sein fantastisches Aussehen macht seinen Wert aus. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1907	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_KOREAFLAG_F_TT_DESC	태극문양과 건곤이감 4괘가 그려진 태극기. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk flag<br>taegeuki with taegeuk circle and four signs of geon, gon, i, gam.. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk flag<br>taegeuk çemberi ve geon, gon, i, gam'ın dört işaretiyle taegeuki... Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki con círculo Taegeuk y cuatro signos de geon, gon, i, gam. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2>علم تايوجيوكي<br>taegeuki مع دائرة taegeuki وأربعة علمات جيون و جون و جام ويمكن استخدامها عند وضعها في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuki-Flagge<br>Taegeuki mit Taegeuk-Kreis und vier Zeichen von Geon, Gon, I, Gam.. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1908	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_GOLDKOREAFLAG_F_TT_DESC	태극문양과 건곤이감 4괘가 그려진 태극기. 태극기 주변으로 멋진 황금색 자수가 새겨져 있어 저 고급스럽게 보인다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>golden embroidered taegeuki<br>taegeuki with taegeuk circle and four signs of geon, gon, i, gam. it is nicely golden embroidered around the edge. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>altın işlemeli taegeuki<br>taegeuk çemberi ve geon, gon, i, gam'ın dört işaretiyle taegeuki. Kenarındaki altın işlemeler güzel. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Golden Embroidered Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki con circulo Taegeuk y cuatro signos de geon, gon, i, gam. Tiene una hermosa costura dorada alrededor del borde. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2>taegeuki مطرزة بالذهب<br>taegeuki مع دائرة taegeuki وأربعة علمات جيون و جون و جام وبها تطريز ذهبي أنيق حول حافتها. ويمكن استخدامها عند وضعها في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Golddurchwirkter Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki mit Taegeuk-Kreis und vier Zeichen von Geon, Gon, I, Gam. Er ist an den Rändern mit Gold durchwirkt. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1909	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050815_TAEGUKBUNTING_F_TT_DESC	거대한 태극기가 걸려있는 휘장이다. 웅장한 모습이 그 가치를 더하고 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk curtain<br>a huge curtain on which the taegeuki is hanged. its magnificent view adds the value to it. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk curtain<br>üzerinde taegeukinin asılı durduğu büyük bir curtain. İhtişamlı görüntüsü ona değer katıyor. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuk Courtain<br>Una gran cortina para colgar el Taegeuki. Su magnífica vista le da valor. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2> غطاء ايوجيوكي<br>غطاء كبير يعلقه taegeuki. منظرها رائع وقيمتها عالية. ويمكن استخدامه عند وضعه في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuk-Vorhang<br>Ein großer Vorhang, auf den der Taegeuki gehängt wird. Sein fantastisches Aussehen macht seinen Wert aus. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1910	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070807_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_YELLOWSTARFLAG_TT_DESC	베트남 깃발	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk flag<br>taegeuki with taegeuk circle and four signs of geon, gon, i, gam.. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk flag<br>taegeuk çemberi ve geon, gon, i, gam'ın dört işaretiyle taegeuki... Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuki flag<br>Taegeuki con círculo Taegeuk y cuatro signos de geon, gon, i, gam. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2>علم تايوجيوكي<br>taegeuki مع دائرة taegeuki وأربعة علمات جيون و جون و جام ويمكن استخدامها عند وضعها في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuki-Flagge<br>Taegeuki mit Taegeuk-Kreis und vier Zeichen von Geon, Gon, I, Gam.. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1911	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070807_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_YELLOWSTARGOLDFLAG_TT_DESC	황금자수 베트남기	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>golden embroidered taegeuki<br>taegeuki with taegeuk circle and four signs of geon, gon, i, gam. it is nicely golden embroidered around the edge. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>altın işlemeli taegeuki<br>taegeuk çemberi ve geon, gon, i, gam'ın dört işaretiyle taegeuki. Kenarındaki altın işlemeler güzel. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Golden Embroidered Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki con circulo Taegeuk y cuatro signos de geon, gon, i, gam. Tiene una hermosa costura dorada alrededor del borde. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2>taegeuki مطرزة بالذهب<br>taegeuki مع دائرة taegeuki وأربعة علمات جيون و جون و جام وبها تطريز ذهبي أنيق حول حافتها. ويمكن استخدامها عند وضعها في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Golddurchwirkter Taegeuki<br>Taegeuki mit Taegeuk-Kreis und vier Zeichen von Geon, Gon, I, Gam. Er ist an den Rändern mit Gold durchwirkt. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1912	SN_ITEM_ETC_E070807_INDEPENDENCE_DAY_VIETNAMBUNTING_TT_DESC	별문양 베트남 휘장	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk curtain<br>a huge curtain on which the taegeuki is hanged. its magnificent view adds the value to it. usable if equipped into the job slot.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>taegeuk curtain<br>üzerinde taegeukinin asılı durduğu büyük bir curtain. İhtişamlı görüntüsü ona değer katıyor. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuk Courtain<br>Una gran cortina para colgar el Taegeuki. Su magnífica vista le da valor. Se puede usar si  se coloca en el espacio de trabajo.</sml2>	<sml2> غطاء ايوجيوكي<br>غطاء كبير يعلقه taegeuki. منظرها رائع وقيمتها عالية. ويمكن استخدامه عند وضعه في موضع المهنة</sml2>	<sml2>Taegeuk-Vorhang<br>Ein großer Vorhang, auf den der Taegeuki gehängt wird. Sein fantastisches Aussehen macht seinen Wert aus. Benutzbar, wenn im Job-Slot abgelegt.</sml2>
1	1913	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060614_TAEGUKBUNTING_M_TT_DESC	월드컵 응원용 태극기가 걸려있는 휘장이다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1914	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060614_TAEGUKBUNTING_F_TT_DESC	월드컵 응원용 태극기가 걸려있는 휘장이다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1915	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050918_SONGPYON_TT_DESC	멥쌀가루를 반죽하여 소를 넣고 반달 또는 조개 모양으로 빚어서 솔잎을 깔아 찐 떡.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1916	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050918_FRUITPUNCH_TT_DESC	새앙을 달인 물에 설탕이나 꿀을 탄 다음, 곶감과 계피를 담그고 잣을 띄운 음료.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1917	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050918_RICEDRINK_TT_DESC	쌀밥에 엿기름 가루를 우린 물을 부어 삭힌 것에, 생강과 설탕을 넣고 끓여 식힌 다음, 건져 둔 밥알을 띄운 음료.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1918	SN_ITEM_ETC_E050918_MAGICSONGPYON_TT_DESC	신비한 기운이 들어있는 송편. 사용하면 hp와 mp가 즉시 회복된다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1919	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051003_GARLIC_TT_DESC	단군신화에 따르면 곰 한마리가 이 마늘과 쑥을 먹고 사람의 몸이 되었다고 한다. 사용하면 몸에 좋을 것 같다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1920	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051003_MUGWORT_TT_DESC	단군신화에 따르면 곰 한마리가 이 쑥과 마늘을 먹고 사람의 몸이 되었다고 한다. 사용하면 몸에 매우 좋을 것 같다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1921	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_REDPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 붉은빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1922	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_ORANGEPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 주황빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1923	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_YELLOWPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 노란빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1924	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_GREENPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 초록빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1925	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_BLUEPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 파란빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1926	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_VIOLETPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 보라빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1927	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_BLACKPEARL_TT_DESC	예로부터 진귀한 보석이라고 불리는 검은빛을 띤 진주이다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1928	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_BLUEDRAGON_BUNTING_COUPON_TT_DESC	청룡무늬 휘장을 받을 수 있는 교환권이다. 이벤트 소옥에게 가져다 주면 휘장으로 바꿔준다. 단, 이벤트 기간 내에 반드시 바꾸도록 하자.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1929	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_PHOENIX_BUNTING_COUPON_TT_DESC	주작무늬 휘장을 받을 수 있는 교환권이다. 이벤트 소옥에게 가져다 주면 휘장으로 바꿔준다. 단, 이벤트 기간 내에 반드시 바꾸도록 하자.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1930	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_WHITETIGER_BUNTING_COUPON_TT_DESC	백호무늬 휘장을 받을 수 있는 교환권이다. 이벤트 소옥에게 가져다 주면 휘장으로 바꿔준다. 단, 이벤트 기간 내에 반드시 바꾸도록 하자.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1931	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_TURTLE_BUNTING_COUPON_TT_DESC	현무무늬 휘장을 받을 수 있는 교환권이다. 이벤트 소옥에게 가져다 주면 휘장으로 바꿔준다. 단, 이벤트 기간 내에 반드시 바꾸도록 하자.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1932	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_BLUEDRAGON_BUNTING_M_TT_DESC	멋들어진 청룡 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 청룡의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious Blue dragon engraved. It shows Blue dragon's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem Blue dragon tasarımlı sancağı. Blue dragon'un ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Dragón Azul grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Dragón Azul .
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.	راية مع التنين الأزرق مجيد محفورة. يبين روح التنين الأزرق وكرامته. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eine Gravur des ruhmreichen blauen Drachen hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des blauen Drachen zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1933	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_BLUEDRAGON_BUNTING_F_TT_DESC	멋들어진 청룡 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 청룡의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious Blue dragon engraved. It shows Blue dragon's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem Blue dragon tasarımlı sancağı. Blue dragon'un ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Dragón Azul grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Dragón Azul .
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.	راية مع التنين الأزرق مجيد محفورة. يبين روح التنين الأزرق وكرامته. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eine Gravur des ruhmreichen blauen Drachen hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des blauen Drachen zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1934	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_PHOENIX_BUNTING_M_TT_DESC	멋들어진 주작 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 주작의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious Joojak engraved. It shows Joojak's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem Joojak tasarımlı sancağı. Blue Joojak ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Joojak grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Joojak.
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.	راية مع جوجاك مجيد محفورة.يبين جوجاك الأرواح والكرامة. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eine Gravur des ruhmreichen Joojak hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des Joojak zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1935	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_PHOENIX_BUNTING_F_TT_DESC	멋들어진 주작 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 주작의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious Joojak engraved. It shows Joojak's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem Joojak tasarımlı sancağı. Blue Joojak ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Joojak grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Joojak.
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.	راية مع جوجاك مجيد محفورة.يبين جوجاك الأرواح والكرامة. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eine Gravur des ruhmreichen Joojak hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des Joojak zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1936	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_WHITETIGER_BUNTING_M_TT_DESC	멋들어진 백호 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 백호의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious White tiger engraved. It shows White tiger's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem White tiger tasarımlı sancağı. White tiger'in ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Tigre Blanco grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Tigre Blanco.
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.	راية مع النمر الابيض مجيد محفورة. يبين الارواح النمر الابيض وكرامته. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eine Gravur des ruhmreichen weißen Tiger hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des weißen Tigers zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1937	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_WHITETIGER_BUNTING_F_TT_DESC	멋들어진 백호 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 백호의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious White tiger engraved. It shows White tiger's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem White tiger tasarımlı sancağı. White tiger'in ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Tigre Blanco grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Tigre Blanco.
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.	راية مع النمر الابيض مجيد محفورة. يبين الارواح النمر الابيض وكرامته. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eine Gravur des ruhmreichen weißen Tiger hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des weißen Tigers zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1938	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_TURTLE_BUNTING_M_TT_DESC	멋들어진 현무 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 현무의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious Hyunmu engraved. It shows Hyunmu's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem Hyunmu tasarımlı sancağı. Hyunmu'nun ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Hyunmu grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Hyunmu.
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.
	راية مع حيونمو مجيد محفورة.يبين حيونمو الأرواح والكرامة. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eien Gravur des ruhmreichen Hyunmu hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des Hyunmu zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1939	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051021_TURTLE_BUNTING_F_TT_DESC	멋들어진 현무 무늬가 새겨져 있는 휘장이다. 이 휘장은 현무의 기운과 함께 기품 있는 모습을 나타낼 수 있다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A ensign with glorious Hyunmu engraved. It shows Hyunmu's spirits and dignity.
Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Muhteşem Hyunmu tasarımlı sancağı. Hyunmu'nun ruhu ve şerefini gösterir. Meslek bölmesinde donatılabilir.	Una insignia con el glorioso Hyunmu grabado. Muestra los espíritus y la dignidad del Hyunmu.
Puede ser equipado en trabajo.
	راية مع حيونمو مجيد محفورة.يبين حيونمو الأرواح والكرامة. يمكن أن تكون مجهزة في فتحة العمل.	Eine Fahne die eien Gravur des ruhmreichen Hyunmu hat. Es stellt den Geist und die Würde des Hyunmu zur Schau. Kann im Job Slot ausgerüstet werden
1	1940	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051111_CHOCO_PEPERO_TT_DESC	과자에 초코렛을 입혀 만든 빼빼로이다. 먹으면 어떤 좋은 효과가 나에게 일어날 것 같다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1941	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051111_STRAWBERRY_PEPERO_TT_DESC	빼빼로 모양을 하고 있는데 딸기맛과 향이 나는 특이한 빼빼로다. 좀 귀해 보이는데 먹으면 더 좋은 효과가 있을까.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1942	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051111_WHITECHOCO_PEPERO_TT_DESC	초코렛 중에서도 화이트 초코렛을 이용해서 만든 빼빼로다. 검은 빼빼로만 보다가 흰색 빼빼로를 보니 색다른 기분이 든다. 먹으라고 있는 것이니 일단 먹어보자.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1943	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051111_ALMOND_PEPERO_TT_DESC	아몬드를 갈아 과자에 입힌 아몬드 빼빼로다. 한입 먹어보면 고소한 맛이 느껴질 것 같다. 이런 빼빼로를 만들 생각을 하다니…	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1944	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051111_GREENTEA_PEPERO_TT_DESC	이것은 빼빼로에 녹차 가루를 씌워 만든 웰빙 빼빼로!! 웰빙 바람이 빼빼로에도 불고 있다. 몸이 가벼워질 것 같은 녹차 빼빼로.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1945	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051111_GINSENG_PEPERO_TT_DESC	아무리 빼빼로라지만 인삼가루를 입혀 만들 생각을 하다니. 매우 비쌀 것 같은 느낌이 드는 빼빼로다. 맛은 있겠지?	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1946	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051123_EVATION_SCROLL_TT_DESC	두루마리를 펼치는 순간 회피율이 크게 증가해서 상대의 공격을 좀 더 잘 피할 수 있게 된다.	0	0	0	0	0	When scroll is used, parry ratio increases.	0	0	0	Parşömen kullanıldığında, siper onanını arttırır.	Cuando usa el Scroll, la capacidad evasiva se aumenta.	عند استخدام scroll تزيد نسبة الصد.	Wenn die Scroll benutzt wird, erhöht sich die Abwehrbilanz.
1	1947	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051123_HIT_SCROLL_TT_DESC	두루마리를 펼치는 순간 명중률이 크게 증가해서 상대를 공격할 때 좀 더 성공률을 높일 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	When scroll is used, attack rating increases.	0	0	0	Parşömen kullanıldığında, saldırı oranını arttırır.	Cuando usa el Scroll, la puntería se aumenta.	عند استخدام scroll تزيد نسبة الهجوم.	Wenn die Scroll benutzt wird, erhöht sich die Angriffsstärke.
1	1948	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051123_SPEED_UP_SCROLL_TT_DESC	두루마리를 펼치는 순간 다리에 힘이 솟아 이동속도가 좀 더 빨라진다.	0	0	0	0	0	When scroll is used, movement speed increases	0	0	0	Parşömen kullanıldığında, hareket hızını arttırır.	Cuando usa el Scroll, la velocidad de movimiento se aumenta.	عند استخدام scroll تزيد سرعة الحركة.	Wenn die Scroll benutzt wird, erhöht sich die Bewegungsschnelligkeit.
1	1949	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051123_AGILITY_SCROLL_TT_DESC	두루마리를 펼치는 순간 평소보다 민첩해져서 상대의 공격을 잘 피하고, 상대를 공격할 때 좀 더 성공률을 높일 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	When scroll is used, parry ratio and attack rating increases.	0	0	0	Parşömen kullanıldığında, siper ve saldırı oranını arttırır.	Cuando usa el Scroll, la capacidad evasiva y puntería se aumentan.	عند استخدام scroll تزيد نسبة الصد ونسبة الهجوم.	Wenn die Scroll benutzt wird, erhöhen sich Abwehrbilanz und Angriffsstärke.
1	1950	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051123_HP500_SCROLL_TT_DESC	이 주문서를 사용하면 생명력이 늘어나는 것을 느낄 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can feel increase of life force when you use it.	0	0	0	Kullandığında, yaşam gücündeki artışı hissedebilirsin.	Al usarlo,podrás sentir el incremento de su fuerza vital	ستشعر بزيادة في قوة الحياة عند استخدامها.	Du spürst eine Erhöhung der Lebenskraft, wenn du sie benutzt.
1	1951	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051123_MP500_SCROLL_TT_DESC	이 주문서를 사용하면 기의 충만함을 느낄 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can feel aboundance of sprits when you use it.	0	0	0	Kullandığında, ruhların varlığını hissedeceksin.	Al usarlo,podrás sentir la abundancia de las energías.	ستشعر بزيادة في قوة الحياة عند استخدامها.	Du spürst den Überschwang des Geistes, wenn du sie benutzt.
1	1952	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MITTEN_RED_M_TT_DESC	산타가 끼고 다니는 장갑으로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Glove that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın giydiği eldiven, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	Los Gloves que utiliza Santa  no tienen poderes especiales./n Pueden colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	السوار الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhandschuh hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1953	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MITTEN_RED_F_TT_DESC	산타가 끼고 다니는 장갑으로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Glove that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın giydiği eldiven, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot).	Los Gloves que utiliza Santa  no tienen poderes especiales./n Pueden colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	السوار الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhandschuh hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1954	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MITTEN_BLUE_M_TT_DESC	산타가 끼고 다니는 장갑으로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Glove that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın giydiği eldiven, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot).	Los Gloves que utiliza Santa  no tienen poderes especiales./n Pueden colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	السوار الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhandschuh hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1955	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MITTEN_BLUE_F_TT_DESC	산타가 끼고 다니는 장갑으로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Glove that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın giydiği eldiven, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot).	Los Gloves que utiliza Santa  no tienen poderes especiales./n Pueden colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	السوار الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhandschuh hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1956	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MUFFLER_RED_M_TT_DESC	산타가 메고 다니는 목도리로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Muffler that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın taktığı atkı, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	La Muffler que utiliza Santa no tienen poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	الكوفية الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannschal hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1957	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MUFFLER_RED_F_TT_DESC	산타가 메고 다니는 목도리로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Muffler that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın taktığı atkı, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	La Muffler que utiliza Santa no tienen poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	الكوفية الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannschal hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1958	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MUFFLER_BLUE_M_TT_DESC	산타가 메고 다니는 목도리로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Muffler that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın taktığı atkı, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	La Muffler que utiliza Santa no tienen poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	الكوفية الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannschal hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1959	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_MUFFLER_BLUE_F_TT_DESC	산타가 메고 다니는 목도리로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Muffler that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın taktığı atkı, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	La Muffler que utiliza Santa no tienen poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	الكوفية الذي يرتديه Santa  وليست به قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannschal hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1960	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_SET_RED_M_TT_DESC	산타가 입고 다니는 모자, 장갑, 목도리 세트로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A set of the Hat, Glove and Muffler that Santa wears. It has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santa'nın giydiği bir Şapka, Eldiven ve Atkı takımı. Özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	Un conjunto de Hat,  Gloves y Muffler que utiliza Santa  no tiene poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	مجموعة من قبعة وسوار وكوفية يرتديهم Santa . وليست بهم قوى مميزة. /n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Ein Set aus Hut, Handschuh und Schal, das der Weihnachtsmann trägt. Es hat keine besonderen Kräfte./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1961	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_SET_RED_F_TT_DESC	산타가 입고 다니는 모자, 장갑, 목도리 세트로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A set of the Hat, Glove and Muffler that Santa wears. It has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santa'nın giydiği bir Şapka, Eldiven ve Atkı takımı. Özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	Un conjunto de Hat,  Gloves y Muffler que utiliza Santa  no tiene poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	مجموعة من قبعة وسوار وكوفية يرتديهم Santa . وليست بهم قوى مميزة. /n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Ein Set aus Hut, Handschuh und Schal, das der Weihnachtsmann trägt. Es hat keine besonderen Kräfte./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1962	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_SET_BLUE_M_TT_DESC	산타가 입고 다니는 모자, 장갑, 목도리 세트로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A set of the Hat, Glove and Muffler that Santa wears. It has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santa'nın giydiği bir Şapka, Eldiven ve Atkı takımı. Özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	Un conjunto de Hat,  Gloves y Muffler que utiliza Santa  no tiene poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	مجموعة من قبعة وسوار وكوفية يرتديهم Santa . وليست بهم قوى مميزة. /n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Ein Set aus Hut, Handschuh und Schal, das der Weihnachtsmann trägt. Es hat keine besonderen Kräfte./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1963	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_SET_BLUE_F_TT_DESC	산타가 입고 다니는 모자, 장갑, 목도리 세트로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	A set of the Hat, Glove and Muffler that Santa wears. It has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santa'nın giydiği bir Şapka, Eldiven ve Atkı takımı. Özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	Un conjunto de Hat,  Gloves y Muffler que utiliza Santa  no tiene poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	مجموعة من قبعة وسوار وكوفية يرتديهم Santa . وليست بهم قوى مميزة. /n
يمكن وضعه في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Ein Set aus Hut, Handschuh und Schal, das der Weihnachtsmann trägt. Es hat keine besonderen Kräfte./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1964	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_HAT_BLUE_M_TT_DESC	산타가 쓰고 다니는 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Hat that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın taktığı Şapka, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	El Hat que utiliza Santa no tiene poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	القبعة التي يرتديها Santa  وليست بها قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعها في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhut hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1965	SN_ITEM_ETC_E051125_SANTA_HAT_BLUE_F_TT_DESC	산타가 쓰고 다니는 모자로 특별한 능력치는 없다.\n아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Hat that Santa wears has no special power./n
It can be placed in an event slot(job equipment slot).	0	0	0	Santanın taktığı Şapka, özel bir güce sahip değil./n Bir görev yerine yerleştirilmiş olabilir (job equipment slot)	El Hat que utiliza Santa no tiene poderes especiales./n Puede colocarse en el espacio de evento (espacio de equipamiento de trabajo).	القبعة التي يرتديها Santa  وليست بها قوى مميزة./n
يمكن وضعها في موضع المناسبة )موضع أدوات المهنة(	Der Weihnachtsmannhut hat keine besonderen Fähigkeiten./n
Er kann in einen Eventslot gelegt werden (Job-Ausrüstungs-Slot).
1	1966	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060118_60EXP_HELP_TT_DESC	<sml2>하루중 3시간 동안은 사냥시 60%의 경험치를 추가로 받습니다.<br>** 하루의 기준은 이용권을 사용한 순간부터 24시간 입니다.<br>** 소모되지 않은 경험치 보너스 시간은 다음 날까지 유효합니다.<br>** 보너스 경험치 시간은 전투중에만 시간이 흐릅니다.<br>(전투중이란 공격하거나 공격받은 직후 20초까지의 시간을 의미합니다.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용방법</font></strong><br>이용권을 사용하는 순간부터 적용됩니다. 5레벨 이상일 때만 사용이 가능합니다.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">조건</font></strong><br>실버/골드 타임 서비스, 100% 경험치 도우미와 동시에 사용 할 수 없습니다.</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2> For 3 hours a day, you can get additional 60% character exp. & skill exp.<br>** A day is considered as 24 hours from the moment the item is used.<br><br>** Bonus experience time passes by only during battle.<br>(Battle time refers to the 20 seconds from either attacking or being attacked by a monster.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">How To Use</font></strong><br>The item will be in use when activated. Must be level 5 or higher to use this item.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Restrictions</font></strong><br>Cannot be used simultaneously with Silver/Gold Time service and 100% Exp. Helper item.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2> Günde 3 saat için, fazladan %60 karakter ve beceri tecrübesi alabilirsin.<br>** Bir gün, öğenin kullanıldığı andan itibaren 24 saattir. <br><br>** Bonus tecrübe süresi yalnızca savaş sırasında işler.<br>(Savaş süresi, her bir saldırın veya bir canavarın saldırısından 20 saniye denk gelir.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Kullanımı</font></strong><br>Eşya aktif hale geldiğinde kullanılabilir. 5 veya daha yüksek bir seviyede olunmalıdır.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Sınırlandırma</font></strong><br>Gümüş/altın süre servisi 100% Tec. destek eşyası ile aynı anda kullanılamaz.</sml2>	<sml2> Durante 3 horas al día, recibes  un 60% de puntos adicionales de experiencia para el personaje y de habilidad.<br>** Se considera como un día, las 24 horas transcurridas desde el momento del uso de  ítem.<br><br>** El tiempo bonus de punto de experiencia transcurre sólo en el tiempo de la batalla. <br>(El tiempo de Batalla es un tiempo de 20 segundos transcurrido después de atacar o ha sido atacado por un monstruo )<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Cómo usar</font></strong><br>El ítem estará en uso después de ser activado. El jugador debe tener nivel 5 o superior a 5 para poder usarlo.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Restricciones</font></strong><br>No puede usarse simultáneamente con el Silver/Gold Time service y el ítem Ayudante de 100% Exp.</sml2>	<sml2> ستحصل على 60% إضافية من خبرة الشخصية وخبرة المهارات لمدة 3 ساعات في اليوم<br>** يحتسب اليوم كـ24 ساعة من لحظة استخدام الأداة<br><br>** يمر وقت الخبرة أثناء المعارك فقط<br>)وقت المعارك يشير إلى 20 ثانية من  إما المهاجمة أو الهجوم عليك(<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">كيفية الاستخدام</font></strong><br>ستستخدم الأداة عند تفعيلها. يجب أن تكون في مستوى 5 أو أكثر لاستخدام تلك الأداة.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">القيود</font></strong><br>لا يمكن استخدامها في وقت واحد مع الكارت الذهبي/الفضي أو أداة مساعدة 100% من الخبرة.</sml2>	<sml2> Du kannst zusätzliche 60% CharakterExp. für 3 Stunden pro Tag bekommen. & Skill-Exp.<br>** Ein Tag bedeutet 24 Stunden ab dem Moment, wo der Gegenstand benutzt wird.<br><br>** Bonus-Erfahrungszeit vergeht nur während einer Schlacht.<br>(Schlachtzeit bezieht sich auf die 20 Sekunden ab dem Angriff auf oder durch ein Monster.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Anleitung</font></strong><br>Der Gegenstand wird bei Aktivierung benutzt. Du musst Level 5 oder höher sein, um den Gegenstand zu nutzen.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Einschränkung</font></strong><br>Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit Silver/Gold Time Service und 100% Exp. genutzt werden. Helper Item.</sml2>
1	1967	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060118_100EXP_HELP_TT_DESC	<sml2>하루중 3시간 동안은 사냥시 100%의 경험치를 추가로 받습니다.<br>** 하루의 기준은 이용권을 사용한 순간부터 24시간 입니다.<br>** 소모되지 않은 경험치 보너스 시간은 다음 날까지 유효합니다.<br>** 보너스 경험치 시간은 전투중에만 시간이 흐릅니다.<br>(전투중이란 공격하거나 공격받은 직후 20초까지의 시간을 의미합니다.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용방법</font></strong><br>이용권을 사용하는 순간부터 적용됩니다. 10레벨 이상일 때만 사용이 가능합니다.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">조건</font></strong><br>실버/골드 타임 서비스, 60% 경험치 도우미와 동시에 사용 할 수 없습니다.</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2> For 3 hours a day, you can get additional 100% character exp. & skill exp.<br>** A day is considered as 24 hours from the moment the item is used.<br><br>** Bonus experience time passes by only during battle.<br>(Battle time refers to the 20 seconds from either attacking or being attacked by a monster.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">How To Use</font></strong><br>The item will be in use when activated. Must be level 10 or higher to use this item.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Restrictions</font></strong><br>Cannot be used simultaneously with Silver/Gold Time service and 60% Exp. Helper item.</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2> Günde 3 saat için, fazladan %50 karakter ve beceri tecrübesi alabilirsin.<br>** Bir gün, öğenin kullanıldığı andan itibaren 24 saattir. <br><br>** Bonus tecrübe süresi yalnızca savaş sırasında işler.<br>(Savaş süresi, her bir saldırın veya bir canavarın saldırısından 20 saniye denk gelir.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Kullanımı</font></strong><br>Eşya aktif hale geldiğinde kullanılabilir. 10 veya daha yüksek bir seviyede olunmalıdır.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Sınırlandırma</font></strong><br>Gümüş/altın süre servisi 100% Tec. destek eşyası ile aynı anda kullanılamaz.</sml2>	<sml2> Durante 3 horas al día, recibes un 100% de puntos adicionales de experiencia para el personaje y de habilidad.<br>** Se considera como un día, las 24 horas transcurridas desde el momento del uso de  ítem<br><br>** El tiempo bonus de punto de experiencia transcurre sólo en el tiempo de la batalla.  <br>(El tiempo de Batalla es un tiempo de 20 segundos transcurrido después de haber atacado o haber sido atacado por un monstruo .)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Cómo usar</font></strong><br>El ítem estará en uso después de ser activado. El jugador debe tener nivel 5 o superior para poder usarlo.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Restricciones</font></strong><br>No puede usarse simultáneamente con el Silver/Gold Time service y el ítem Ayudante de 60% Exp.</sml2>	<sml2> ستحصل على 100% إضافية من خبرة الشخصية وخبرة المهارات لمدة 3 ساعات في اليوم<br>** يحتسب اليوم كـ24 ساعة من لحظة استخدام الأداة<br><br>** يمر وقت الخبرة أثناء المعارك فقط<br>)وقت المعارك يشير إلى 20 ثانية من  إما المهاجمة أو الهجوم عليك(<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">كيفية الاستخدام</font></strong><br>ستستخدم الأداة عند تفعيلها. يجب أن تكون في مستوى 5 أو أكثر لاستخدام تلك الأداة.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">القيود</font></strong><br>لا يمكن استخدامها في وقت واحد مع الكارت الذهبي/الفضي أو أداة مساعدة 100% من الخبرة.</sml2>	<sml2> Du kannst zusätzliche 100% CharakterExp. für 3 Stunden pro Tag bekommen. & Skill-Exp.<br>** Ein Tag bedeutet 24 Stunden ab dem Moment, wo der Gegenstand benutzt wird.<br><br>** Bonus-Erfahrungszeit vergeht nur während einer Schlacht.<br>(Schlachtzeit bezieht sich auf die 20 Sekunden ab dem Angriff auf oder durch ein Monster.)<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Anleitung</font></strong><br>Der Gegenstand wird bei Aktivierung benutzt. Du musst Level 10 oder höher sein, um den Gegenstand zu nutzen.<br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Einschränkung</font></strong><br>Kann nicht gleichzeitig mit Silver/Gold Time Service und 60% Exp. genutzt werden. Helper Item.</sml2>
1	1968	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060125_RICEDUMPLINGSOUP_TT_DESC	<sml2>새해 첫날에 먹는 맛있는 떡국이다. 떡국을 먹으면 한 살을 더 먹는다고 하는데, 이 떡국은 광채가 나는 것이 특별한 효과가 있을 것 같다.<br>
바로 사용할 수도 있고 소옥이에게 선물로 줄 수도 있다.<br><br>
효과: HP 및 MP 랜덤 증가<br>
유지시간: 10분<br><br>
주의사항: 귀환서 및 텔레포트 이용 시 아이템 효과 사라짐.<br>
</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1969	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060209_WHITE_DUMPLING_TT_DESC	대만의 길거리에서 흔히 볼 수 있는 샤오롱 바오
이벤트 기간 동안 무역이익 2배 적용	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1970	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060209_PINK_DUMPLING_TT_DESC	맛있게 생긴 물만두
이벤트 기간 동안 무역이익 2배 적용	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1971	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060209_CHOCO_CAKE_TT_DESC	연인에게 사랑을 전하는 초코케이크
이벤트 기간 동안 무역이익 2배 적용	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1972	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060411_EGG_TT_DESC	신기한 달걀. NPC 소옥에게 갖다주자	0	0	0	0	0	Marvelous egg. Let's bring it to So-Ok	0	0	0	Muhteşem bir egg. Hadi onu So-ok'a götür	Marvelous egg. Llevémoslo a So-Ok	بيضة رائعة. دعنا  نأتي بها إلى So-Ok.	Wunderbares Ei. Bringen wir es zu So-Ok.
1	1973	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060512_RED_CARNATION_TT_DESC	빨간 카네이션
이벤트 기간 동안 무역이익 2배적용	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1974	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060512_PINK_CARNATION_TT_DESC	분홍 카네이션
이벤트 기간 동안 무역이익 2배적용	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1975	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060512_WHITE_CARNATION_TT_DESC	흰색 카네이션
이벤트 기간 동안 무역이익 2배적용	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1976	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060517_SUMMON_PARTY_SCROLL_TT_DESC	<sml2>몬스터의 마력이 깃든 몬스터 소환주문서. 소환주문서를 사용하면 다른 세상에 있던 강한 몬스터가 소환되어 나타나지만, 오래 있을 수 없고 곧 사라진다고 한다. 강한 소환 몬스터가 출현하는 시간은 약 5분으로 알려져 있다.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용방법: 소환주문서를 사용하면 현재 파티 구성원의 수만큼의 몬스터가 소환된다. 파티 상태가 아니라면 1마리의 강한 몬스터가 소환된다. 마을에서는 사용할 수 없으며, 소환한 후 5분이 지나면 사라진다.<br><br>요구레벨 10 
</font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>Monster summon scroll that contains power of monsters. When used, powerful monsters from the other world will be summoned. However, they cannot stay for a long period of time. Powerful summoned monsters will appear for around 5 minutes.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">How To Use: When scroll is used, the same number of monsters as the current number of party members will be summoned. If you're not in a party, 1 powerful monster will be summoned. Cannot be used in towns, and summoned monsters will disappear after 5 minutes.<br></font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Canavarların gücünü içeren celp parşömeni. Kullanıldığında, öteki dünyadan güçlü canavarlar cağırılacaktır. Ancak, uzun süre kalamazlar. Çağırılan güçlü canavarlar, yaklaşık 5 dakika boyunca görünürler.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Kullanımı: parşömen kullanıldığında, mevcut ekip üyelerinin sayısı kadar canavar çağrılacaktır. Bir ekibe dahil değilsen, güçlü bir canavar çağırılacaktır. Kasabalarda kullanılmaz ve çağrılan canavarlar 5 dakika sonra gözden kaybolur.<br><br>Sınırlandırma seviye 10</font></strong></sml2>	<sml2>Monster Summon Scroll que contiene el poder de los monstruos. Al usarse, aparecerán poderosos monstruos del otro mundo. Sin embargo, no pueden permanecer por mucho tiempo. Los monstruos invocados aparecerán durante 5 minutos.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Cómo usar: Al usar el Scroll, se invocará el mismo número de monstruos que el número de miembros del grupo. Si el jugador no está en un grupo, se invocará 1 poderoso monstruo. No se puede usar en aldeas. Los monstruos invocados desaparecerán después de 5 minutos.<br><br>Nivel de Restricción 10</font></strong></sml2>	<sml2> رسالة استدعاء الوحوش بها قوة الوحوش. وعند استخدامها فسيتم استدعاء الوحوش القوية من العالم الآخر ومع أنهم لا يمكن أن ينتظروا لفترة طويلة من الوقت فستظهر الوحوش القوية التي تم استدعاؤها لوالي 5 دقائق<br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">كيفية الاستخدام: عند استخدام scroll فسيتم استدعاء عدد من الوحوش بنفس عدد أعضاء الفريق الحاليين. وإذا لم تكن عضو في فريق فسيتم استدعاء وحش واحد قوي. ولا يمكنك استخدامها في المدن. وستختفي الوحوش المستدعاه بعد 5 دقائق<br><br>بدءاً من المستوى 10</font></strong></sml2>	<sml2>Monster Summon Scroll, die die Macht der Monster hat. Bei Verwendung werden starke Monster aus der anderen Welt gerufen. Aber sie können nicht lange bleiben. Die gerufenen starken Monster erscheinen für rund 5 Minuten.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Anleitung: Bei Gebrauch der Scroll werden so viele Monster wie anwesende Gruppenmitglieder gerufen. Wenn du zu keiner Gruppe gehörst, wird 1 starkes Monster gerufen. Kann nicht in Städten benutzt werden; die gerufenen Monster verschwinden nach 5 Minuten.<br></font></strong></sml2>
1	1977	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060526_SUMMON_PARTY_SCROLL_A_TT_DESC	<sml2>몬스터의 마력이 깃든 몬스터 소환주문서. 소환주문서를 사용하면 다른 세상에 있던 강한 몬스터가 소환되어 나타나지만, 오래 있을 수 없고 곧 사라진다고 한다. 강한 소환 몬스터가 출현하는 시간은 약 5분으로 알려져 있다.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">사용방법: 소환주문서를 사용하면 현재 파티 구성원의 수만큼의 강한몬스터가 소환되고, 파티 상태가 아니라면 강한 몬스터 1마리가 소환된다. 마을에서는 사용할 수 없으며, 소환한 후 5분이 지나면 사라진다.
</font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>Monster summon scroll that contains power of monsters. When used, powerful monsters from the other world will be summoned. However, they cannot stay for a long period of time. Powerful summoned monsters will appear for around 5 minutes.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">How To Use: When scroll is used, the same number of monsters as the current number of party members will be summoned. If you're not in a party, 1 powerful monster will be summoned. Cannot be used in towns, and summoned monsters will disappear after 5 minutes.<br></font></strong></sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Canavarların gücünü içeren celp parşömeni. Kullanıldığında, öteki dünyadan güçlü canavarlar cağırılacaktır. Ancak, uzun süre kalamazlar. Çağırılan güçlü canavarlar, yaklaşık 5 dakika boyunca görünürler.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Kullanımı: parşömen kullanıldığında, mevcut ekip üyelerinin sayısı kadar canavar çağrılacaktır. Bir ekibe dahil değilsen, güçlü bir canavar çağırılacaktır. Kasabalarda kullanılmaz ve çağrılan canavarlar 5 dakika sonra gözden kaybolur.<br><br>Sınırlandırma seviye 10</font></strong></sml2>	<sml2>Monster Summon Scroll que contiene el poder de los monstruos. Al usarse, aparecerán poderosos monstruos del otro mundo. Sin embargo, no pueden permanecer por mucho tiempo. Los monstruos invocados aparecerán durante 5 minutos.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Cómo usar: Al usar el Scroll, se invocará el mismo número de monstruos que el número de miembros de grupo. Si el jugador no está en un grupo, se invocará 1 poderoso monstruo. No se puede usar en aldeas. Los monstruos invocados desaparecerán después de 5 minutos.<br><br>Nivel de Restricción 10</font></strong></sml2>	<sml2> رسالة استدعاء الوحوش بها قوة الوحوش. وعند استخدامها فسيتم استدعاء الوحوش القوية من العالم الآخر ومع أنهم لا يمكن أن ينتظروا لفترة طويلة من الوقت فستظهر الوحوش القوية التي تم استدعاؤها لوالي 5 دقائق<br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">كيفية الاستخدام: عند استخدام scroll فسيتم استدعاء عدد من الوحوش بنفس عدد أعضاء الفريق الحاليين. وإذا لم تكن عضو في فريق فسيتم استدعاء وحش واحد قوي. ولا يمكنك استخدامها في المدن. وستختفي الوحوش المستدعاه بعد 5 دقائق<br><br>بدءاً من المستوى 10</font></strong></sml2>	<sml2>Monster Summon Scroll, die die Macht der Monster hat. Bei Verwendung werden starke Monster aus der anderen Welt gerufen. Aber sie können nicht lange bleiben. Die gerufenen starken Monster erscheinen für rund 5 Minuten.<br><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156"></font></strong><br><br><br><strong><font color="255,236,219,156">Anleitung: Bei Gebrauch der Scroll werden so viele Monster wie anwesende Gruppenmitglieder gerufen. Wenn du zu keiner Gruppe gehörst, wird 1 starkes Monster gerufen. Kann nicht in Städten benutzt werden; die gerufenen Monster verschwinden nach 5 Minuten.<br></font></strong></sml2>
1	1978	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060517_PAPER_PIECE_TT_DESC	특수한 문자가 새겨져 있는 종이조각. 
문자의 모양을 보니 인간의 것이 아닌 것 같다.	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1979	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060517_MON_GENERATION_BOX_TT_DESC	<sml2>신비한 능력을 가진 상자.
굉장히 위험할 것 같으니, 절대로 혼자서 열어보지 말자!!
</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	<sml2>Box with mysterious power.
Seems to be very dangerous, do not open it alone!!<br><br>Restriction level 10
</sml2>	0	0	0	<sml2>Gizemli gücü olan kutu. Çok tehlikeli gözüküyor, sakın tek başınayken açma!!<br><br>Sınırlandırma seviye 10
</sml2>	"<sml2>Cofre con un poder misterioso. Parece que es muy peligroso ¡¡no la abran solos!!<br><br>Nivel de Restricción 10</sml2>	<sml2>صندوق به قوة غامضة. يبدو خطيراً جداً لا تفتحه بمفردك !!! <br><br>بدءاً من المستوى 10
</sml2>	<sml2>Box mit geheimnisvoller Kraft.
Scheint sehr gefährlich zu sein, öffne sie nicht allein!!<br><br>Nötiger Level: 10
</sml2>
1	1980	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060607_WORLDCUP_G_TT_DESC	월드컵 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템
G, O, A, L, ! 다섯 글자를 모아서 소옥이에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1981	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060607_WORLDCUP_O_TT_DESC	월드컵 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템
G, O, A, L, ! 다섯 글자를 모아서 소옥이에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1982	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060607_WORLDCUP_A_TT_DESC	월드컵 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템
G, O, A, L, ! 다섯 글자를 모아서 소옥이에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1983	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060607_WORLDCUP_L_TT_DESC	월드컵 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템
G, O, A, L, ! 다섯 글자를 모아서 소옥이에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1984	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060607_WORLDCUP_E_TT_DESC	월드컵 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템
G, O, A, L, ! 다섯 글자를 모아서 소옥이에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1985	SN_ITEM_ETC_E100630_VIETNAM_2	2	0	0	0	2	2	0	0	0	2	0	0	0	0
1	1986	SN_ITEM_ETC_E100630_VIETNAM_9	9	0	0	0	9	9	0	0	0	9	0	0	0	0
1	1987	SN_ITEM_ETC_E100630_VIETNAM_FLAG	베트남 국기	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1988	SN_ITEM_ETC_E100630_VIETNAM_2_TT_DESC	추석 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템.
2,9,그리고 50,000골드나 베트남 국기를 가지고 소옥에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1989	SN_ITEM_ETC_E100630_VIETNAM_9_TT_DESC	추석 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템.
2,9,그리고 50,000골드나 베트남 국기를 가지고 소옥에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1990	SN_ITEM_ETC_E100630_VIETNAM_FLAG_TT_DESC	추석 이벤트에 사용되는 아이템.
2,9 아이템들을 함께 가지고 소옥에게 가자	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0
1	1991	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060529_DRAGONFLAG_TT_DESC	거대하고 웅장한 용문양이 그려져 있는 깃발. 
아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Flag with enormous, magnificent dragon pattern engraved. Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Kocaman, ihtişamlı ejderha motifinin işli olduğu bayrak. Job slot' eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.	Bandera con un enorme y magnífico patrón de dragón engravado. Puede ser ubicada en el espacio de trabajo.	علم به رموز تنين ضخمة رائعة محفورة عليه. يمكن التزود به في موضع المهنة.	Flagge mit gigantischem, schönem, eingesticktem Drachenmuster. Kann im Job-Slot abgelegt werden.
1	1992	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060529_GOLDDRAGONFLAG_TT_DESC	거대하고 웅장한 용문양이 그려져 있는 깃발. 용문양 주변으로 멋진 황금색 자수가 새겨져 있어 더 고급스럽게 보인다. 아바타 슬롯에 장착할 수 있다.	0	0	0	0	0	Flag with enormous, magnificent dragon pattern engraved. The gold colored embroidery surrounding the dragon makes the flag look even classier. Can be equipped in the job slot.	0	0	0	Kocaman, ihtişamlı ejderha motifinin işli olduğu bayrak.  Ejderhanın etrafını çevreleyen altın renkli işleme, bayrağı daha da mükemmel hale getirmiş. Job slotun eklendiğinde kullanılabilir.	Bandera con un enorme y magnífico patrón de dragón engravado. El bordado dorado que rodea al dragón hace que la bandera se vea más elegante. Puede ser ubicada en el espacio de trabajo.	علم به رموز تنين ضخمة رائعة محفورة عليه. التطريز الذهبي اللون الذي يحيط بالتنين يجعل العلم يبدو أنيقاً. يمكن التزود به في موضع المهنة.	Flagge mit gigantischem, schönem, eingesticktem Drachenmuster. Die goldene Stickerei rund um den Drachen lässt die Flagge noch nobler aussehen. Kann im Job-Slot abgelegt werden.
1	1993	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_F_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1994	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_E_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1995	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_S_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1996	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_T_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1997	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_I_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1998	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_V_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
1	1999	SN_ITEM_ETC_E060823_FESTIVAL_A_TT_DESC	<sml2>이벤트에 사용되는 아이템<br>
F, E, S, T, I, V, A, L 8글자를 모아 소옥이 에게 가자!</sml2>	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	0	NULL	0	0
