1	8750	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_020_02	무당 묘소령을 찾아가 주술 부적을 전해주게. 서두르게나.	0	0	0	0	0	Find Exorcist Miaoryeong and give her the Enchanted Talismans.  Hurry!	0	0	0	Büyücü Miaoryeong’u bulun ve Enchanted Talisman’ları ona verin.  Acele edin!	Busca a la Exorcista Miaoryeong y entrégale los Enchanted Talismans. ¡Date prisa!	عليك بالعثور على Exorcist Miaoryeong وإعطائها تعاويذ Enchanted Talismans. أسرع!	Finde Exorzist Miaoryeong und gebe ihr die Enchanted Talismans.  Beeile dich!
1	8751	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_020_03	내가 사람을 잘 못 본 겐가?	0	0	0	0	0	I must have thought too highly of you.	0	0	0	Seni gereğinden fazla abartmışım.	Me ha formado una opinión demasiado buena de ti.	لا بد أنني وضعت فيك أمالاً أكبر من قدراتك.	Ich glaube, ich habe dich zu tapfer eingeschätzt.
1	8752	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_020_04	자네의 가방에 공간이 부족하군. 이래서는 내가 주술 부적을 맡길 수가 없으니 가방의 공간을 확보하고 다시 말을 걸어주게나.	0	0	0	0	0	There is not enough room in your inventory.  I can't give you the Enchanted Talismans like this.  Come and speak with me again once you have freed some room.	0	0	0	Stoğunuzda yeterli yer yok.  Enchanted Talisman’ları bu durumda size veremem.  Stokta yer boşalttıktan sonra tekrar gelin ve benimle görüşün.	No hay espacio suficiente en tu inventario. Así no puedo darte los Enchanted Talismans. Ven a hablar conmigo de nuevo cuando hayas liberado algo de espacio.	نظرًا لعدم وجود مساحة كافية في مخزونك. لا يمكنني إعطاؤك تعاويذ Enchanted Talismans بهذه الطريقة. تعالّ وتحدث معي مرة أخرى بمجرد توفير مساحة في مخزونك.	Du hast nicht genügend Platz in deinem Inventar.  So kann ich dir die Enchanted Talismans nicht überreichen.  Erst musst du Platz im Inventar schaffen und dann kannst du wieder mit mir sprechen.
1	8753	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_020_05	그래, 묘소령이 무어라고 하던가?	0	0	0	0	0	So, what did Miaoryeong say?	0	0	0	Peki, Miaoryeong ne dedi?	Entonces, ¿qué dijo Miaoryeong?	إذًا، ماذا قال Miaoryeong؟	Also, was hat Miaoryeong gesagt?
1	8754	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_020_06	뭐? 차이바오가 이걸 나한테 보여주라고 했다고? 흠… 그래, 맞아. 이 놈이 나무를 미치게 만드는 원흉이야. 지독한 사기(邪氣)가 코를 찌르는 구만. 끌끌끌..	0	0	0	0	0	What?  Tsai Bao told you to show me these things, you say?  Hmm...  Yes, he is right.  These talismans are driving the trees mad.  The terribly wicked energy is very foul to my nose.  Tsk, tsk, tsk.	0	0	0	Ne?  Tsai Bao’nun bu şeyleri bana göstermemi istediğini mi söylüyorsun?  Hmm...  Evet, o haklı.  Bu muskalar ağaçları çıldırtıyor.  Çok kötü enerjisinin pis kokusu burnuma geliyor.  Tısk, tısk, tısk.	¿Qué? ¿Dices que Tsai Bao te dijo que me enseñaras estas cosas? Hmm... Sí, tiene razón. Estos talismanes están volviendo locos a los árboles. La terrible energía maligna tiene un olor nauseabundo. Tsk, tsk, tsk.	ماذا؟ أخبرك بأن تريني هذه الأشياء، أنت قلت؟ همم... نعم، هو على حق. تعمل هذه التعاويذ على دفع الأشجار إلى الجنون. للطاقة الشريرة المزعجة رائحة كريهة جدًا على أنفي. إخخ، إخخ، إخخ.	Was?  Tsai Bao hat dir gesagt, du sollst mir diese Dinger zeigen, hast du das gesagt?  Hmm...  Ja, er hat recht.  Diese Talismane machen die Bäume verrückt.  Die schrecklich böse Energie behagt meiner Nase nicht.  Tsk, tsk, tsk.
1	8755	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_020_07	무당의 집으로 가서 무당 묘소령에게 주술 부적을 배달하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Exorcist's Home and deliver the Enchanted Talismans to Exorcist Miaoryeong.	0	0	0	Büyücünün evine gidin ve Enchanted Talisman’ları Büyücü Miaoryeong’a teslim edin.	Ve a la Casa del exorcista y entrega los Enchanted Talismans a la Exorcista Miaoryeong.	اذهب إلى Exorcist's Home وقم بتسليم تعاويذ Enchanted Talismans إلى Exorcist Miaoryeong.	Geh zu Haus des Exorzist und bringe die Enchanted Talismans zum Exorzist Miaoryeong.
1	8756	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_021_01	이 부적이 요괴를 부린다는 건 알았으니 이제 누가 이런 짓을 하는지가 궁금하겠지? 내 얼마 전 숲에 일이 있어 나갔다가 비적 무리를 본 적이 있는데 그 놈들이 이것과 비슷한 부적을 들고 다니더군. 비적 놈들을 족쳐보다 보면 증거를 찾아낼 수 있을 거라고 차이바오에게 전해.	0	0	0	0	0	Now that we know these talismans control those demons, I suppose you want to know who is behind this?  A while ago, when I was out in the forest for a personal business, I happened to see a group of bandits.  They were carrying talismans that looked an awful lot like these ones.  Tell Tsai Bao that you will be able to find clues if you beat the living snot out of them.	0	0	0	Bu muskaların o canavarları kontrol altında bulundurduğunu bildiğimize göre sanırım bunun arkasında kimin olduğunu öğrenmek istiyorsunuzdur, değil mi?  Bir süre önce şahsi bir iş için ormana gittiğimde bir grup eşkiya gördüm.  Bunlara benzer korkunç muskaları taşıyorlardı.  Tsai Bao’ya o eşkiyaların işini bitirirseniz ipucu bulabileceğinizi söyle.	Ahora que ya sabemos que estos talismanes controlan a estos demonios, supongo que querrás saber quién se oculta detrás de todo... Hace tiempo, cuando estaba en el bosque por motivos personales, vi a un grupo de bandidos. Llevaban talismanes que se parecían muchísimo a estos. Dile a Tsai Bao que podrás encontrar pistas si los destruyes.	الآن وقد عرفنا أن هذه التعاويذ تتحكم في هذه الشياطين، أعتقد أنك تريد معرفة من الذي وراء ذلك؟ منذ فترة، عندما كنت بالخارج في الغابة لمباشرة أعمال شخصية، وتصادف رؤيتي لمجموعة من اللصوص. كانوا يحملون تعاويذ تبدو مخيفة إلى حدٍ كبير مثل هذه التعاويذ. أخبر Tsai Bao بأنك ستكون قادرًا على اكتشاف مفاتيح اللغز في حالة هزيمتك للكائن البغيض الحي من بينهم.	Nun, da wir wissen, dass die Talismane diese Dämonen kontrollieren, möchtest du bestimmt wissen wer dahinter steckt?  Vor einiger Zeit, als ich privat im Wald zu tun hatte sah ich eine Gruppe von Banditen.  Sie trugen Talismane, die diesen sehr ähnlich sehen.  Sage Tsai Bao, dass du in der Lage bist Hinweise zu finden, auch wenn du sie unter Druck setzen musst.
1	8757	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_021_02	감당할 능력도 안 되는 놈들이 이런 걸 들고 다니니까 이런 문제가 발생하는 거야. 차이바오에게 가서 똑똑히 전하라구.	0	0	0	0	0	These troubles happen because incompetent people like you carry something like this.  Tell Tsai Bao that.	0	0	0	Senin gibi beceriksiz insanlar böyle bir şeyi taşıdığı için bu sorunlar yaşanıyor.  Bunu Tsai Bao’ya söyle.	Estos problemas suceden porque gente incompetente como tú lleva algo como esto. Cuéntaselo a Tsai Bao.	تحدث هذه المشكلات نتيجةً لوجود أشخاص غير مؤهلين مثلك يحملون شيء شبيه بهذا. أخبر Tsai Bao بذلك.	Solche Schwierigkeiten entstehen, weil unfähige Menschen wie du so etwas herumtragen.  Sag das Tsai Bao.
1	8758	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_021_03	클클클. 맘대로 하셔.	0	0	0	0	0	*cackles* Do as you wish.	0	0	0	*kahkaha atıyor* İstediğini yap.	*risitas* Haz lo que quieras.	*ضحكات متقطعة* افعل كما تشاء.	*gackernd* Wie du willst.
1	8759	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_021_04	나한테 볼 일이 남았나?	0	0	0	0	0	Do you have something else you want to say to me?	0	0	0	Bana söylemek istediğin başka bir şey var mı?	¿Hay algo más que quieras decirme?	هل لديك شيئًا آخر تود أن تخبرني به؟	Gibt es noch etwas, das du mir sagen möchtest?
1	8760	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_021_05	묘소령이 그리 말하던가? 비적들이라.. 이 놈들이 어떻게 그런 강력한 부적을 손에 넣게 된 거지?	0	0	0	0	0	That is what Miaoryeong said, is it?  Bandits...  How did they come to handle such powerful talismans?	0	0	0	Miaoryeong böyle mi dedi?  Eşkiyalar…  Böyle güçlü muskaları nasıl kullanabilirler acaba?	Eso es lo que Miaoryeong dijo, ¿verdad? Bandidos... ¿Cómo han conseguido controlar talismanes tan poderosos?	هذا ما قاله Miaoryeong، أليس كذلك؟ اللصوص... كيف تمكنوا من التعامل مع مثل هذه التعاويذ القوية؟	Das hat Miaoryeong gesagt, nicht wahr?  Banditen...  Wie konnten sie solche machtvollen Talismane handhaben?
1	8761	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_021_06	초소로 돌아가 초소 대장 차이바오와 대화하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Return to the Outpost and speak with Outpost Commander Tsai Bao.	0	0	0	İleri Karakola geri dönün ve İleri Karakol Komutanı Tsai Bao’yla konuşun.	Regresa al Puesto de avanzada y habla con el Comandante de puesto de avanzada Tsai Bao.	ارجع إلى نقطة الحدود وتحدث مع Tsai Bao قائد نقطة الحدود.	Geh zurück zur Outpost und sprich mit dem Outpost Kommandeur Tsai Bao.
1	8762	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_022_01	비적들은 이 숲을 더럽히는 암적인 놈들이야. 약탈도 모자라 조악한 부적을 이용해서 나무 요괴들을 조종하다니. 허나, 아직 놈들이 나무 요괴를 조종했다는 결정적인 증거가 없는 실정일세. 만약 놈들이 정말 나무 요괴를 조종했다면 그 부적들을 반드시 소지하고 있을 걸세. 그 부적을 찾아주지 않겠나?	0	0	0	0	0	The Bandits are a blight upon this forest.  Not only do they rob and pillage, they are now using shoddy talismans to control tree demons.  However, we have no conclusive proof that they are the ones behind the tree demons.  If they really are controlling these tree demons, they are sure to have the talismans in their possession.  Will you retrieve them for us?	0	0	0	Eşkiyalar bu ormanda bir baş belası.  Sadece yağmalamakla ve çalmakla kalmıyorlar, şimdi canavar ağaçları kontrol etmek için güçlü muskalar da kullanıyorlar.  Sadece yağmalamakla ve çalmakla kalmıyorlar, şimdi canavar ağaçları kontrol etmek için güçlü muskalar da kullanıyorlar.  Bu canavar ağaçları gerçekten eşkiyalar kontrol ediyorlarsa ellerinde muhakkak muska vardır.  O muskaları bize getirir misin?	Los bandidos son una peste para este bosque. No solo perpetran robos y pillaje, ahora utilizan talismanes cutres para controlar a los demonios de los árboles. Sin embargo, no tenemos pruebas concluyentes de que ellos sean los responsables de los demonios de los árboles. Si realmente están controlando estos demonios de los árboles, no hay duda de que tienen los talismanes en su poder. ¿Los recuperarás para nosotros?	يعتبر اللصوص بمثابة آفة وانتشرت في هذه الغابة. فلا يقتصر نشاطهم على السرقة والسلب فحسب؛ بل يستخدمون الآن تعاويذ زائفة للسيطرة على شياطين الأشجار. ومع ذلك، ليس لدينا دليل مقنع على أنهم القوة المحركة لشياطين الأشجار. إذا كانوا يتحكمون بالفعل في شياطين الأشجار، فإنهم متأكدين من امتلاكهم للتعاويذ. هل ستعمل على استعادتها من أجلنا؟	Die Banditen sind ein Fluch für den Wald.  Sie rauben und plündern nicht nur, sie benutzen auch schlampige Talismane, um die Baumdämonen zu steuern.  Jedoch haben wir noch keinen festen Beweis, dass sie die Übertäter sind, die hinter den Baumdämonen stecken.  Sollten sie wirklich diejenigen sein, die die Baumdämonen steuern, dann haben sie auch die Talismane.  Kannst du sie für uns besorgen?
1	8763	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_022_02	일개 도적놈들의 집단이지만 이 숲에서 비적은 만만치 않은 상대일 걸세. 우선 가장 약한 비적 졸개와 비적궁수를 상대하게. 그리고 그들이 가진 주술 부적 40개를 가져오게나.	0	0	0	0	0	They may be a group of mere thieves, but they are still rather formidable in this forest.  To start, slay Bandit Subordinates and Bandit Archers.  Bring me 40 Enchanted Talismans from them.	0	0	0	Basit bir hırsızlar grubu olabilir ama yine de ormanda çok tehlikeliler.  Başlangıçta Eşkiya Erlerini ve Eşkiya Okçularını öldürün.  Onlardan bana 40 tane Enchanted Talisman getirin.	Puede que sean un grupo de simples bandidos, pero su poder en este bosque es formidable. Para empezar, asesina a Bandit Subordinates y a Bandit Archers. Tráeme 40 Enchanted Talismans suyos.	قد يكونوا بمثابة مجموعة من اللصوص فحسب، ولكن لا يزالوا يمثلون القوة الهائلة في هذه الغابة. للبدء، اقتل Bandit Subordinates وBandit Archers. قم بإحضار 40 من تعاويذ Enchanted Talismans منهم.	Sie könnten auch nur eine Gruppe von Dieben sein. Sie sind aber sehr furchterregend in diesem Wald.  Zunächst, erledigst du Bandit Subordinates und Bandit Archers.  Bringe mir 40 ihrer Enchanted Talismans.
1	8764	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_022_03	비적들을 무서워 해서야 어디 무인이라고 할 수 있겠나?	0	0	0	0	0	How can you call yourself a warrior if you are afraid of petty thieves?	0	0	0	Ufak hırsızlardan bile korkuyorsan nasıl kendine savaşçı diyebilirsin?	¿Cómo puedes llamarte guerrero y estar asustando de ladronzuelos?	كيف يمكن أن تطلق على نفسك محاربًا إذا كنت خائفًا من لصوص تافهين؟	Also sag mal, wie kannst du dich einen Krieger nennen, wenn du Angst vor Dieben hast?
1	8765	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_022_04	주술 부적은 어찌되었는가?	0	0	0	0	0	What of the Enchanted Talismans?	0	0	0	Enchanted Talisman'larla ilgili gelişme var mı?	¿Qué ha pasado con los Enchanted Talismans?	ما هي تعاويذ Enchanted Talismans؟	Wie wär`s mit den Enchanted Talismans?
1	8766	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_022_05	역시.. 비적놈들의 짓이었군! 이 일은 바삐 조정에 보고해야겠네. 토벌 명령이 떨어지면 비적들의 산채를 불 지르고 그들이 저지른 만행에 대한 죄값을 치르게 할 것이야.	0	0	0	0	0	So, it really IS their doing!  I will have to report this to the Royal Court immediately.  Once the order of their annihilation is issued, we will set their den on fire and make them pay for their crime.	0	0	0	Demek bu gerçekten onların işiymiş!  Bunu hemen Kraliyet Mahkemesine haber vermeliyim.  Bu eşkiyaları yok etme emri çıkar çıkmaz inlerini ateşe vereceğiz ve işedikleri cinayetler için cezalandıracağız.	¡Entonces, realmente lo ESTÁN provocando ellos! Tendré que informar de esto a la Corte Real inmediatamente. Una vez que se envíe la orden de su aniquilación, incendiaremos su guarida y les haremos pagar por sus delitos.	لذا، فهذه الأفعال تنسب إليهم! سأقوم على الفور بإبلاغ المحكمة الملكية عن هذا الأمر. وبمجرد صدور أمر بإبادتهم، سنقوم بإشعال النيران في وكرهم ونجعلهم يدفعون ثمن جرائمهم.	Also sind SIE es doch!  Ich muss das sofort dem Königlichen Gericht melden  Sobald ihre Vernichtungserklärung ausgestellt wurde, setzen wir ihre Behausung in Brand, und dann müssen sie für ihr Verbrechen bezahlen.
1	8767	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_022_06	주술 부적의 수집이 완료되었습니다. 초소 대장 차이바오를 찾아가 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You have finished collecting Enchanted Talismans.  Return to Outpost Commander Tsai Bao.	0	0	0	Enchanted Talisman’ları toplamayı bitirdiniz.  İleri Karakol Komutanı Tsai Bao’ya geri dönün.	Has terminado de reunir Enchanted Talismans. Regresa con el Comandante de puesto de avanzada Tsai Bao.	لقد انتهيت من جمع تعاويذ Enchanted Talismans. ارجع إلى قائد نقطة الحدود Tsai Bao.	Du hast das Sammeln der Enchanted Talismans beendet.  Kehre zum Outpost Kommandeur Tsai Bao zurück.
1	8768	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_023_01	이 숲에 살고 있는 호랑이들은 매우 사납다네. 제 앞을 지나가는 거라면 뭐든 갈기갈기 찢어놓곤 하지. 덕분에 상단들의 피해가 이만저만이 아닐세. 자네가 이 호랑이들을 처치해준다면 큰 도움이 되겠지.	0	0	0	0	0	The tigers that live in this forest are very vicious.  They have a habit of tearing apart whatever walks by in front of them.  Traders are seeing the worst of it.  If you would slay the tigers, it will help them greatly.	0	0	0	Bu ormanda yaşayan kaplanlar çok vahşiler.  Önlerine çıkan herşeyi parçalama adetleri var.  Bundan en çok acı çeken de tüccarlar.  Kaplanları öldürürseniz tüccarlara çok yardım etmiş olacaksınız.	Los tigres que viven en este bosque son muy sanguinarios. Tienen el hábito de despedazar a cualquiera que se les ponga delante. Los comerciantes se están llevando la peor parte. Si mataras a los tigres, les ayudaría mucho.	تتصف النمور التي تعيش في هذه الغابة بالشراسة والوحشية. وهي تتميز بعادة تمزيق المارين أمامها أيًا كانوا. ويرى التجار الأسوأ من ذلك. فإذا تمكنت من قتل النمور، فسيعمل ذلك على مساعدة التجار بشكلٍ كبيرٍ.	Die Tiger, die im Wald leben sind sehr bösartig.  Sie haben die Angewohnheit, dass sie alles, was sich vor ihnen bewegt, in Stücke reißen.  Händler vermuten das Schlimmste.  Es würde uns sehr helfen, wenn du die Tiger töten könntest.
1	8769	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_023_02	어린 놈이고 어른이고 할 것 없이 처단하게. 새끼 맹호 48마리, 맹호 55마리 정도만 처치해도 이 숲이 좀 조용해질 게야.	0	0	0	0	0	Slay them young and old.  Slaying 48 Young Tigers and 55 Tigers should keep things in good order.	0	0	0	Genç yaşlı demeden kaplanları öldürün.  48 tane Young Tiger ve 55 tane Tiger öldürmeniz işleri düzene koyacaktır.	Asesina a los jóvenes y a los viejos. Si asesinas a 48 Young Tigers y a 55 Tigers las cosas deberían mantenerse en orden.	اقتلها صغارًا وكبارًا؛ حيث إن قتل 48 نمرًا من Young Tigersو 55 نمرًا من Tigers يجعل الأمور تسير في مسارها الصحيح.	Ob jung , ob alt, erledige sie.  Erledige 48 Young Tiger und 55 Tiger.Das sollte Dinge wieder in Ordnung bringen.
1	8770	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_023_03	호랑이가 무서운 건가? 한심하군, 그래.	0	0	0	0	0	Are you afraid of tigers?  How pathetic.	0	0	0	Kaplanlardan korkuyor musunuz?  Ne kadar dokunaklı.	¿Te asustan los tigres? Qué patético.	هل أنت خائف من النمور؟ يا له من أمر مثير للشفقة.	Hast du vor Tigern Angst?  Wie erbärmlich.
1	8771	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_023_04	호랑이 퇴치는 잘 되어가는가?	0	0	0	0	0	How goes the tiger hunt?	0	0	0	Kaplan avı nasıl gidiyor?	¿Cómo va la caza de tigres?	كيف يسير صيد النمور؟	Wie jagt man Tiger?
1	8772	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_023_05	사나운 호랑이들의 이빨도 자네는 비껴가는 모양이군. 자네의 활약 덕에 상단들도 조금은 안심하고 숲을 지날 수 있을 걸세. 수고가 많았네.	0	0	0	0	0	Even the teeth of vicious tigers must be powerless against you.  Thanks to your good effort, caravans will be able to pass through the forest with peace of mind.  Well done.	0	0	0	Vahşi kaplanların dişi bile size karşı güçsüz olmalı.  Çaba sarfettiğiniz için teşekkür ederim, kervanlar ormandan gönül rahatlığı içinde geçebilecekler.  İyi iş.	Incluso los dientes de tigres sanguinarios carecen de poder contra ti. Gracias a tu positivo esfuerzo, las caravanas podrán atravesar el bosque tranquilas. Bien hecho.	حتى أسنان النمور الشرسة يجب أن تكون عاجزة أمامك. شكرًا على جهودك العظيمة، ستتمكن القوافل من المرور عبر الغابة بسلام. أحسنت صنعًا.	Sogar die Zähne des bösartigen Tigers haben keine Chance gegen dich.  Danke für deinen Aufwand, Karawanen werden wieder in der Lage sein, den Wald in Ruhe zu passieren.  Super Job.
1	8773	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_023_06	새끼 맹호, 맹호의 퇴치가 완료되었습니다. 초소 대장 차이바오를 찾아가 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You have finished slaying Young Tigers and Tigers.  Return to Outpost Commander Tsai Bao.	0	0	0	Young Tiger’leri ve Tiger’leri öldürmeyi bitirdiniz.  İleri Karakol Komutanı Tsai Bao’ya geri dönün.	Has terminado de asesinar Young Tigers y Tigers. Regresa con el Comandante de puesto de avanzada Tsai Bao.	لقد انتهيت من قتل نمور Young Tigers وTigers. ارجع إلى قائد نقطة الحدود Tsai Bao.	Du hast das Töten der Young Tiger und Tiger beendet.  Kehre zum Outpost Kommandeur Tsai Bao zurück.
1	8774	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_024_01	솦의 더 깊숙한 곳으로 들어가면 장안의 3초소가 있다네. 3초소의 대장 탄위가 지원병을 보내달라고 요청을 했는데 보다시피 우리도 주변의 요괴들을 상대하는 걸로 벅차서 말이야. 자네가 한 번 지원해보지 않겠나? 자네에게 좀 더 새로운 도전의 기회가 될지도 모르니까 말일세.	0	0	0	0	0	Deeper into the forest and you will find Jangan Outpost 3.  Their commander, Tan Wei, has asked for reinforcements.  But, as you can see, we have our hands full just dealing with monsters around our own outpost.  Why don't you volunteer for it?  It may bring you new challenges.	0	0	0	Ormanın derinliklerine gittiğinizde Jangan İleri Karakolu 3’ü bulacaksınız. Karakol komutanı Tan Wei takviye istemiş.  Ama gördüğünüz gibi ileri karakolumuzun etrafındaki canavarlarla uğraşmaktan hiç boş vaktimiz yok.  Neden gönüllü olmayasınız.  Bu size yeni meydan okumalar getirebilir.	En lo más profundo del bosque encontrarás el Puesto de avanzada de Jangan 3. Su comandante, Tan Wei, ha pedido refuerzos. Pero, como puedes ver, estamos muy ocupados encargándonos de los monstruos que cercan nuestro propio puesto de avanzada. ¿Por qué no te presentas voluntario? Te puede aportar nuevos retos.	عند التغلغل في أعماق الغابة ستجد Jangan Outpost 3. وقد طلب منك قائدهم، Tan Wei، تعزيزات. ولكن، كما ترى، نحن مشغولون جدًا في التعامل مع الوحوش الموجودة حول نقطة حدودنا. لماذا لم تتطوع لذلك؟ فإن هذا الأمر قد يجلب لك تحديات جديدة.	Tiefer im Wald findest du Jangan Outpost 3.  Ihr Kommandeur, Tan Wei. Er hat um Unterstützung gebeten.  Aber wie du siehst haben wir alle Hände voll zu tun, mit diesen Monstern bei unserer Outpost.  Warum meldest du dich nicht freiwillig?  Es könnte neue Herausforderungen bedeuten.
1	8775	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_024_02	탄위의 초소는 우리 초소에서 좀 더 서쪽으로 가면 있다네. 못 찾겠다면 지도에서 한 번 확인해 보게나.	0	0	0	0	0	You will find Tan Wei's outpost to the west of here.  If you can't find it, try consulting your map.	0	0	0	Tan Wei’nin ileri karakolunu buradan batıda bulacaksınız.  Karakolu bulamazsanız haritanıza başvurun.	Encontrarás el puesto de avanzada de Tan Wei al oeste de aquí. Si no lo encuentras, prueba a consultar tu mapa.	ستجد نقطة حدود Tan Wei نحو الغرب من هنا. إذا لم تعثر عليها، حاول الاستعانة بخريطتك.	Du findest die Outpost von Tan Wei westlich von hier.  Wenn du sie nicht finden kannst, schaue auf deine Landkarte.
1	8776	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_024_03	자네에게 좋은 기회라고 생각하네만.. 본인이 싫다면 강제할 수도 없는 일이지.	0	0	0	0	0	I think it will be a good opportunity for you, but I suppose I can't force you into it.	0	0	0	Bence bu sizin için iyi bir fırsat olacak ama sanırım bunu yapmaya sizi zorlayamam.	Creo que será una buena oportunidad para ti, pero supongo que no puedo forzarte a hacerlo.	أعتقد بأنها ستكون فرصة جيدة لك، ولكن لا أستطيع إجبارك على الدخول فيها.	Ich denke es wäre eine gute Gelegenheit für dich, aber ich kann dich nicht dazu zwingen.
1	8777	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_024_04	장안 3초소로 가서 탄위를 만나보게. 그를 돕다 보면 자네의 실력도 더 상승하게 될 것이야.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Jangan Outpost 3 and speak with Tan Wei.  You will see your skills improving as you assist him.	0	0	0	Jangan İleri Karakolu 3’e gidin ve Tan Wei’yle konuşun.  Ona yardım ederken becerilerinizin geliştiğine şahit olacaksınız.	Ve al Puesto de avanzada de Jangan 3 y habla con Tan Wei. Verás que al ayudarlo tus habilidades mejoran.	اذهب إلى Jangan Outpost 3 وتحدث مع Tan Wei. ستلاحظ عند مساعدته بأن مستوى مهاراتك يتحسن.	Gehe zu Jangan Outpost 3 und sprich mit Tan Wei.  Du wirst sehen, wie sich deine Fähigkeiten verbessern während du ihn unterstützt.
1	8778	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_024_05	음? 자네는… 아아, 이야기는 들었네. 차이바오가 입이 마르도록 칭찬을 하더군. 하지만 우리 초소에서의 임무는 지금보다 더 힘들지도 모른다네. 각오 단단히 하게나. 하하하.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm?  You are...  Oh, yes!  I have heard much about you.  Tsai Bao could not stop praising you.  But the work at our outpost may be more difficult.  Be prepared, ha ha ha!	0	0	0	Hmm?  Sen…  Ah, evet!  Hakkında çok şey duydum.  Tsai Bao seni öve öve bitiremiyordu.  Ama bizim ileri karakolumuzdaki iş daha zor olabilir.  Hazırlıklı ol, ha ha ha!	¿Hmm? Tú eres... ¡Ah, sí! He oído hablar mucho de ti. Tsai Bao no paraba de alabarte. Pero la tarea en nuestro puesto de avanzada puede resultar más difícil. ¡Prepárate, ja, ja, ja!	ماذا؟ أنت... أوه، نعم! لقد سمعت الكثير عنك. لم يتمكن Tsai Bao من التوقف عن مدحك. ولكن قد يكون العمل في نقطة الحدود الخاصة بنا أكثر صعوبة. كن مستعدًا، ها ها ها!	Hmm?  Du bist...  Oh, ja!  Ich habe schon viel über dich gehört.  Tsai Bao hat dich immer wieder gelobt.  Die Arbeit hier in unserer Outpost ist wahrscheinlich schwieriger.  Bereite dich darauf vor, ha ha ha!
1	8779	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_024_06	장안 3초소로 가서 초소 대장 탄위와 대화하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Go to Jangan Outpost 3 and speak with Outpost Commander Tan Wei.	0	0	0	Jangan İleri Karakolu 3’e gidin ve İleri Karakol Komutanı Tan Wei’yle konuşun.	Ve al Puesto de avanzada de Jangan 3 y habla con el Comandante de puesto de avanzada Tan Wei.	اذهب إلى Jangan Outpost 3 وتحدث مع قائد نقطة الحدود Tan Wei.	Gehe zu Jangan Outpost 3 und sprich mit dem Outpost Kommandeur Tan Wei.
1	8780	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_01	어이쿠, 내 이럴 줄 알았지. 이런 곳에 배치받을 때부터 알아봤다고. 아, 글쎄. 무슨 놈의 숲에 나무 요괴들이 이렇게 돌아다니는지 원.. 뒷간도 없어서 볼일을 보려면 숲 속으로 들어갈 수밖에 없는데 아주 그냥 무서워 미치겠다니까요. 이 나무 요괴들 좀 어떻게 퇴치 안 될까요?	0	0	0	0	0	Hmph!  I knew it!  I knew it the moment I got assigned to this place.  What kind of a forest is infested with so many tree demons, anyway?  We don't even have an outhouse here, so we have to go into the forest to do our business, you know.  It scares the crap out of me.  Could you take care of them for me somehow?	0	0	0	Hmf!  Biliyordum!  Bunu buraya atandığım andan beri biliyordum.  Her neyse, bu kadar ağaç canavarının bulaştığı orman nasıl bir ormandır?  Burada tuvaletimiz bile yok, o yüzden ihtiyacımızı gidermek için de ormana gitmemiz gerekiyor, biliyorsun.  Bu beni çok korkutuyor. Benim için bir şekilde onların icabına bakabilir misin?	¡Hmph! ¡Lo sabía! Lo supe en el momento en que me asignaron a este lugar. ¿Pero qué tipo de bosque está infectado con tantos demonios de los árboles? Ni siquiera tenemos un edificio anexo aquí, así que tenemos que internarnos en el bosque para hacer nuestro trabajo, ¿sabes? Me asusta mucho. ¿Crees que podrías encargarte de ellos por mí?	آه! عرفت ذلك! عرفت ذلك في اللحظة التي تم تخصيصي فيها لهذا المكان. أي نوعٍ من الغابات الذي يوجد فيه عدد كبير من شياطين الأشجار، على أية حال؟ كما تعرف، نحن ليس لدينا حتى مبنى ملحق صغير هنا، لذا يجب علينا الدخول في الغابة للقيام بأعمالنا. إن الأمر يخيفني بدرجةٍ كبيرةٍ. هل بوسعك الاعتناء بهم من أجلي بطريقةٍ أو بأخرى؟	Hmm!  Ich wusste es!  I wusste es, sobald man mich hierher geschickt hatte.  Welche Art von Wald ist überhaupt mit so vielen Baumdämonen verseucht?  Hier gibt es noch nicht einmal eine Toilette, also müssen wir unsere "Geschäfte" im Wald erledigen, oh je.  Das macht mir wirklich Angst.  Kannst du diesen Job für mich übernehmen?
1	8781	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_02	썩은 나무 여하와 여하 놈들을 처치하면 되는데.. 뭐, 잡았다는 증거로 그 놈들의 몸에서 나오는 썩은 나무 껍데기를 가져와 주시면 고맙겠군요. 30개 정도면 충분하지 싶습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You need to slay Rotten Yeohas and Yeohas.  I would appreciate it if you brought me the Rotten Tree Bark from their bodies as proof of their death.  30 should do nicely.	0	0	0	Rotten Yeoha’ları ve Yeoha’ları öldürmen gerekiyor.  Öldüklerinin kanıtı olarak vücutlarından Rotten Tree Bark getirirsen minnettar olurum.  30 tane olsa iyi olur.	Tienes que asesinar Rotten Yeohas y Yeohas. Te agradecería que me trajeras la Rotten Tree Bark de los cuerpos como prueba de su muerte. 30 debería ser suficiente.	يتعين عليك قتل Rotten Yeohas وYeohas. سأكون ممتنًا إذا أحضرت لي لحاء Rotten Tree Bark من أجسادهم كدليل على موتهم. 30 ستفي بالغرض.	Du musst Rotten Yeohas und Yeohas erledigen.  Ich wäre dir dankbar, wenn du mir die Rotten Tree Bark als Beweis ihres Todes bringen würdest.  30 wären wunderbar.
1	8782	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_03	허헛. 이것 참.. 모처럼 아껴둔 수행자의 주화를 선물로 드리려고 했는데.	0	0	0	0	0	Oh, dear me.  I suppose I should hang onto these Monk's Tokens for now, then.	0	0	0	Ah, canım. Sanırım şimdilik bu Monk'un Simgelerine güvenmem gerekecek.	Oh, pobre de mí. Supongo que tendré que quedarme estos Monk's Tokens por ahora.	أوه، عزيزي. أعتقد بأنه يجب الاحتفاظ بعملات Monk's Tokens هذه الآن وفيما بعد.	Oh du meine Güte.  Ich nehme an, ich sollte diese Monk's Token noch etwas länger behalten.
1	8783	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_04	썩은 여하와 여하 놈들을 잡다보면 썩은 나무 껍데기가 떨어질 겁니다. 30개만 구해주십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	You will find Rotten Tree Bark as you slay Rotten Yeohas and Yeohas.  Bring me 30 of those.	0	0	0	Rotten Yeoha’ları ve Yeoha’ları öldürdüğünde Rotten Tree Bark bulacaksın.  Bana onlardan 30 tane getir.	Encontrarás la Rotten Tree Bark cuando asesines a Rotten Yeohas y a Yeohas. Tráeme 30 de esas.	ستجد لحاء Rotten Tree Bark أثناء قيامك بقتل Rotten Yeohas وYeohas. أحضر لي 30 منهم.	Du findest die Rotten Tree Bark wenn du Rotten Yeohas und Yeohas killst.  Bringe mir 30 von ihnen.
1	8784	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_05	오호라! 정말 나무 요괴를 물리쳐 주셨군요. 정말 감사합니다. 이제 숲에 들어갈 때도 겁날 일이 없겠어요. 그나저나 이 나무 껍데기들은 이제 어디다가 써야할지 모르겠군요. 아무튼 제 부탁을 들어주셨으니 이 수행자의 주화를 선물로 드리겠습니다. 꼭 필요하신 곳에 사용하십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	Ah-ha!  You really did slay those tree demons for me.  Thank you ever so much!  Now, I don't have to be afraid of entering the forest.  Anyway, I have no idea what I will use this tree bark for.  No matter.  You helped me, so I will give you these Monk's Tokens as a gift.  I hope they will come in handy.	0	0	0	Ah-ha!  O ağaç canavarlarını gerçekten benim için öldürmüşsün. Çok teşekkür ederim! Şimdi ormana girmekten korkmama gerek yok.  Her neyse, bu ağaç kabuğunu nasıl kullanacağıma dair hiçbir fikrim yok.  Önemli değil.  Bana yardım ettin, bu nedenle bu Monk’un Simgelerini hediye olarak sana vereceğim.  Umarım işine yarar.	¡Ajá! En verdad has asesinado a esos demonios de los árboles por mí. ¡Te lo agradezco mucho! Ahora, ya no tengo miedo de entrar en el bosque. De todas formas, no tengo ni idea de para qué usaré esta corteza de árbol. No importa. Me has ayudado, así que te daré estos Monk's Tokens de regalo. Espero que te sean útiles.	مفهوم! أنت بالفعل قتلت شياطين الأشجار هذه من أجلي. شكرًا جزيلاً. الآن، يجب عليّ عدم الخوف من دخول الغابة. على أية حال، ليس لدي أدنى فكرة عن الغرض الذي من أجله سأستخدم لحاء الشجرة هذا. الأمر ليس مهمًا. لقد ساعدتني، لذا سأعطيك عملات Monk's Tokens هذه كهدية. أتمنى بأنها ستكون مفيدة.	Ah-ha!  Du hast tatsächlich die Baumdämonen für mich getötet. Ganz herzlichen Dank!  Jetzt kann ich ohne ängstlich zu sein in den Wald.  Allerdings weiß ich überhaupt nicht, was ich mit der Baumrinde anfangen soll.  Egal.  Du hast mir geholfen, und aus Dank gebe ich dir diese Monk's Token.  Ich hoffe sie nützen dir eines Tages.
1	8785	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_06	음.. 저를 도와주신 것은 감사하지만 가방 안에 빈 공간이 없으면 사례를 할 수가 없습니다. 가방에 공간부터 확보해주시기 바랍니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm...  I really AM grateful for your help, but I can't show my gratitude if you have no room in your inventory.  Please, make sure that you have enough space in your inventory first.	0	0	0	Hmm...  Gerçekten müteşekkirim ama stoğunda yer yoksa minnettarlığımı gösteremem.  Lütfen önce stoğunda yeterli yer bulunduğundan emin ol.	Hmm... Realmente ESTOY agradecido por tu ayuda, pero no puedo demostrarte mi gratitud si no tienes espacio en tu inventario. Por favor, asegúrate de que tienes espacio suficiente en tu inventario primero.	همم... إنني ممتن حقًا لمساعدتك، ولكن لا يمكنني إبداء امتناني إذا لم يكن لديك مساحة في مخزونك. من فضلك، تأكد أولاً من وجود مساحة كافية في مخزونك.	Hmm...  Ich bin dir für deine Hilfe dankbar. Ich kann dir meine Dankbarkeit jedoch nicht zeigen, da du in deinem Inventar keinen Platz hast.  Bitte mache zuerst Platz in deinem Inventar.
1	8786	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_025_07	썩은 나무 껍데기 수집이 완료되었습니다. 초소 경비병 진쟈총을 찾아가 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You have finished collecting Rotten Tree Bark.  Return to Outpost Guard Qin Jia Qong.	0	0	0	Rotten Tree Bark toplamayı bitirdin.  İleri Karakol Muhafızı Qin Jia Qong’a geri dönün.	Has terminado de reunir Rotten Tree Bark. Regresa con el Guardia de puesto de avanzada Qin Jia Qong.	لقد انتهيت من جمع لحاء Rotten Tree Bark. ارجع إلى حارس نقطة الحدود Qin Jia Qong.	Du hast das Sammeln der Rotten Tree Bark beendet.  Gehe zur Outpost Wache Qin Jia Qong zurück.
1	8787	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_01	요즘 전체적으로 재정난이라는 소리 들어보셨습니까? 장안 헌터조합도 지금 무기 보급할 여력도 없이 죽을 맛이라는 군요. 그래서 제가 생각을 해봤는데 말이죠. 비적들의 무기를 빼앗아서 쓰면 어떨까 싶더라고요. 우리는 비적들의 수가 줄어서 좋고 헌터 조합은 무기를 얻어서 좋고 일석이조 아니겠습니까? ….뭐, 물론 비적들을 좀 퇴치해야하긴 합니다만..	0	0	0	0	0	Have you heard?  They say everyone is having a financial crisis.  The Hunter Association in Jangan is also penny-pinching and can't even supply weapons.  So, I started thinking...  What if we seized the weapons of the Bandits?  We benefit from the decreasing number of Bandits, and merchants benefit from the supply of weapons.  It's a win-win situation, you see.  Of course..., that does require slaying plenty of Bandits...	0	0	0	Duydun mu?  Herkesin mali krizde olduğu söyleniyor.  Jangan’daki Avcıları Birliği de her kuruşunu sayıyor ve hatta silah bile tedarik edemiyor.  Bu yüzden aklıma şöyle bir şey geldi…  Eşkiyaların silahlarını ele geçirsek nasıl olur?  Eşkiyaların sayısının azalmasından faydalanırız ve tüccarlar silah tedarikinden kazanç sağlarlar.  Görüyorsun, bu bir kazan-kazan durumu.  Tabii... bunun için epey Eşkiya öldürülmesi gerekiyor...	¿Te has enterado? Dicen que todo el mundo está pasando una crisis financiera. La Asociación de Cazadores en Jangan también es muy tacaña y ni siquiera pueden suministrar armas. Así que me he puesto a pensar... ¿Y si nos apoderáramos de las armas de los bandidos? Nos beneficiaríamos de un número reducido de bandidos y los comerciantes se beneficiarían del suministro de armas. Como ves, es una situación en la que todos ganan. Por supuesto... Eso implica asesinar a un montón de bandidos...	أسمعت بذلك؟ يقولون أن الجميع يعاني من أزمة مالية. مؤسسة الصيادين في Jangan ليس لديها الرغبة في إنفاق الأموال وبالتالي لا يمكنها توريد الأسلحة. لذا، بدأت في التفكير... ماذا لو تمكنا من السيطرة على أسلحة اللصوص؟ سنستفيد من عدد اللصوص المنخفض، ويستفيد التجار من توريد الأسلحة. إنها صفقة تعود بالنفع على الطرفين، كما ترى. بالطبع...، ذلك يتطلب قتل عدد كبير من اللصوص...	Hast du schon das Neuste gehört?  Man sagt, dass jeder finanziell schlecht dasteht.  Der Jagdverein in Jangan muss jeden Pfennig umdrehen und kann deswegen keine Waffen zur Verfügung stellen.  Also habe ich folgendes gedacht...  Wie wäre es, wenn wir uns die Waffen der Banditen holen?  So hätten wir den Vorteil, dass die Banditen weniger werden und die Händler hätten Waffen.  Es wäre eine Win-Win Situation.  Natürlich bedeutet das, dass wir einige Banditen töten müssten...
1	8788	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_02	비적들과 전면전을 펼치기는 어려우니 일단은 제일 약한 비적 졸개와 비적궁수를 노리는 게 좋을 것 같습니다. 비적궁수와 그들을 졸졸 따라다니는 졸개들이 가진 화살 40개만 빼앗아 와주십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	It's difficult to wage an all-out war against them.  For now, let's strike the weakest among them - Bandit Subordinates and Bandit Archers.  Bring me 40 arrows carried by Bandit Archers and their Bandit Subordinates that follow them around everywhere.	0	0	0	Onlara karşı geniş çaplı bir savaş başlatmak zor.  Şimdilik aralarında en zayıf olanlarını, yani Eşkiya Erlerini ve Eşkiya Okçularını vuralım.  Eşkiya Okçuların ve onları her yerde takip eden Eşkiya Erlerinin taşıdığı oklardan bana 40 tane getir.	Es difícil hacer una guerra sin cuartel contra ellos. Por ahora, ataquemos a los más débiles: Bandit Subordinates y Bandit Archers. Tráeme 40 flechas de los Bandit Archers y de sus Bandit Subordinates, que los siguen a todas partes.	من الصعب شن حرب كاملة ضدهم. أما حاليًا، دعنا نقضي على الضعفاء منهم - Bandit Subordinates وBandit Archers. أحضر لي 40 سهمًا تحملها Bandit Archers وBandit Subordinates التابعين لهم في كل مكان.	Es ist schwierig einen totalen Krieg gegen sie zu führen.  Für den Moment wollen wir die Schwächsten von ihnen beseitigen Bandit Subordinates und Bandit Archers..  Bringe mir 40 Pfeile von den Bandit Subordinates und Bandit Archers., die ihnen immer folgen.
1	8789	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_03	음.. 역시 이 계획은 누군가 의뢰를 수락해주지 않으면 말짱 도루묵인 계획이군요.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm...  As expected, this plan is no good without someone to take on the task.	0	0	0	Hmm...  Beklendiği gibi bu görevi üstlenecek biri olmadan bu plan işe yaramaz.	Hmm... Como esperaba, este plan no es bueno sin alguien que se encargue de la tarea.	همم... كما هو متوقع، هذه الخطة ليست مناسبة بدون وجود شخص يتولى المهمة.	Hmm...  Wie erwartet ist dieser Plan nicht gut, ohne dass jemand diese Aufgabe übernimmt.
1	8790	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_04	비적 졸개들은 비적궁수들이 쓸 화살을 들고 다닌다고 합니다. 두 놈들을 족치다 보면 많은 양의 화살을 얻을 수 있을 거에요. 40개만 부탁합니다.	0	0	0	0	0	I hear that Bandit Subordinates carry arrows for the archers.  Get them both and you should be able to find plenty of arrows.  Just bring me 40 of them.	0	0	0	Eşkiya Erlerin okçuların oklarını taşıdığını duydum.  İkisini de avlayın ve çok sayıda ok bulabileceksiniz.  Bana onlardan 40 tane getir.	He oído que los Bandit Subordinates portan flechas para los arqueros. Ve a por ambos y deberías conseguir un montón de flechas. Basta con que traigas 40.	سمعت بأن Bandit Subordinates تحمل أسهمًا لرماة السهام. احصل على كليهما ويجب أن تجد عددًا كبيرًا من الأسهم. أحضر لي 40 منهم فقط.	Ich habe gehört, dass die Bandit Subordinates die Pfeile für die Schützen tragen.  Erledige beide, und du wirst sehen, dass du genügend Pfeile findest.  Bringe mir 40 von ihnen.
1	8791	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_05	훌륭합니다! 이 계획은 실력자가 지원을 해줘야 성공 가능한 계획입니다만.. 역시나 멋지게 성공했군요. 제가 보는 눈이 있나 봅니다. 후후후후. 자, 저를 대신해서 고생하셨으니 이 수행자의 주화를 드리지요. 분명 쓸모가 있을 겁니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Astounding!  This plan depended on someone powerful, and you did it!  I guess I am an excellent judge of character.  *chuckles*  Now, for going through all that trouble for me, I will give you these Monk's Tokens.  I'm sure they will come in handy.	0	0	0	Şaşırtıcı!  Bu plan kuvvetli birilerine dayanıyordu ve sen onu yerine getirdin!  Sanırım karakterleri tanımada üstüme kimse yok.  *kahkaha atıyor* Şimdi tüm bu zorluklara benim adıma katlandığın için bu Monk’un Simgelerini sana vereceğim.  Eminim işine yarar.	¡Increíble! Este plan dependía de alguien poderoso, ¡y lo has conseguido! Supongo que juzgo muy bien a las personas. *risas* Ahora, para compensar todas las molestias, te entregaré estos Monk's Tokens. Seguro que te serán útiles.	مذهل! اعتمدت هذه الخطة على وجود شخص قوي، وأنت قمت بها! أخمن بأنني قاضٍ متميز في الحكم على الشخصيات. *ضحكات خافتة* الآن، ونظرًا لتحملك جميع المشاكل والمتاعب من أجلي، فسأعطيك عملات Monk's Tokens الرمزية. أنا متأكد بأنها ستكون مفيدة.	Erstaunlich!  Dieser Plan hing von jemandem mit Power ab, und du warst derjenige!  Ich denke ich kann Charakteren sehr gut einschätzen.  *lacht*  Nun gebe ich dir für all deine Mühe diese Monk`s Token.  Ich bin mir sicher sie nützen dir eines Tages.
1	8792	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_06	음.. 저를 도와주신 것은 감사하지만 가방 안에 빈 공간이 없으면 사례를 할 수가 없습니다. 가방에 공간부터 확보해주시기 바랍니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm...  I really AM grateful for your help, but I can't show my gratitude if you have no room in your inventory.  Please, make sure that you have enough space in your inventory first.	0	0	0	Hmm...  Gerçekten müteşekkirim ama stoğunda yer yoksa minnettarlığımı gösteremem.  Lütfen önce stoğunda yeterli yer bulunduğundan emin ol.	Hmm... Realmente ESTOY agradecido por tu ayuda, pero no puedo demostrarte mi gratitud si no tienes espacio en tu inventario. Por favor, asegúrate de que tienes espacio suficiente en tu inventario primero.	همم... إنني ممتن حقًا لمساعدتك، ولكن لا يمكنني إبداء امتناني إذا لم يكن لديك مساحة في مخزونك. من فضلك، تأكد أولاً من وجود مساحة كافية في مخزونك.	Hmm...  Ich bin dir für deine Hilfe dankbar. Ich kann dir meine Dankbarkeit jedoch nicht zeigen, da du in deinem Inventar keinen Platz hast.  Bitte mache zuerst Platz in deinem Inventar.
1	8793	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_026_07	비적의 화살 수집이 완료되었습니다. 초소 경비병 진쟈총을 찾아가 보고하세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You have finished collecting Bandit's Arrows.  Return to Outpost Guard Qin Jia Chong.	0	0	0	Bandit’s Arrow toplamayı bitirdiniz.  İleri Karakol Muhafızı Qin Jia Chong’a geri dönün.	Has terminado de reunir Bandit's Arrows. Regresa con el Guardia de puesto de avanzada Qin Jia Chong.	لقد انتهيت من جمع أسهم Bandit's Arrows. ارجع إلى حارس نقطة الحدود Qin Jia Chong.	Du hast das Sammeln Bandit's Arrows beendet.  Gehe zur Outpost Wache Qin Jia Chong zurück.
1	8794	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_027_01	호랑이.. 호랑이… 어흥! 아, 실례했습니다. 요즘 호랑이들이 사나워져서 그 생각 좀 하다보니 그만… 휴우, 생각만 해도 무섭군요. 그 놈들 이빨만 모두 뽑아버려도 좀 덜 무서울 것 같은데.. 누가 호랑이 놈들 이빨 좀 뽑아주면 좋겠어요.	0	0	0	0	0	Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.  Catch the tiger by the...  Oh, pardon me.  The tigers in the area have become so ferocious that I'm frightened...  *sigh*  Just thinking about them gives me the chills.  I would be a lot more at ease if only someone would pluck out their teeth for me...	0	0	0	Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.  Kaplanın şeyinden yakala…  Ah, özür dilerim. Buradaki kaplanlar o kadar acımasız ki, korkuyorum…  Ah, özür dilerim. Buradaki kaplanlar o kadar acımasız ki, korkuyorum…  Birileri benim yerime kaplanların dişini çekse çok rahatlarım...	Pito, pito, gorgorito. Dónde vas tú tan... Oh, lo siento. Los tigres de la zona se han vuelto tan feroces que estoy asustado... *suspiro* Solo pensar en ellos me da escalofríos. Me sentiría mucho más tranquilo si alguien les arrancara los dientes por mí...	حادي بادي كرنب زبادي شالوا وحطوا كله على... أوه، عفوًا. لقد أصبحت النمور في هذه المنطقة أكثر ضراوة وشراسة إلى حدٍ يخيفني... *آه* إن مجرد التفكير بهم يشعرني بالقشعريرة. سأشعر بالراحة إلى حدٍ كبير إذا قام شخص ما باقتلاع أسنانها من أجلي...	Eins, zwei, drei...  Und du bist dabei...  Ach, entschuldige. Die Tiger in dieser Gegend werden sehr wild. Das macht mir Angst...  *Seufzt*  Wenn ich an sie denke bekomme ich Gänsehaut.  Es ginge mir schon wesentlich besser, wenn jemand für mich ihre Zähne ziehen würde...
1	8795	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_027_02	호랑이 이빨을 뽑아주시겠다고요? 아유~ 저야 그래주시면 감사하지요. 이 숲 안쪽에는 사나운 맹호와 새끼 맹호들이 진을 치고 있답니다. 그 놈들의 이빨을 그냥 아주 죄다 뽑아주시기 바랍니다. 더도 말고 덜도 말고 50개만 부탁드릴게요.	0	0	0	0	0	You will remove their teeth for me?  Why, I would be tickled to death!  Deeper into the forest, ferocious Tigers and Young Tigers have taken over an area.  Pull out all of their teeth.  Bring me 50 of them, would you?  No more, no less.	0	0	0	Benim için onların dişini çekecek misin?  Ölümüne korkarım!  Ormanın deridnliklerine gittikçe acımasız Tiger’ler ve Young Tiger’ler her yeri işgal etmiş.  Dişlerinin hepsini çekin.  Bana onlardan 50 tane getirirsiniz, değil mi?  Çok ta değil, az da değil.	¿Les quitarás los dientes por mí? ¡Me sentiría muy feliz si lo hicieras! En lo más profundo del bosque, Tigers y Young Tigers feroces se han hecho con el poder en una zona. Sácales todos los dientes. Tráeme 50, ¿de acuerdo? Ni uno más, ni uno menos.	هل ستنزع أسنانها من أجلي؟ لماذا، سأكون ممتنًا وراضيًا حتى الموت؟ عند التغلغل في أعماق الغابة، ستجد أن Tigers وYoung Tigers الشرسة قد استولت على إحدى المناطق. اقتلع جميع أسنانها ستقوم بإحضار 50 منهم لي، أليس كذلك؟ دون زيادة أو نقصان.	Wirst du für mich ihre Zähne rausreißen?  Warum? Ich würde mich schrecklich darüber freuen!  Tiefer im Wald findest du wilde Tiger und Young Tiger, die sich dort breit gemacht haben.  Ziehe ihnen alle Zähne.  Bringst du mir 50 Zähne, bitte?  Also nicht weniger aber auch nicht mehr.
1	8796	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_027_03	어흥! 역시.. 호랑이는 좀 무섭죠? 도와주실 분이 없어서 슬픕니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Eeny, meeny...  I guess it really IS a difficult task, isn't it?  Woe is me!  There's no one to help me.	0	0	0	Eeny, meeny...  Sanırım gerçekten zor bir iş, değil mi?  Yazıklar olsun bana!  Bana yardım edecek kimse yok.	Pito, pito... Supongo que realmente ES una tarea difícil, ¿verdad? ¡Pobre de mí! No hay nadie que me ayude.	حادي بادي... أعتقد بأنها مهمة صعبة حقًا، أليس كذلك؟ واآسفاه! ليس هناك من يساعدني.	Eins, zwei...  Ich nehme an, dies ist wahrhaftig eine schwierige Aufgabe, nicht wahr?  Etwas Bedenken habe ich schon!  Es kann dir niemand dabei helfen.
1	8797	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_027_04	새끼 맹호와 맹호들의 이빨을 뽑아주십시오. 50개만 뽑아주시면 수행자의 주화를 드리겠습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Pull out the teeth of Young Tigers and Tigers.  Bring me 50 of them and I will give you Monk's Tokens.	0	0	0	Young Tiger’lerin ve Tiger'lerin dişlerini çekin. Bana onlardan 50 tane getir, sana Monk’un Simgelerini vereceğim.	Sácales los dientes a Young Tigers y a Tigers. Tráeme 50 y te daré Monk's Tokens.	اقتلع أسنان Young Tigers وTigers. أحضر لي 50 منهم وسأعطيك عملات Monk's Tokens الرمزية.	Ziehe die Zähne der Young Tiger und Tiger.  Bringe mir 50 davon und ich gebe dir Monk's Token.
1	8798	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_027_05	하나, 둘, 셋… 오십. 와, 정말 딱 맞춰 오셨군요. 마치 어디선가 몇 개를 모았는지 알려라도 주는 것처럼 정확합니다. 후후. 덕분에 이 숲길도 당분간은 조용하겠네요. 저의 고민을 해결해 주셨으니 이 수행자의 주화를 드리겠습니다. 사양 말고 받아주십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	One, two, three...  Fifty.  Wow.  How precise of you.  You would make a good mathematician.  *chuckles*  Thanks to you, the forest should be quiet for a while.  I will give you this Monk's Token for helping me work through my issues.  Please, take it.	0	0	0	Bir, iki, üç…  Elli.  Vay be.  Ne kadar titizsin.  Senden iyi matematikçi çıkar.  *kahkaha atıyor*  Teşekkür ederim, orman bir süreliğine sakinleşir.  Bana sorunlarımı çözmede yardımcı olduğun için bu Monk’un simgelerini sana vereceğim.  Lütfen şunu al.	Uno, dos, tres... Cincuenta. Guau. Qué precisión. Serías un buen matemático. *risas* Gracias a ti, el bosque debería estar tranquilo una temporada. Te daré este Monk's Token por ayudarme con mis asuntos. Quédatelo, por favor.	واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة... خمسون. يا للروعة! ما هذا المدى من الدقة التي تتصف بها. إنك تصلح لأن تكون متخصصًا في الرياضيات. *ضحكات خافتة* شكرًا لك، يجب أن تكون الغابة هادئة لفترة من الوقت. سأعطيك عملات Monk's Token الرمزية نظير مساعدتك لي في التغلب على هذه المشكلات. من فضلك، خذها.	Eins, zwei, drei...  fünf.  Wow.  Wie abgezählt.  Aus dir würde ein guter Mathematiker werden.  *lacht*  Danke, der Wald wird jetzt eine Zeitlang ruhig sein.  Ich geben dir diesen Monk's Token, da du mir geholfen hast das Problem zu lösen.  Bitte nimm ihn.
1	8799	SN_TALK_QNO_N_CH_027_06	음.. 저를 도와주신 것은 감사하지만 가방 안에 빈 공간이 없으면 사례를 할 수가 없습니다. 가방에 공간부터 확보해주시기 바랍니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Hmm...  I really AM grateful for your help, but I can't show my gratitude if you have no room in your inventory.  Please, make sure that you have enough space in your inventory first.	0	0	0	Hmm...  Gerçekten müteşekkirim ama stoğunda yer yoksa minnettarlığımı gösteremem.  Lütfen önce stoğunda yeterli yer bulunduğundan emin ol.	Hmm... Realmente ESTOY agradecido por tu ayuda, pero no puedo demostrarte mi gratitud si no tienes espacio en tu inventario. Por favor, asegúrate de que tienes espacio suficiente en tu inventario primero.	همم... إنني ممتن حقًا لمساعدتك، ولكن لا يمكنني إبداء امتناني إذا لم يكن لديك مساحة في مخزونك. من فضلك، تأكد أولاً من وجود مساحة كافية في مخزونك.	Hmm...  Ich bin dir für deine Hilfe dankbar. Ich kann dir meine Dankbarkeit jedoch nicht zeigen, da du in deinem Inventar keinen Platz hast.  Bitte mache zuerst Platz in deinem Inventar.
