1	750	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_06	자네의 소지품이 너무 많아서 물건을 줄 수가 없네. 2칸 이상 비우고 오게.	0	0	0	0	0	Your inventory is full. Empty some slots and come again.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu. Biraz boş yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Tu inventario esta lleno. Vacía algunos espacios y regresa de nuevo.	خزينتك ممتلئة. أرجوك قم بالتخلص من بعض الأدوات غير الضرورية أولاً.	Dein Inventar ist voll. Sorge für Platz, dann komm wieder.
1	751	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_07	정제된 보약과 보리의 편지를 획득했습니다. 장안의 잡화점 점원 진진에게 가져다 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've obtained the medicine and the letter from Bori. Deliver them to Jinjin, the shop keeper of accessories shop, in Jangan.	0	0	0	Bori'den ilacı ve mektubu aldın. Onları Jangan'daki aksesuar dükkanının satıcısı Jinjine götür.	Has obtenido la Medicine y la Letter de Bori. Entrégaselas a Jinjin, la dependienta de la tienda de accesorios en Jangan.	لقد حصلت على جميع الدواء والخطاب من Bori. قم بتوصيلهم إلى Jinjin حارس متجر الاكسسوارات في Jangan.	Du hast die Medizin und den Brief von Bori bekommen. Bring sie zu Jinjin im Zubehörladen in Jangan.
1	752	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_08	아 어서 오세요. 보리 아저씨에게 이야기는 들었어요.
아사덕 아저씨네 오빠들 정말 착한 오빠들이었는데… 아직도 슬퍼요. 흑흑.
오빠들을 위해서라도 정말 예쁘게 포장을 해서 아사덕 아저씨에게 드려야겠네요. 
잠시만 기다리세요. 정성껏 포장해서 가져올게요.	0	0	0	0	0	Ho, come. I heard from Bori.
The children of Leegak were wonderful people… It's a pity. 
For them, I'll pack these up really beautifully. Wait here. I'll pack them up and come back.	0	0	0	Ah, gel, Bori'den haberi aldım.
Leegak'ın çocukları mükemmel insanlardı… Çok yazık.
Bunları, onlar için çok şık bir şekilde paketleyeceğim. Burada bekle. Şunları paketleyip geliyorum.	Oye, Ven. Escuché de Bori que los niños de Leegak eran maravillosos. Es una pena. Por ellos, voy a empacar estas cosas para que queden muy bonitas. Espera aquí, los empacaré y regreso.	هاي .. تعال .. لقد سمعت من Bori.
أطفال Leegak كانوا أناساً رائعين .. ياللشفقة.
بالنسبة لهم سأقوم بتغليف هذه بشكل جميل جداً. أنتظر هنا. سأغلفهم وسأعود إليك.	Ho, komm her. Ich habe von Bori gehört.
Die Kinder von Leegak waren wunderbar… Es ist so schade um sie. 
Für sie werde ich das richtig gut einpacken. Warte hier. Ich verpacke sie, dann komme ich wieder.
1	753	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_09	짜잔. 예쁘죠. 제가 지금까지 만든 선물 포장 중 제일 예쁜 것 같아요.
어서 아사덕 아저씨에게 가져다 주세요.
이걸 받으면 슬픈 아저씨 마음이 조금은 위로가 될 거에요.
그럼 수고하세요~.	0	0	0	0	0	How about this? I think this is the best packaging I have ever made.
Hurry and bring this to Leegak. This may comfort his broken heart.	0	0	0	Ne dersin? Sanırım bu benim şu ana kadar yaptığım en güzel paket. Acele et bunu Leegak'a götür. Bu belki onun kırık kalbine teselli olur.	¿Qué tal esto? Creo que es el mejor empaque que jamás había hecho. De prisa, llévale esto a Leegak para reconfortar su corazón roto.	ماذا عن ذلك؟ أعتقد أن هذا أفضل تغليف قد فعلته من قبل.
أسرع وخذهم هذه إلى Leegak. فربما يريح هذا قلبه المحطم.	Wie gefällt dir das? Das ist die beste Verpackung, die ich je gemacht habe.
Bring das schnell zu Leegak. Vielleicht tröstet das sein gebrochenes Herz.
1	754	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_10	아직도 안 전해 주셨어요? 혹시 쑥스러워서 그러신 거에요?
에이~ 아사덕 아저씨가 정말 기뻐하실 거에요. 어서 가져다 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Not yet delivered? Are you shy perhaps?
Leegak will be really happy if he gets this. Go quickly.	0	0	0	Hala teslim etmedin mi? Belki de utanmışsındır?
Leegak bunu aldığında çok mutlu olacak. Çabucak git.	¿No entregado aún? ¿Quizá eres tímido? Leegak estará muy feliz de recibir esto. Ve rápido.	لم تقم بتوصيلها بعد؟ ربما أنت خجول؟
Leegak سيفرح جداً عندما تصله هذه. اذهب بسرعة.	Noch nicht abgeliefert? Bist du vielleicht schüchtern?
Leegak wird sehr glücklich sein, wenn er das bekommt. Geh schnell.
1	755	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_11	무슨 물건이 그리 많으세요. 좀 비우고 오세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Do you have in your inventory? Empty some slots and come again.	0	0	0	Envanterine ne halt doldurdun böyle? Biraz yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	¿Qué demonios tienes en tu inventario? Vacía algunos espacios y regresa de nuevo.	ماذا لديك في خزينتك؟ قم بإفراغ بعض المواضع ثم عد مرة أخرى.	Was hast du nur in deinem Inventar? Sorge für Platz, dann komm wieder.
1	756	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_12	보리가 보낸 생일 선물이라고 했소? 그 친구가 나에게 생일 선물을 보내다니 오래 살고 볼일이오.
포장도 정말 예쁘구먼. 아마도 진진이 했을 테지.
어디 보자. 무슨 노망이 들어서 이걸 보냈을까나.
(주섬주섬 포장을 뜯어본 후 안에 들어있는 편지를 읽는다.)	0	0	0	0	0	Did you say Bori sent this to me as a birthday present? He surprises me. I've never expected any birthday present from him.
And the package is very beautiful. Perhaps this is Jinjin's work.
(Opening the present and reads the letter.)	0	0	0	Bunu bana doğum günü hediyesi olarak Bori'nin gönderdiğini mi söylüyorsun? Beni çok şaşırttı. Ondan asla bir doğum günü hediyesi beklemezdim.
Ve pakette çok güzel. Muhtemelen bunu Jinjin yapmış.
(Hediyeyi açar ve mektubu okur.)	¿Dijiste que Bori me envió esto? Me sorprende. Nunca esperé un regalo de cumpleaños de él. Y el empaque es muy bonito. Quizá es trabajo de Jinjin. (Abre el empaque y lee la carta.)	هل تقول أن Bori أرسل هذه لي هدية عيد ميلاد؟ 
لقد فاجأني. لم اتوقع مطلقاً هدية عيد ميلاد منه.
والتغليف جميل جداً ربما هذا عمل Jinjin.
)يفتح الهدية ويقرأ الخطاب(	Du sagst, dass Bori mir das als Geburtstagsgeschenk schickt? Er überrascht mich. Ich hätte nie ein Geburtstagsgeschenk von ihm erwartet.
Und die Verpackung ist so schön. Vielleicht war das Jinjin.
(Er öffnet das Geschenk und liest den Brief.)
1	757	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_13	(천천히 편지를 다 읽어본 후 눈물을 펑펑 흘린다.)
이게 내 아들들이 나에게 해주려 했던 선물이라니.
난 이런 거 필요 없는데.... 그저 너희들만 내 곁에 있어주면 되는데.... 이 못난 아버지 때문에 목숨을 잃다니 바보 같은 놈들. 흑흑.
부모보다 먼저 세상을 떠나다니 에이 나쁜 놈들. 흑흑흑.
(한참을 울다가 간신히 정신을 차린다.)
고맙소이다. 그런 사정이 있는 줄도 모르고 그 동안 먼저 세상을 떠난 자식들을 원망만 하고 있었구려.
내가 못난 자식들을 대신해서 감사의 인사를 드리겠소. 정말 고맙소.	0	0	0	0	0	(Slowly reads through the letter and bursts into tears.)
Is this the present that my children wanted to give me?
I didn't need this.... Just being with all of them was my wish.... How stupid they were, sacrificing their lives for the poor father. (Crying).
Leaving before the parent. What cruel children they are! (Crying.)
(Cries softly and long. Pulls himself together.)
Thank you. Without knowing this, I would have resented my children for leaving me so early.
I want to say, on behalf of my poor children, that I am eternally grateful.	0	0	0	(Mektubu yavaşça okur ve göz yaşlarına boğulur.)
Bu çocuklarımın bana vermek istedikleri hediye mi?
Buna ihtiyacım yoktu.... Tek isteğim hep beraber olmaktı.... Ne kadar aptallar, garip babaları için hayatlarını feda ettiler. (Ağlıyor.)
Ana baba'dan önce gittiler. Ne zalim çocuk bunlar! (Ağlıyor.) (Usulca uzun süre ağlıyor. Kendine çeki düzen veriyor.)
Teşekkür ederim. Bunu bilmeseydim, beni bu kadar erken terk ettikleri için onlara kızardım.
Çocuklarım adına ebediyen minnettar kalacağımı söylemek istiyorum.	(Lee lentamente la carta y estalla en llanto) ¿Este es el regalo que mis hijos me iban a traer? No lo necesitaba....Mi deseo sólo era estar con ellos... Que tontos fueron, sacrificando sus vidas por el pobre padre. (Llorando) ¡Yéndose antes que el padre! ¡Qué niños tan crueles son! (llorando) (Llora pausadamente y por un largo rato. Se compone.) Gracias. De no saber esto, me hubiese resentido con mis hijos por dejarme tan pronto. En nombre de mis pobres hijos, quiero decir que estoy eternamente agradecido.	يقرأ الخطاب ببطء ... ويذرف الدموع

هل هذه الهدية أراد أطفالي إعطائها لي؟
أنا لا أحتاج هذا ... فقد كانت أمنيتي أن أظل معهم جميعاً .. كم هم أغبياء ضحوا بحياتهم من أجل والدهم البائس. )يبكي(
غادروا خلف الهدية. يالهم من أطفال قساه! )يبكي(
)يبكي بهدوء ولفترة طويلة. ينتزع نفسه من البكاء(
شكراً لك. بدون معرفة هذا فكنت سأستاء من أطفالي لمغادرتهم مبكراً.
أرغب في قول بالنيابة عن أطفالي البؤساء أنني ممتن لهم إلى الأبد.	(Langsam liest er den Brief und bricht in Tränen aus.)
Das ist das Geschenk, das mir meine Kinder machen wollten?
Ich habe das nicht gebraucht... Ich wollte nur mit ihnen zusammen sein... Wie dumm von ihnen, ihre Leben für ihren armen Vater zu opfern. (Weint).
Vor dem Vater zu sterben. Was für grausame Kinder sie sind! (Weint.)
(Weint leise und lange. Reißt sich zusammen.)
Danke. Ohne das zu wissen, hätte ich meinen Kindern nie vergeben, mich so früh zu verlassen.
Auch im Namen meiner Kinder, wir werden dir ewig dankbar sein.
1	758	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_14	포장된 생일선물을 획득했습니다. 돈황의 특산품점 노인 아사덕에게 전달해 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've gained the present package. Bring it to Leegak Trade shop in Donwhang.	0	0	0	Present package'yi aldın. Onu Donwhang'daki Ticaret dükkanı, Leegak'a götür.	Has obtenido el Present Package. Llévalo a la tienda de Leegak en Donwhang.	لقد حصلت على الهدية المغلفة. خذها إلى Leegak في متجر Donwhang.	Du hast die Present Package. Bring sie zu Leegaks Laden in Donwhang.
1	759	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_15	어서오세요. 돈황에서부터 오시느라 수고가 많으셨어요.	0	0	0	0	0	Come in come in. You have traveled quite far from Donhwang	0	0	0	Gel, içeri gir. Donwhang'dan uzun bir yolculuk yapıp geldin.	Pasa, pasa. Has viajado muy lejos desde Donwhang.	تعال هنا تعال هنا .. لقد سافرت كثيراً من Donwhang.	Herein, herein. Die Reise von Donwhang war weit.
1	760	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_POTION_3_16	진진에게 생일선물에 대해서 물어보세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Ask Jinjin about the birthday gift.	0	0	0	Birthday gift hakkında Jinjin'le konuş.	Pregunta a Jinjin sobre el Birthday Gift.	اسأل Jinjin عن هدية عيد الميلاد.	Frag Jinjin nach dem Geburtstagsgeschenk.
1	761	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_01	얼마 전에 호탄에서 돈황으로 이동을 하던 여행자들이 옹의 습격을 받아서 돈황의 병사들이 출동하여 그들을 구해준 적이 있습니다.
정말 힘든 구조 작업이었지만 지나가던 헌터분의 빠른 신고 덕에 크게 다친 사람 없이 무사히 사람들을 구할 수 있었지요.
그런데 사람들을 구하던 중에 저를 공격하던 옹 한 마리에게 저의 결혼 반지를 빼앗기고 말았지 뭡니까.
저에게는 정말 중요한 반지인데 사사로운 일 때문에 자리를 비울 수도 없고 고민입니다.
저 대신에 반지를 좀 찾아다 주시면 안되겠습니까?
사례는 톡톡히 해 드리겠습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	When we were moving from Hotan to Donwhang earlier, we were attacked by Ongs and the soldiers of Donwhang rescued us. They were able to help us only becasue a hunter reported the situation early enough.
But I lost my wedding ring during combat. It's very important to me but I can't stay away from here on a private affair.
Can you bring my ring back? I'll pay you enough.	0	0	0	Geçenlerde Hotan'dan Donwhang'a giderken saldırıya uğradık ve Donwhang'ın askerleri bizi kurtardı. Bizi bir avcının haber vermesiyle çok çabuk kurtardılar.
Ama saldırı sırasında wedding ring'imi kaybettim. Bu benim için çok önemli fakat şahsi meselelerim için buradan ayrılamam.
Ring'imi geri getirebilir misin? Yeterince para veririm.	Al principio, cuando nos estábamos mudando de Hotan para Donwhang, fuimos atacados y unos soldados de Donwhang nos rescataron. Ellos pudieron rescatarnos sólo a nosotros tan rápido gracias al reporte de un cazador. Pero perdí mi Wedding Ring durante el combate. Es muy importante para mí, pero tengo prohibido alejarme de aquí si es por un asunto privado. ¿Puedes traérmelo de vuelta? Te pagaré lo suficiente.	عندما كنا مسافرين من Hotan إلى Donwhang هذا الصباح هوجمنا ولكن لحسن الحظ أنقذنا جنود Donwhang.
أستطاعوا إنقاذنا بسرعة بفضل بلاغ صياد لهم.
ولكني فقدت خاتم الزفاف أثناء القتال.
إنه هام جداً لي ولكني لا أستطيع الابتعاد عن هنا لشأن شخصي. 
هلا أعدت الخاتم لي؟
سأدفع لك ما يكفي.
	Als wir von Hotan nach Donwhang reisten, wurden wir von Ongs angegriffen. Die Soldaten von Donwhang haben uns gerettet. Sie konnten uns nur so schnell erreichen, weil ein Jäger früh von der Situation berichtete.
Aber während des Kampfes habe ich meinen Ehering verloren. Er ist mir sehr wichtig, aber ich kann hier wegen einer Privatangelegenheit nicht weg.
Kannst du meinen Ring zurückbringen? Ich werde genug bezahlen.
1	762	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_02	감사합니다. 반지를 가져간 옹의 모습을 제가 기억하지 못해서 아마도 보이는 옹 전부를 잡으셔야 할지도 모르겠습니다.
그래도 꼭 찾아주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Thank you. I can't remember the appearance of the Ong that took my ring. So you have to kill all of them. Anyway be sure to get my ring back.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. Ring'imi alan Ong'un görünüşünü hatırlamıyorum. O yüzden hepsini öldürmek zorundasın. Her neyse, benim ring'im olduğundan emin ol.	Gracias. No puedo recordar la apariencia del Ong que tomó mi Wedding Ring, así que debes matarlos a todos. De cualquier modo, asegúrate de traérmelo de regreso.	شكراً لك لا يمكنني تذكر ظهور الOng الذين أخذوا خاتمي. لذا يجب عليك قتلهم جميعاً. على آية حال تأكد من الحصول على الخاتم.	Danke. Ich erinnere mich nicht, wie der Ong ausgesehen hat, der meinen Ring gestohlen hat. Also musst du alle töten. Bring mir jedenfalls meinen Ring zurück.
1	763	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_03	우…난 이제 마누라에게 맞아 죽었다. 아이고~	0	0	0	0	0	Oh…I'm so dead. My wife will beat me to death. Oh, god.	0	0	0	Of…Ben bir ölüyüm. Karım beni öldürecek. Of allahım.	Oh... Estoy muerto. Mi esposa me matará. Oh, Dios	أوه ... أنا محروم تماماً. ستضربني زوجتي حتى الموت أوه يا إلهي.	Oh… Ich bin ein toter Mann. Meine Frau wird mich umbringen. Oh Gott.
1	764	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_04	아직 못 찾으셨나요?
제 마누라가 눈치채기 전에 하루빨리 찾아야 합니다. 서둘러 주세요.
마누라가 이 사실을 알면 전 죽습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Have you found it yet?
You have to find it before my wife..If she figures out, I am so dead…w-oh just hurry, please.
	0	0	0	Hala bulamadın mı?
Karım farketmeden önce onu bulmalısın..off..lütfen acele et.
Ben öldüm.	¿No lo has encontrado aún? Debes encontrarlo antes que mi esposa... se dé cuenta... Ay sólo date prisa, por favor. Estoy muerto.	لم تجده بعد؟
يجب أن تجده قبل أن تكتشف زوجتي ذلك .. أسرع من فضلك.
أنا محروم تماماً.	Hast du ihn gefunden?
Du musst ihn finden, bevor meine Frau... Wenn sie es herausfindet, bin ich tot … oh, beeil dich bitte.

1	765	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_05	사례를 하고 싶은데 소지품창이 꽉 찼군요. 소지품을 5칸 이상 비우고 다시 오세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Your inventory is full. Empty some slots and come again.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu. Biraz boş yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Tu inventario está lleno. Vacía algunos espacios y regresa de nuevo.	خزينتك ممتلئة. أرجوك قم بالتخلص من بعض الأدوات غير الضرورية أولاً ثم عد لي مرة أخرى.	Dein Inventar ist voll. Sorge für Platz, dann komm wieder.
1	766	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_06	휴. 다행히도 마누라가 눈치채기 전에 찾아주셔서 감사합니다.	0	0	0	0	0	Phew. You've gotten my ring back before my wife figured things out. Thank you.	0	0	0	Oh. Karım farketmeden önce ringimi geri aldın. Teşekkürler.	Fiuh. Has traído mi Wedding Ring de vuelta antes de que mi esposa se diese cuenta. Gracias.	يا إلهي ... لقد أعدت خاتمي مرة أخرى قبل أن تكتشف زوجتي ذلك.. شكراً لك.	Mensch. Du hast mir den Ring zurückgebracht, bevor meine Frau etwas erfahren hat. Danke.
1	767	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE1_1_07	척만의 결혼 반지를 획득했습니다. 척만에게 가져다 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	You've gained the wedding ring of Cheogman. Get it to Cheogman.	0	0	0	Manho'nun wedding ring'ini ele geçirdin. Onu Manho'ya götür.	Has obtenido el Wedding Ring de Cheogman. Entrégalo a Manho.	لقد حصلت على خاتم زفاف شايوجمان. خذه إلى Manho.	Du hast den Wedding Ring of Cheogman. Bring ihn zu Cheogman.
1	768	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_01	요즘 꽃의 요정의 꿈을 계속 꾸고 있습니다. 그들은 자신들의 동족인 혈마화와 혈사화가 타림분지가 사막이 되면서 미쳐버렸다며 그들을 해방시켜 달라고 부탁하고 있었습니다. 그 간절한 목소리가 꿈을 깬 뒤에도 잊혀지지가 않아요. 저를 대신해서 꽃의 요정들의 바람을 이루어주시지 않으시겠습니까?	0	0	0	0	0	Nowadays, I am constantly dreaming about flower fairies. They were saying the Blood Devil Flowers and the Blood Death Flowers who were of the same race had gone mad as Tarim Basin became a desert, and asked me to liberate them. I couldn’t forget that pleading voice even after waking up from the dream. Could you fulfill the wishes of the flower fairies on behalf of me?	0	0	0	Bugünlerde sürekli olarak çiçek perileri ile ilgili rüya görüyorum. Aynı ırktan olan Blood Devil Flowers ve Blood Death Flowers'ları söylüyorlar ve Tarim Basin çölleştikçe deliye dönüyor, benden kendilerini serbest bırakmamı istiyorlar. Rüyadan uyandığımda dahi bu rica kokan sesi unutamıyorum. Çiçek perilerinin isteklerini benim adıma yerine getirebilir misiniz?	Hoy en día, sueño constantemente con hadas de las flores. Decían que los Blood Devil Flower y los Blood Death Flower, que pertenecían a la misma raza, se habían vuelto locos cuando la Cuenca de Tarim se convirtió en un desierto, y me pidieron que los liberara. No he podido olvidar esa voz suplicante ni siquiera tras despertar del sueño. ¿Podrías cumplir los deseos de las hadas de las flores en mi nombre?	إنني أحلم دائمًا هذه الأيام بجنيات الأزهار. وقد أخبروني بأن أزهار Blood Devil Flowers وBlood Death Flowers، وهم من نفس السلالة، جن جنونهم لأن حوض Tarim قد أصبح جافًا كالصحراء، كما طلبوا مني إعتاقهم. إنني لا أستطيع نسيان ذلك الصوت المتضرع حتى بعد استيقاظي من الحلم؛ فهل تستطيع تحقيق أمنيات جنيات الزهور نيابة عني؟	Heute träume ich ständig von Blumenelfen. Sie sagten, die Blood Devil Flowers und die Blood Death Flowers, die von derselben Gattung seien, seien verrückt geworden, als das Tarimbecken eine Wüste geworden ist, und baten mich, sie zu befreien. Ich konnte diese flehentliche Stimme auch nach dem Aufwachen nicht vergessen. Könntest du die Wünsche der Blumenelfen für mich erfüllen?
1	769	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_02	제가 이 얘기를 꺼내는 이유는 얼마 전부터 밤마다 꽃 요정들이 저에게 찾아와 제발 자신들을 죽여달라고 애원하는 꿈을 꾸고 있습니다.
그 슬픈 목소리를 듣고 있다 보면 저 자신도 너무나 슬퍼져서 잠에서 깨어나버립니다.
제가 꿈에서 본 것이 꽃 요정들의 간절한 바람인지 단순히 꿈일 뿐인지는 잘 모르겠지만 왠지 그들을 죽여주지 않으면 이 꿈이 계속 될 거 같아 불안합니다.
저 대신에 꽃 요정들의 바람을 이루어주시지 않으시렵니까? 불쌍한 요정들을 구제해 주십시오.	0	0	0	0	0	The reason why I'm telling this story is that I dream every night that the elves of flowers come to me and ask me to kill them. I can feel how sad they are. I want to free them from this terrible destiny. Can you fulfill the wish of the elves? Rescue the elves from this terrible life.	0	0	0	Bunu sana anlatmamın sebebi her gece rüyamda flower elf'lerinin gelip benden onları öldürmemi istemeleri. Ne kadar üzgün olduklarını hissedebiliyorum. Onları bu korkunç kaderden kurtarmak istiyorum. Elflerin dileğini yerine getirir misin? Elfleri bu korkunç hayattan kurtar.	La razón por la cual estoy contando esta historia es que sueño todas las noches que los elfos de flores vienen a mí y me piden que los mate. Puedo imaginar lo triste que están. Quiero liberarlos de su terrible destino. ¿Puedes cumplir el deseo de los elfos? Salva a los elfos de su terrible vida.	سبب إخباري هذه القصة لك هو أنني أحلم كل ليلة بعفاريت الزهور هذه تأتي إلي وتطلب مني قتلهم.
أستيقظ لأنني أشعر بمدى الأسى الذي يشعرون به. 
أنا لست واثقاً هل هذا مجرد حلم أم أنها أمنية لهذه العفاريت. ولكن أنا أشعر بأن هذا الكابوس سيستمر إلا إذا قتلتهم.
هلا لبيت أمنية العفاريت أنقذهم من حياتهم البائسة هذه.	Ich erzähle dir das, weil ich jede Nacht träume, wie die Blumenelfen zu mir kommen und mich bitten, sie zu töten. Ich kann spüren, wie traurig sie sind. Ich will sie von diesem schrecklichen Schicksal befreien. Kannst du den Wunsch der Elfen erfüllen? Erlöse die Elfen von diesem schrecklichen Leben.
1	770	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_03	이제는 혈마화와 혈사화가 되어버린 꽃 요정들을 500마리만 죽여주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Kill 500 of Blood Evil Flowers and Blood Death Flowers.	0	0	0	500 Blood Evil Flower ve Blood Death Flower öldür.	Mata 500 Blood Evil Flowers y Blood Death Flowers.	اقتل 500 من Blood Evil Flower و Blood Death Flower.	Töte 500 Blood Evil Flowers und Blood Death Flowers.
1	771	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_04	하긴 저의 말이 좀 안 믿어지실 수도 있죠. 뭐 괜찮아요.	0	0	0	0	0	Yeah, my story sounds unbelivable. No problem.	0	0	0	Tabi, hikayem kulağa inandırıcı gelmiyor. Sorun değil.	Sí, mi historia suena increíble. No hay problema.	يااااااااه .. قصتي تبدو صعبة التصديق لا توجد مشكلة.	Ja, meine Geschichte hört sich unglaubwürdig an. Kein Problem.
1	772	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_05	혈마화와 혈사화들은 타림분지의 동쪽 지역에 많이 있습니다.	0	0	0	0	0	You can find the Blood Evil Flowers and Blood Death Flowers to the east of Tarimbunji.	0	0	0	Blood Evil Flowers ve Blood Death Flowers Tarimbunji'nin doğusunda bulabilirsin.	Puedes encontrar Blood Evil Flower y Blood Death Flower al este de Tarimbunji.	ستجد Blood Evil Flower و Blood Death Flower شرق Tarimbunji.	Du kannst die Blood Evil Flowers und Blood Death Flowers östlich von Tarimbunji finden.
1	773	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_06	사례를 하고 싶은데 가지고 계신 물건이 너무 많네요. 소지품창을 비우고 다시 오세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Your inventory is full. Empty your slots first and come to me again.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu. Biraz yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Tu inventario está lleno. Vacía algunos espacios y regresa de nuevo.	خزينتك ممتلئة. أرجوك قم بالتخلص من بعض الأدوات غير الضرورية أولاً ثم عد لي مرة أخرى.	Dein Inventar ist voll. Sorge für Platz, dann komm wieder zu mir.
1	774	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_07	꽃 요정들을 대신해서 감사 드립니다.
이제 편안하게 잘 수 있을 것 같네요.	0	0	0	0	0	I'll thank you on behalf of the flower elves.
Now they can pass away in peace.	0	0	0	Sana çiçek elfleri adına teşekkür ederim.
Artık huzura erebilirler.	Te agradezco en nombre de los elfos de flores. Ahora ellos pueden descansar en paz.	أرغب في شكرك نيابة عن فلاور. الآن يمكنهم المرور بسلام.	Ich danke dir im Namen der Blumenelfen.
Jetzt können sie in Frieden sterben.
1	775	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_08	아직도 요정들의 애원이 해결되지 않았나 봐요. 꿈에서 계속 나오네요.
다시 한번만 꽃 요괴들을 500마리만 죽여주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Still they once again appear in my dreams asking me to kill them.
Please kill 500 of flower monsters again.	0	0	0	Hala rüyalarıma girip onları öldürmemi söylüyorlar.
Lütfen bir kez daha 500 flower monster öldür.	Aparecen una vez más en mis sueños pidiéndome que los mate. Por favor, mata 500 monstruos-flores de nuevo.	يظلون يظهرون مرة أخرى في أحلامي يطلبون مني قتلهم.
أرجوك اقتل 500 من وحوش Flower مرة أخرى.	Und wieder erscheinen sie in meinen Träumen und wollen, dass ich sie töte.
Bitte töte wieder 500 Flower Monster.
1	776	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_09	꽃 요괴 사냥을 완료했습니다. 도각에게 보고하러 가세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Hunting the flower monster is completed. Go and report to Dogag.	0	0	0	Flower monster avı tamamlandı. Git ve Dooil'e bildir.	La caza de los monstruos-flores está completa. Infórmalo a Dogag.	تم اصطياد وحوش فلاور. اذهب وأخبر دوجاج.	Die Jagd auf die Flower Monster ist abgeschlossen. Erstatte Dooil Bericht.
1	777	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_SOLDIER_WE2_1_10	오늘 저의 부탁을 들어주셨으니 편히 잘 수 있을 것 같습니다.
내일 다시 찾아와 주시지 않으시렵니까?	0	0	0	0	0	I think I can sleep peacefully now since you freed the souls of these lost elves. Thank you. See you tomorrow.	0	0	0	Bu kayıp elflerin ruhlarını özgürlüğe kavuşturduğun için sanırım artık huzurlu bir şekilde uyuyabilirim. Teşekkür ederim. Yarın görüşürüz.	Creo que puedo dormir pacíficamente ahora desde que liberaste las almas de los elfos perdidos. Gracias. Nos vemos mañana.	أعتقد أنه يمكنني أن أنام بسلام الآن بعد أن حررت أرواح هذه العفاريت المفقودة. شكراً لك. أراك غداً.	Jetzt kann ich in Ruhe schlafen, da du die Seelen dieser Elfen befreit hast. Danke. Bis morgen.
1	778	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_01	타림분지 남쪽의 메마른 대지에는 비단과 같이 부드러운 뱀의 몸과 화려한 색깔의 피부의 인간의 몸을 가진 여와라는 요괴들이 살고 있다네.
이 여와라는 요괴들은 피부 색깔에 따라 적여와와 흑여와로 나뉘는데 이 여와들의 비늘이 상당히 부드럽고 질이 좋아서 최근에 상인들 사이에서 고가에 매입이 되고 있네.
그런데 이 여와라는 놈들이 워낙 사나워서 비늘을 구하기가 영 힘들단 말이야.
어때? 여와의 비늘을 200개만 구해다 주지 않겠는가? 보상은 두둑이 챙겨주겠네.	0	0	0	0	0	In the dry area of the southern Tarimbunji, there are monsters called Yeowa that has body of silky snakes and colorful skin of human bodies.
Yeowa are divided into two categories: Red Yeowa and  Black Yeowa according to their colors. The skin of the Yeowa is very smooth and of good quality so traders want to sell them at a high price.
But they are very fierce and difficult to get.
Can you get me 200 Yeowa scales? I'll pay you quite a lot.	0	0	0	Güney Tarimbunji'nin kurak bölgesinde , yılan ile insan karışımına benzeyen Yeowa adında canavarlar var. Yeowa iki türe ayrılıyor: renklerin göre, Red Yeowa ve Black Yeowa. Yeowa'nın skin'i o kadar pürüzsüz ve kalitelidir ki tüccarlar onları çok yüksek fiyatlara satarlar. Fakat çok vahşidirler ve ele geçirilmeleri zordur. Bana 200 Yeowa scale getirir misin? Sana epeyce para veririm.	En la vasta zona al sur de Tarimbunji, hay monstruos llamados Yeowa que parecen una fusión entre serpientes y humanos. Los Yeowa estan divididos en dos categorías: Red Yeowa y Black Yeowa según su color. La piel de los Yeowa es muy suave y de buena calidad; es por ello que los comerciantes las quieren vender a un alto precio. Pero son muy feroces y difíciles de obtener. ¿Puedes traerme 200 Scales de Yeowa? Te pagaré muy bien.	في المنطقة الجافة جنوب Tarimbunji توجد وحوش تسمى Yeowa أجسامها خليط ما بين الحيات والبشر.
انقسمت Yeowa إلى فصيلتين: Red Yeowa وBlack Yeowa على حسب ألوانها. جلود Yeowa ناعمة جداً وعالية الجودة. لذلك يريد التجار بيعها بأغلى الأسعار. 
ولكنها شرسة جداً ومن الصعب قتلها. 
هل تستطيع أن تأتي لي بـ 200 من قشور Yeowa؟ سأدفع لك جيداً.	Im trockenen Land im Süden von Tarimbunji gibt es Monster namens Yeowa. Ihre Körper bestehen aus seidigen Schlangen und farbenfroher, menschlicher Haut.
Es gibt zwei Kategorien von Yeowa: Red Yeowa Und Black Yeowa, entsprechend ihrer Farbe. Die Haut der Yeowa ist sehr glatt und von guter Qualität, die Händler verkaufen sie teuer.
Aber sie sind wild und schwer zu jagen.
Kannst du mir 200 Yeowa Scales bringen? Ich werde dich sehr gut bezahlen.
1	779	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_02	하하. 역시 화끈하군. 자 어서 여와의 비늘을 구해다 주게.	0	0	0	0	0	Ha, ha. You are a real man. Mmm..Scales….	0	0	0	Ha, ha. Sen esaslı bir adamsın. Scale'leri bana getir….	Ja ja. Eres un verdadero hombre. Mmm. Scales...	ها ها ها . أنت رجل حقيقي ... مممم .. قشور	Ha, ha. Du bist ein echter Mann. Mmm... Schuppen...
1	780	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_03	일할 사람은 많네. 하하하	0	0	0	0	0	Eh.I can ask someone else then. Ha, ha.	0	0	0	Madem öyle başka birinden isterim. Ha, ha.	¡Eh! Le puedo pedir a otra persona entonces. Ja ja	إذاً يمكنني طلب ذلك من شخص آخر ها ها ها ها	Dann frage ich jemand anderen. Ha, ha.
1	781	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_04	게으름 피우지 말고 어서 구해오게.
여와들은 타림분지 남쪽에 많이 있네.	0	0	0	0	0	Work hard and be quick.
Yeowa slither south of Tarimbunji.	0	0	0	Sıkı çalış, hızlı ol.
Yeowa Tarimbunji'nin güneyinde bulunuyor.	Trabaja duro y rápido. Los Yeowa merodean por el sur de Tarimbunji.	اعمل بجد وبسرعة.
ستجد yeowa شرق Tarimbunji.	Arbeite hart und beeil dich.
Die Yeowa gleiten südlich von Tarimbunji herum.
1	782	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_05	이 아름다운 색깔, 화려한 빛깔, 역시 최고의 재료군.
여기 보상일세. 수고했네.	0	0	0	0	0	Oh, look at these beautiful colours. Yes, it's the best.
Here your reward. Thanks	0	0	0	Oh, şu güzel renklere bak. Evet, bu en iyisi. İşte ödülün. Teşekkürler.	Oh, mira todos esos bellos colores. Sí, es lo mejor. Aquí está tu recompensa. Gracias.	أوه أنظر إلى هذه الألوان الجميلة. نعم إنها الأفضل. خذ مكافأتك. شكراً لك.	Oh, sieh dir diese schönen Farben an. Ja, das sind die besten.
Deine Belohnung. Danke.
1	783	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_06	자네가 좋은 비늘을 많이 가져다 줘서 장사가 아주 잘된다네.
다시 한번만 여와의 비늘을 200개만 가져다 주겠나.
부탁함세.	0	0	0	0	0	Thanks to you, business is hot!
Could you maybe just once more. bring me 200 Yeowa scales?
Your cooperation will be appreciated.	0	0	0	Sayende işlerim açıldı. Belki bir kez daha yapabilirsin, bana 200 Yeowa scale getirir misin? İşbirliğin karşılıksız kalmayacak.	Gracias a ti, el negocio está reñido, ¿podrías, tal vez, traerme 200 Scales de Yeowa? Tu cooperación será apreciada.	شكراً لك العمل على ما يرام!
هل قمت بذلك مرة أخرى أحضر لي 200 من قشور yeowa.
سيتم تقدير تعاونك.	Dank dir läuft das Geschäft wie geschmiert!
Könntest du mir vielleicht noch einmal 200 Yeowa Scales bringen?
Ich wäre dir sehr dankbar.
1	784	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_07	여와의 비늘 수집이 완료되었습니다. 합리극에게 가져다 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Collecting the skin of Yeowa is completed. Bring them to Leegeuk.	0	0	0	Yeowa scale toplama tamamlandı. Onları Leegeuk'a götür.	La recolección de skin de Yeowa está completa. Llévalas a Leegeuk.	تم تجميع قشور yeowa. أحضرهم إلى Leegeuk.	Die Sammlung der Scales of Yeowa ist abgeschlossen. Bring sie zu Leegak.
1	785	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_DOCTOR_3_08	오늘 필요한 여와의 비늘은 모두 구했다네.
내일 다시 찾아와 주게나.	0	0	0	0	0	You have gotten all that is needed today.
Please return tomorrow.	0	0	0	Bugün ihtiyacım olan herşeyi getirdin. Lütfen yarın tekrar gel.	Has obtenido todo lo que se necesita por el día de hoy. Por favor, regresa mañana.	لقد حصلت على جميع ما تحتاجه اليوم. أرجوك عد مرة أخرى غداً.	Du hast mir alles gebracht, was für heute notwendig war.
Bitte komm morgen wieder.
1	786	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_01	얼마 전에 상인조합의 합리극에게 잃어버린 보석들을 찾아주었다고 이야기 들었네.
그래서 말인데 혹시 보석을 찾아주면서 수상한 점을 발견하지는 못했나?
소문에 의하면 합리극이 보석들을 빼앗길 때 그 중에 정말 값비싼 보석이 몇 개 있었는데 그것들을 흑막궁수들이 훔쳐갔다고 하네.
그런데 합리극은 그 보석들이 불법 행위를 통해 보석들이라서 소문이 나면 나라에 빼앗길 까봐 무서워서 신고도 못하고 있는 상황이라고 하더군.
부정한 행위로 모은 재산은 당연히 관아에 보고해야 하는 것인데 합리극은 죽어도 모르는 일이라고 잡아떼니 은밀히 조사를 해보려고 하네.
흑막궁수들을 잡아서 빼앗긴 값비싼 보석 중 100개만 찾아다 주게.	0	0	0	0	0	I heard that you had retrieved Leegeuk's stolen jewels earlier.
Didn't you find anything suspicious while taking back the jewels?
According to rumors, the most expensive of Leegeuk's jewels were taken by the Black Robber archers.
But Leegeuk can't not report this to the proper authorities because he too got them in an illegal way.
Leeguk will deny everything so we are going to investigate secretly.
Defeat the Black Robber archers and take back 100 of the most expensive jewels from them.	0	0	0	Geçenlerde Leegeuk'un çalınan mücevherlerini bulup getirdiğini duydum.
Mücevherleri geri getirdiğinde şüpheli bir şey farketmedin mi? Söylentilere göre Leegeuk'un en pahalı mücevherleri Black Robber archer'lar tarafından alınmış.
Fakat Leegeuk bunu ilgili mercilere bildirmemiş çünkü o da mücevherleri yasal olmayan yollarla ele geçirmiş.
Leegeuk herşeyi inkar edecektir o yüzden gizli bir şekilde araştıracağız. Black Robber archer'ları öldür ve en pahalı mücevherlerden 100 tane getir.	Escuché que has recuperado pronto las joyas robadas de Leegeuk. ¿No encontraste nada sospechoso mientras las llevabas de vuelta? Según los rumores, las Most Expensive Jewels de Leegeuk fueron robadas por los Black Robber Archers. Sin mebrago, Leegeuk no puede reportar esto a las propias autoridades porque él también las tomó de forma ilegal. Leegeuk negará todo, así que vamos a investigar secretamente. Derrota a los Black Robber Archers y trae de vuelta 100 de las Most Expensive Jewels.	لقد سمعت أنك أعدت إلى Leegeuk جواهره هذا الصباح.
هل لاحظت أي شئ مريب أثناء إعادة المجوهرات له؟
طبقاً للشائعات فإن أثمن جواهر Leegeuk قد سرقت منه مرة أخرى سرقها منه الرامي black archers.
ولكن Leegeuk لا يمكنه إبلاغ السلطات لانه حصل عليها أيضاً بطريقة غير شرعية.
وهو ينكر ذلك .. لذلك فنتحقق من ذلك بسرية.
اهزم  Black Robbers archer واستعد 100 من أثمن المجوهرات منهم.	Ich habe gehört, dass du Leegaks gestohlene Juwelen zurückgebracht hast.
Ist dir dabei nichts Verdächtiges aufgefallen?
Den Gerüchten nach sollen die teuersten Juwelen Leegaks von Black Robber Archers gestohlen worden sein.
Aber Leegak kann das nicht der Obrigkeit melden, weil er sie sich auch auf illegale Weise beschafft hat.
Leegak wird das abstreiten, also ermitteln wir heimlich.
Besiege die Black Robber Archers und bring 100 der teuersten Juwelen von ihnen zurück.
1	787	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_02	고맙네. 요즘 헌터 조합이 바빠서 일손이 부족해 부탁하는 것이니 수고 좀 해주게.
아 그리고 보석은 흑막궁수가 가져갔다고 하네. 흑막사수들을 잡아봤자 헛수고일 것이야.	0	0	0	0	0	Thanks. These days the Hunter Association is shorthanded so we're grateful for the help. The jewels were taken by Black Robber archers so defeating Black Robbers is useless.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. Bugünlerde Avcı Derneği eleman kıtlığı çekiyor bu yüzden yardımın için sana minnettarız. Mücevherler Black Robber archer'lar tarafından alındı bu yüzden sırf Black Robber öldürmen yetmez.	Gracias. En estos días la asociación de cazadores estuvo inactiva, así que estamos muy agradecidos por la ayuda. Las Jewels fueron robadas por Black Robber Archers así que vencer a los Black Robbers será inútil.	شكراً لك. هذه الأيام رابطة التجار مشغولة لذا فنحن ممتنون جداً لمساعدتك. لقد أخذ Black Robbers archer الجواهر لذا فمجرد هزيمة Black Robbers عديم النفع.	Danke. Die Jägervereinigung ist momentan unterbesetzt, also sind wir dankbar für Hilfe. Die Juwelen wurden von Black Robber Archers gestohlen, also nützt es nichts, Black Robbers zu töten.
1	788	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_03	나라에 반항하려 하느냐. 이 놈!	0	0	0	0	0	Do you want to betray us? You are mean.	0	0	0	Bize ihanet etmek mi istiyorsun? PİSLİK!	¿Nos quieres traicionar? ¡IDIOTA!	هل ترغب في خيانتنا؟ غبي!	Willst du uns verraten? Du bist gemein.
1	789	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_04	힘이 부치는 것인가. 힘을 내게.
흑막궁수들은 타림분지의 흑막단 근처에 있네.	0	0	0	0	0	Is it too tough for you?
Black Robber archers gather near the Black Robbers of Tarimbunji.	0	0	0	Bu kadarı senin için fazla mı geldi?
Black Robber archer'lar Tarimbunji'li Black Robber'ların yanında toplanıyor.	¿Es demasiado difícil para ti? Los Black Robber Archers se reúnen cerca de los Black Robbers de Tarimbunji.	إنه هذا قاس  جداً عليك؟.
Black Robbers archer تجمعوا بالقرب من Black Robbers في Tarimbunji.	Ist dir das zu schwierig?
Black Robber Archers befinden sich nahe der Black Robbers von Tarimbunji.
1	790	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_05	역시 기대를 저버리지 않는군. 수고했네.
황제 폐하께서 기뻐하실 걸세.	0	0	0	0	0	Yes, you are the man who we need. Thanks. The emperor will be happy with the news.	0	0	0	Evet, ihtiyacımız olan adam sensin. İmparator bu habere çok sevinecek.	Sí, tú eres el hombre que necesitamos. Gracias. El emperador estará contento con la noticia.	نعم أنت الرجل الذي نحتاجه. شكراً لك. سيكون الامبراطور سعيداً لسماع هذه الأخبار.	Ja, genau dich brauchen wir. Danke. Dem Kaiser wird diese Nachricht gefallen.
1	791	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_06	아직 보석이 더 있다고 하네.
나라를 위하여 조금만 더 수고해 주게나.
흑막궁수를 잡아 빼앗긴 값비싼 보석 중 100개만 찾아다 주게.	0	0	0	0	0	I heard that there are more of these jewels. Please help us again. This is for the Emperor.
Take back 100 stolen jewels from the Black Robber archers.	0	0	0	Bu mücevherlerden daha olduğunu duydum. Lütfen bize bir kez daha yardım et. İmparator için.
Black Robber archer'lardan, çalınan 100 mücevheri geri getir.	Escuché que hay más de esas Jewels. Por favor, ayúdanos una vez más. Es para el Emperador. Recupera 100 Stolen Jewels de los Black Robber Archers.	لقد سمعت أنه يوجد المزيد من هذه الجواهر. فساعدنا أرجوك مرة أخرى من أجل الامبراطور.
قم بإعادة 100 من الجواهر المسروقة من Black Robbers archer.	Ich habe gehört, dass es noch mehr dieser Juwelen gibt. Bitte hilf uns wieder. Für den Kaiser.
Bring 100 Stolen Jewels von den Black Robber Archers zurück.
1	792	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_07	값비싼 보석 수집이 완료되었습니다. 하라호에게 가져다 주세요.	0	0	0	0	0	Collecting the priceless jewels is completed. Get them to Haraho.	0	0	0	Paha biçilmez mücevherleri toplama tamamlandı. Onları Haraho'ya götür.	La recolección de Jewels está completa. Llévalas a Haraho.	تم تجميع المجوهرات الثمينة. خذهم إلى Haraho.	Die Sammlung der unbezahlbaren Juwelen ist abgeschlossen. Bring sie zu Haraho.
1	793	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_2_08	오늘 자네가 할 일은 끝났네.
내일 다시 찾아오게나.	0	0	0	0	0	The jobs today are all done. Come back tomorrow.	0	0	0	Bugünlük işlerin hepsi yapıldı. Yarın tekrar kontrol et.	Los trabajos del día de hoy están listos. Vuelve mañana.	تمت مهمة اليوم. تفقد مرة أخرى غداً.	Für heute ist die Arbeit getan. Komm morgen wieder.
1	794	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_3_01	합리극의 부정한 보석을 찾아줘서 고마웠네.
자네의 능력을 높이 사서 부탁을 하나 더 할까 하는데 말이야.
최근에 실크로드를 중심으로 요괴들이 계속해서 늘어나고 있다네. 헌터조합에서 나서서 요괴들을 물리치고 있긴 하지만 워낙에 숫자가 많아서 역부족이야.
사람이 부족하기도 하지만 싸울 때마다 부서지는 무기들을 감당하기도 어렵네.
그래서 생각한 것이 흑막사수들이 쓰는 활을 빼앗아서 우리가 쓰면 좋을 것 같다는 결론을 내렸네.
어때 한번 더 나를 도와주지 않겠나?
흑막사수들이 쓰는 활을 100개만 구해다 주게나.	0	0	0	0	0	Thank you for collecting the jewels of Leegeuk.
I want to ask you one more thing.
The number of monsters is increasing and whenever we can the Hunter Association is there to defeat them but we are shorthanded. Whenever we fight, our weapons break too easily. 
So we have concluded that stealing and using the bows of the Black Robber bowman would be an effective  and elegant solution.
Can you help us? Get us 100 Black Robber bowman bows.	0	0	0	Leegeuk'un mücevherlerini topladığın için teşekkür ederim.
Sana bir şey daha sormak istiyorum. Canavarların sayıları artıyor, elimizden geldiğince Avcı Derneği olarak yetişmeye çalışıyoruz fakat adam kıtlığı çekiyoruz. Ne zaman bir savaşa girsek, silahlarımız hemen parçalanıyor. Ayrıca bu da ciddi bir sorun. Biz de Black Robber bowman'in bow'larını çalıp kullanmanın etkili ve zekice bir çözüm olacağına karar verdik. Bize yardım eder misin? Bize 100 Black Robber bowman bow'u getir.	Gracias por recolectar las Jewels de Leegeuk. Quiero pedirte una cosa más. El número de monstruos está aumentando; siempre que podamos, la asociación de cazadores está allí para derrotarlos, pero en estos momentos estamos inactivos. Siempre que luchamos contra ellos, nuestras armas se rompen fácilmente. Este también es un serio problema. Así que hemos acordado que robar los Bows de los Black Robber Bowman. Sería una efectiva y elegante solución. ¿Puedes ayudarnos? Tráenos 100 Bows de los Black Robber Bowman.	شكراً لك لاستعادة مجوهرات Leegeuk.
أرغب في استعمال خدماتك مرة أخرى لأنني أقدر عقلك وقدراتك بشدة.
عدد الوحوش يتزايد كثيراً في سيلك رود. 
والأشخاص في رابطة الصيادين يحاولون هزيمتهم ولكنهم لا يستطيعون هذا. وأيضاً كلما قاتلناهم تتحطم أسلحنا بسهولة. إنها مشكلة كبيرة.
لقد توصلنا إلى أن سرقة واستخدام الأقواس من Black Robbers bowmen سيكون فعالاً بشكل أكبر هلا ساعدتنا؟
أحضر لنا 100 من أقواس Black Robbers bowmen.	Danke, dass du Leegaks Juwelen gesammelt hast.
Ich will dich um noch etwas bitten.
Es gibt immer mehr Monster, und die Jägervereinigung hat zu viel zu tun, um sie alle zu töten. Immer wenn wir kämpfen, zerbrechen unsere Waffen sehr schnell. 
Also haben wir uns entschlossen, die Bogen der Black Robber Bowman zu stehlen, das wäre eine effektive und elegante Lösung.
Kannst du uns helfen? Besorg uns 100 Black Robber Bowman Bows.
1	795	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_3_02	흑막단에서 활을 쓰는 놈들은 흑막궁수와 흑막사수가 있는데 흑막궁수가 쓰는 활은 질이 좋지 않아서 필요 없고 꼭 흑막사수의 활을 구해와야 되네.
부탁함세.	0	0	0	0	0	Black Robbers have two units who use archery skills. One is the Black Robber archer and the other is Black Robber bowman. The bows Black Robber archer use are not good. I need only the Black Robber bowman's bows. Get them quickly. Thanks.	0	0	0	Kara Soyguncularının okçuluk becerisi olan iki birliği var. Biri Black Robber archer'lar ve diğeri de Black Robber bowman'lar. Black Robber archer'ların kullandıkları bowlar iyi değil. Benim sadece Black Robber bowman bow'larına ihtiyacım var. Çabucak getir onları. Teşekkürler.	Los Black Robber tienen dos unidades que usan habilidades de arquería. Una es los Black Robber Bowman y la otra es la de Black Robber Archers. El uso de los Bows de los Black Robber Archers no es bueno. Sólo necesito los Bows de los Black Robber Bowman. Obtenlos rápido. Gracias.	لدى Black Robbers وحدتين يستخدمونهم في مهارات الرماية. واحدة تسمى Black Robbers archer والأخرى Black Robbers bowmen. Black Robbers archer ليسوا جيدين. أرغب فقط في أقواس Black Robbers bowmen. أحضرها بسرعة. شكراً لك.	Black Robbers haben zwei Einheiten, die mit Pfeil und Bogen kämpfen. Die Black Robber Archer und die Black Robber Bowman. Die Bogen, die die Black Robber Archer benutzen, sind nicht gut. Ich brauche nur die Bogen der Black Robber Bowman. Hol sie schnell. Danke.
1	796	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_3_03	흑막단이 무서운가 보군. 뭐 어쩔 수 없지.	0	0	0	0	0	So you are afraid of Black Robber. Well, I understand.	0	0	0	Demek Kara Soyguncu'dan korkuyorsun. Peki, seni anlıyorum. Ama çok da değil.	Así que le temes a los Black Robbers.Bueno, entiendo.. en realidad no.	إذاً فأنت خائف من Black Robbers حسناً أنا أفهم ذلك ولكن هذا ليس حقيقي.	Du hast also Angst vor den Black Robber. Das kann ich verstehen.
1	797	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_3_04	무기가 없어서 많은 사람들이 요괴들에게 피해를 입고 있네.
어서 구해다 주게.	0	0	0	0	0	Many people are taking damages from the monsters because we lack good weapons.
Be swift.	0	0	0	Sağlam silahları olmadığı için birçok insan canavarlar tarafından katlediliyor.
Süratli ol.	Mucha gente está siendo lastimada por los monstruos por falta de buenas armas. Sé veloz.	تسبب الوحوش في الأضرار للعديد من الناس بسبب نقص الأسلحة الجيدة. 
أسرع.	Viele Leute werden von den Monstern verletzt, weil wir keine guten Waffen haben.
Beeil dich.
1	798	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_3_05	답례를 하고 싶은데 인벤토리가 꽉 차있네. 비우고 오게.	0	0	0	0	0	Your inventory is full so I can't give you anything. Empty some slots and come again.	0	0	0	Envanterin dolu olduğu için sana bir şey veremiyorum. Biraz boş yer açtıktan sonra tekrar gel.	Tu inventario está lleno, así que no puedo darte nada. Vacía algunos espacios y regresa de nuevo.	خزينتك ممتلئة لا يمكنني إعطائك أي شئ. أرجوك قم بالتخلص من بعض الأدوات غير الضرورية أولاً ثم عد لي مرة أخرى.	Aber dein Inventar ist voll, also kann ich dir nichts geben. Sorge für Platz, dann komm wieder.
1	799	SN_TALK_QNO_WC_GENARAL_SW_3_06	매번 고맙네.
이제 이 무기들만 있으면 요괴의 피해를 덜 입을 수 있겠지.	0	0	0	0	0	Thanks.
Now having these  weapons will reduce the damage we take from monsters.	0	0	0	Teşekkürler. Artık bu silahlar sayesinde canavarlardan aldığımız hasarı azaltabileceğiz.	Gracias. Ahora, teniendo estas armas se reducirá el daño que recibimos de los monstruos.	شكراً لك. الآن وبعد الحصول على هذه الأسلحة سيقلل من التدمير الذي تسببه الوحوش.	Danke.
Mit diesen Waffen werden uns die Monster weniger anhaben können.
